<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>10667</idnum><title>Euphoric Relaxation Bliss</title><author>dgplexus</author><substance>damiana</substance><substance>kava</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


Mindset and Setting:
/n
/n
Working as a security guard in an office building, swing shift.  I was somewhat stressed out over being audited &amp; summarily cheated by the state tax people.  So I was searching for a good combination for better relaxation.
/n
/n
Preparation:
/n
/n
I acquired 'DAMIANA 4:1 powder extract' (100 grams) and 'KAVA KAVA standardized extract. 55% kavalactones, 144mg, 90 caps.  I already had some megadose 'B vitamin complex' tablets.  (Each tablet has 100mg of many of the B vitamins, and less of others, in a balanced combination.  Pretty standard.)  I also had about 1oz of soy protein powder.
/n
/n
Dosage and Timing:
/n
/n
After most people left the building, I took the following together:
/n
/n
- One large glass of water (about 16oz)
/n
- One 144mg softgel Kava extract (55% kavalactones)
/n
- 1/4tsp Damiana powder (4:1 extract) mixed with the water
/n
- About 1oz soy protein powder, mixed thoroughly with the water
/n
- One megadose 'B vitamin complex' tablet
/n
/n
Results:
/n
/n
After about 5 minutes, I started to feel a euphoria coming on.  I did not feel mentally impaired, in fact I felt more energized, alert and euphoric than I would without the Damiana in the mix.  I felt much more confident, patient, blissful, and in control.  This was a mild, pleasantly euphoric, and healthy feeling.  My sense of 'well being' was significantly increased.  The effect seemed to peak at about 20 or 30 minutes, and gradually diminished for about 4 or 5 hours.
/n
/n
Notes:
/n
/n
This combination could become habit-forming (psychologically addictive,) but was definitely not physically addictive for me.  After discovering it, I took this combination daily (once or twice a day) for several weeks, then abruptly stopped taking it to test the habit-forming potential of it.  After stopping, I missed the feeling I had while taking it, but I just felt the same as I did before, no worse.
/n
/n
Comparing this combination to Damiana or Kava alone, I would give this combination a '10' (on a scale of 1 to 10,) while Damiana would be a '3' and Kava would be about a '6.'  I was happily surprised at the apparent synergy between the two herbs.
/n
/n
Conveniently, all of its ingredients are legal in the U.S., and the substances are currently easily obtained from many sources.  :-)</bodytext></report>