<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>11083</idnum><title>A Good Thing Gone Wrong - Revisited</title><author>Groovegal</author><substance>mdma</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>



I just wanted to revisit my last experience report and share some new insights with you all.  Since taking E back in September, I've been diagnosed with a slightly overactive thyroid. That's what's been causing my heart palpitations. I was told that stimulants of any kind, coffee, chocolate, and especially E should be avoided.  Hence, my wild night alone was really due to my condition (which I had no clue about at the time!) being overly stimulated by the E. I was placed on a beta-blocker, atenolol, to take care of the palps. 
/n
/n
Remember, I had fallen in love with E. I really wanted to have fun, but I didn't want to die!!! So 3 weeks ago, I did a lot of reading up on the web and found that my beta-blocker can be used to counter the ill effects that the E has on my heart.  Doctors actually use beta-blockers to help people who have overdosed on coke, not to mention it's a heart-attack medication. I went to a well-respected doctor's website where he has a column. He gave this advice, which I took.  I swallowed 50 mgs of atenolol 20 minutes before I took my E. Now, because I was worried, I only took 1/4.  /n  I suggest you do the same, don't you dare pop two pills if you have a sensitive heart.  After 30 minutes, I felt a slight buzz, not totally rolling.   /n

I checked my pulse and I was at a normal rate.  I decided after 2 hours that I'd go ahead and take my other 1/4.  15 minutes later, I was rolling out of my mind.  I was actually kind of scared how hard I was rolling.  I could barely stand up.  Totally a better experience than my last.  My heart rate stayed at a normal rate and I experienced no irregular beats.  
/n
/n
I found however, that I was more nauseous than usual. Where I usually throw up or gag at the onset of the E, this time, I gagged through the night here and there, but never fully threw up. /n  Again, if you have palps, irregular beats, or high blood pressure, you can still have fun.   /n

Beta=blockers are a Godsend! I just take it easy, make sure I'm around people I trust who know about my condition, and don't over do it.  
/n
/n
Take care,
/n
Groovegal.</bodytext></report>