<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>11522</idnum><title>'Social Anxiety' and the Pink Pill Experiment</title><author>Veronica</author><substance>paroxetine</substance><bodytext>


I started taking Paxil after being clinically diagnosed with Social Anxiety Disorder and panic attacks. Now, I have always been willing to try anything once, so I followed my doctors advice.  
/n
/n
It took about 1 week for me to notice the effects of the drug. I started on 10 mg a day and increased to 20 mg in two weeks.  After 2 weeks I was able to function in society without panicking and wanting to die. It was instant confidence for me which before I had only been able to reach through alcohol or E.  Friends and family think it is a miracle. A few friends often get irratated and jealous of my new-found happiness and upbeat nature. 
/n
/n
         After a visit to a new doctor today, he mentioned 
/n
                    a few intersting things. 
/n
/n
1. That I will need to be on Paxil for the rest of my life or until    medical science develops something other than a pink pill.
/n
2. That research shows Paxil is re-constructing DNA in certain areas of the brain.... ??? This is quite interesting
/n
3. I do not have medical and it is getiing expensive.... really!?!
/n
/n
              A few side effects I have noticed... 
/n
                 some are fun... some are not.
/n
/n
1. Balance - like I am walking on a rocky boat from time to time.
/n
/n
2. Very vivid and complex dreams
/n
/n
3. I am like a non-sexual being. No feeling, no interest, no nothin'
/n
/n
4. Enhanced self image, and extreme self confidence
/n
/n
5. Smoking a lot more, Grinding teeth quite often, jaw clenching.
/n
/n
6. Loss of emotion, yet extremely happy and confident @ the same time
/n
/n
7. Have always been blessed by the gift of telepathy, it is now       slowly withering away. Can no longer read minds, and this saddens me.
/n
/n
I am still taking Paxil and will continue for fear of falling back into my old self. I am now vey scared for what will happen if I stop taking the drug. So in fact, medical science has now trapped me financially and emotionally. I am now dependent on a little pink pill... until there is a new teal, turquoise or fuschia pill.</bodytext></report>