<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>116</idnum><title>A Day To Remember</title><author>Alter Ego</author><substance>cacti</substance><bodytext>



I have been interested in the effects of Psychedelic Cacti for awhile.  While using Psychedelics for the last few years I feel I have learned a great deal about myself.  I had mostly used LSD as my psychedelic drug of choice, also MDMA and Mushrooms. I had no way of fathoming what I was to expect with my Cactus experience.  I read somewhere that San Pedro was a fairly good Mescaline producer and legal in the US.  I had heard amazing things about Mescaline from friends and became interested in it's uses in tribal medicine and Native-American religion.  
/n
/n
I decided to try and obtain some through on-line ordering.  I obtained four six inch cacti from a business located in the Netherland.  I recieved my cacti somewhere around a month later.  My first experience was on a day when I had nothing else to do, I ended up plucking ths spines and eating one whole cactus.  I ended up with minimal effects including slight mood disturbances and a kind of phantom image in my peripheral vision.  I did not leave my home for my first voyage and it ended up being something of a waste.  
/n
/n
About a week later I decided to try again.  I ingested two of my remaining three cacti giving one to my friend.  We watched the movie 'Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas' waiting for the effects to become evident.  After somewhere around two or so hours I began to feel energized.  We departed from my house on a journey to no where in particular with hearts full of sunshine.  I began to notice strange designs not evident to me normally.  I was not seeing things that were not there, and not patterns such as would be common with LSD, it was more like everything was enhanced and I could only see the beauty in all things.  I could consider things from all aspects and I had a feeling like everything fit into a grand puzzle, every little thing that we did affected other things, which affected other things.  It sounds awkward when I try to put it into words, but I feel like I really grasped the nature of things, all things.  I realized that everything is made up of atoms and energies that never truly die.  Everything is in cycles always ending up at the beginning again.  
/n
/n
At this moment I felt like everything I have ever worried about was worth no more concern than the death of a bacterium.  I felt I could do no wrong, as my friend and I ventured up to a small pond I felt it would be perfectly natural that I could merge with the water, I felt my body could easily become a fluid to mix and mingle with every molecule of the pond.  Everything was so perfect and I felt I had true insight into the nature of the Universe.  At this point I remember thinking I did not need anything.  It was one of the only times in my life I have not desired anything at all, I was not hungry or thirsty, not discontent, not lusting for something.  
/n
This contrasted with my LSD experiences in that I truly had to work to quiet my soul before I could concentrate on anything or attain any insight, on San Pedro I felt the world's mysteries were bathed in light and presented to me on a silver platter.  I later tried to make a concentrate paste using the boiling technique, this was effective but with a much less rounded experience.  If you are a first time user of Psychedelics and are looking for something legal to posess, try San Pedro, you will not be disappointed.  REMEMBER if you are going to try this you must know it is legal to posess the cactus but not to consume it, so don't shoot your mouth off because you think it is completely legal.  As always, be careful if you want to try this, make sure you have a buddy (sitter) to watch over you on those high-dose experiences.  HAPPY TRIPPING! ;]</bodytext></report>