<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>11614</idnum><title>Newyear's Candyflip</title><author>Dextrose</author><substance>tryptophan</substance><substance>lsd</substance><substance>5meo_dipt</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><substance>mdma</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


[21:00]
/n
Ingests 2 pills Vitamin-C (500 mg. in each, selfdosing over 12 hours), 2 pills Vitamin-B6 (30 mg. in each) and 150 mg. 5-HTP.
/n
/n
[22:00]
/n
Arrives at some friends, starts drinking booze and beers (there were plenty of alcohol).
/n
/n
[~22:30]
/n
Starts eating of them pills. (3 Diamonds, an EZ-test first turned orange, then pitch black - definitly MDMA, and probably also amphetamine).
/n
/n
[~23:30]
/n
Party's on, everybody is totally drunk, loud and most of us are drugged too.
/n
/n
[somewhere between 2 and 4]
/n
We take off 8-10 persons to a new-years psytrance party.
/n
/n
[~45 mins. after]
/n
Arrives at the party, i don't remember details but it ruled, and i danced my ass off.
/n
/n
[~5:45]
/n
A girl gives me 2 blotters (Condoms, very good LSD!), after i give her 10 mg. foxy methoxy.
/n
/n
[~6:00]
/n
My friend doesn't hesitate to eat the one, i eat 3/4 of my blotter, and give the last quarter to a friend. (I had eaten the 3 pills at that time).
/n
/n
[~6:45]
/n
We can't feel if the acid has kicked in, because we are pretty MDMA-fucked, so we each eat a capsule of 10 mg. foxy methoxy (5-MeO-DiPT) to kick in the acid... It was about that time i ate another 150 mg. 5-HTP.
/n
/n
[~7:00]
/n
I go to take a piss, and notice some minor visual distortions, 30 seconds after while i'm pissing, the visuals are accelerating, and from that point i have the most beautifull visuals i've ever had, definitly from the acid, but with a little of the foxy-visuals mixed in.
/n
/n
[~7:45]
/n
I take off from the party with a couple of friends.
/n
/n
[~8:30-9:30]
/n
We arrive 3 persons at my place, my MDMA-buzz is still present, but now clearly much more dominated by the hallucinogens.
/n
I eat another 150 mg.'s of 5-HTP.
/n
/n
...we trip, talk, listens to music, and enjoys each others great friendly company.
/n
/n
We order some food at about 8 pm., i go online to post something on a webboard, IRC's a little, logs off, and watches a movie with my friends.
/n
/n
Sleeps at about 11 pm.
/n
/n
Absolutely the best new years eve i had, a clear +++!
/n
Great music, good friends, nice set &amp; setting, good drugs...
/n
/n
I've been told that the blotters (Condoms) are 185 mic. each, wich i believe is true. [Erowid note: Nobody really knows]
/n
/n
MDMA &amp; LSD is wonderfull together, and the little fox on top of it, is a great combination - absolutely recommendable!
/n
/n
/Dex</bodytext></report>