<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>11976</idnum><title>Mild and Promising</title><author>Bricoleur</author><substance>4_acetoxy_det</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>



SET: I am coming into he last 2 months of my audio engineering course. As a result I am required to shift more stress and anxiety; other than this I am in good running order. 
/n
/n
SETTING: Early evening at my flat. Last food approximately 4.5 hours prior (fruit salad). Last drug  cannabis previous evening. Other than this nothing inside of a week. 
/n
/n
10mg of 4-AcO-DET freebase was loaded into a glass DMT pipe. Freebase was a dark grey powder. 
/n
/n
+:00 I take 5 large lung-fulls of before I am satisfied that no chemical remains. Smoke is actually easy to smoke and not harsh on throat or lungs (I am surprised).
/n
/n
After the 3rd toke the first effects are felt. Very similar to the first .5 seconds of 5-MeO-DMT. 
/n
/n
Sweaty hands
/n
/n
Colours are more vibrant. 
/n
/n
+:10  No mental gymnastics at this point but I can see the veins through my hands. Body is feeling fine  no complaints. Lungs feel expanded. 
/n
/n
+:15  No progression of visual or mental effects. Upon standing I have a sense of feeling taller.
/n
/n
I do not feel restless.
/n
/n
OEVs are expanded, no morphing or dripping. Colours are vibrant.
/n
/n
CEVs are no more lucid or intricate than when I am sober. 
/n
/n
+:30  Notice clenched jaw + tightness in stomach.
/n
Still no mental gymnastics, although I am starting to peak. 
/n
/n
+:45  Increase in sexual awareness  I now know what Ill be doing next time with this chemical. 
/n
/n
+1:00  Definitely passed my peak. Decide to go for a walk. Phone rings, talking no problem. 
/n
/n
+1:10  Go for a walk. 
/n
/n
+1:25  Back from the walk. Too cold and navigating London traffic (even as a pedestrian) is too scary.
/n
Effects have diminished considerably. 
/n
/n
+1:45  Just got off the phone talking to a mate about the trip. Post trip synopsis  nearly baseline now. 
/n
/n
REFLECTION:
/n
This is a strange experience. I was expecting an increase in associations, to generate new perspectives. I think this is a dosage reliant effect.
/n
/n
Visuals were not the typical bending/morphing variety. No form constants like lattice, filigree, tunnel, spiral, etc.
/n
/n
My visual field seemed expanded or as if I were viewing the world through a fish eye lens. This is a commonly noted effect of 4-AcO-DET.</bodytext></report>