<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>12003</idnum><title>Blissful</title><author>octo</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>hbw</substance><substance>tobacco</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


Dose: 5 cleaned seeds boiled
/n
/n
This was my first experience with this substance. This log was written during the trip. 
/n
/n
I prepared a tea with the seeds.  First scraping the casings until they were a brighter/more alive color than the brown fuzz, softening them in boiling water, then took them out and sliced them each into 4 divisions with scissors, boiled again for 10-15 minutes.  Water was greenish, which was a little surprising.
/n
/n
4:45pm 
/n
Drank it.  It's not nearly as nasty-tasting as some say.  No chaser required.  Perhaps this indicates I should have ground them up more?
/n
/n
Will smoke some mj in a half hour for stomache-ease. In the future I will try to grind them up more and add some nice tea to the drink.
/n
/n
5:03pm
/n
Already I feel something.  Movement is noticably different.
/n
/n
5:35pm
/n
I'm sort of 'tripping' I would say now.  Smoked a small loosely packed bowl of some new weed.  Am high.  But also 'other'.  Played guitar for a bit.  Am pleasantly tripping.  
/n
/n
5:45pm
/n
I'm not sure if this feeling is actually familiar or if it just seems like it is.  But I feel like saying 'I remember what this is like.'  but I'm not sure if this is accurate.
/n
/n
[I'd done LSD many years in the past, and I think that's where this feeling was coming from.]
/n
/n
5:55pm
/n
Whoa.
/n
/n
6:25pm
/n
Still getting stronger.
/n
/n
6:29pm
/n
Movement is strange.  Not unpleasant.  All physical sensation is slightly more pleasant, warmer, more tactile, richer.  Balance is not exactly correct, but it may be because I'm distracted by every sensation involved in walking.  
/n
/n
[much like when rolling on e, I was rubbing my arms and sides and legs with my hands a lot.  Very very easily distracted by any physical sensation.]
/n
/n
6:50pm
/n
This ffx puzzle is too difficult / boring.  I don't know which.
/n
/n
7:05pm
/n
Feels like a lot of time has passed [since I wrote anything in the log] but it hasn't.  Bleh.
/n
/n
Tripping.  Agh!  
/n
/n
[I was beginning to lose direct control over my actions/thoughts at this point.  I was sort of being tugged around.  I can barely recall the sensation now, and wish I expanded on it at the time.]
/n
/n
7:08pm
/n
I have no sense of rythm.  Or I don't care to adhere to.  Not sure which.  S.e.r.p.e.n.t.I.n.e.  [I couldn't stop moving like a snake.]
/n
/n
Dancing with/to myself.  It is w o n d e r f u l.  Bliss.
/n
/n
Considering going to mcdonalds or some other fast-food.
/n
/n
7:12pm
/n
If this is the peak, then this drug is a wonderful, mellow, pleasant, lovely alternative to LSD.  Much more forgiving, much more agreeable, much easier to work with.  Same place, same feel, similar head-trip, less sterile, less forceful, less aggressive.  Very positive.  I am a giant fan.  
/n
/n
[I would further say that the period of time between 1.5 hours before and after the peak (for 3 hours total) is probably a nice analog to tasty e.]
/n
/n
7:20pm
/n
Yes.  I want to go to a club.  Dance dance dance.  This is a fantastic drug.  I feel like being very social right now, but at the same time, and a little frightened by the prospect of talking to people.  Slight paranoia.
/n
/n
Amanita muscaria smells great.  Another trip, another day.
/n
/n
I want to get out of the house, but, am unsure.  I wish someone was here.  Maybe I'll just wander around the city.
/n
/n
7:25pm
/n
Solvent is w on der f ul.  Still climbing.
/n
/n
7:35pm
/n
Really enjoying this.
/n
/n
[I was sitting in my bed, playing guitar/singing along to the vaselines.  I was in a good place.]
/n
/n
7:45pm
/n
I've decided to have a cigarette.
/n
/n
[I quit a couple months ago, but really really wanted one.  Went to 7-11 and bought cigs with little trouble.  Slight paranoia.  Really enjoyed walking around in the fresh air.  But quickly realized I needed to get back to my apartment.  It wasn't panic-driven, but just an understood fact: I must return home.]
/n
/n
8:55pm
/n
Still tripping.  Coming down?
/n
/n
Sleepy.
/n
/n
9:17pm
/n
Coming down nice and smoothly.
/n
/n
6:00am the next morning.
/n
At around 9:30pm last night I trailed into sleep and needed to puke but didn't.  Mild need to puke.  I sort of 'willed' the feeling away.  Mild panic began when my roomate came home which further justified sleeping.
/n
/n
Woke up around 10:30 and dressed for sleep, still tripping.  Went back to sleep with some very vivid dreams.  Woke just now.  The dreams ended only now upon waking.
/n
/n
Oddly enough, the last dream ended like the end of an e experience at a club.  The lights were coming on in the club, but I wasn't ready to stop.  Everyone was very very tired and sad that the night was over.  It was as if I was being told, 'ok, the drug is done, the trip is over.'
/n
/n
Overall impression: _powerful_ fun, pleasant.  No visual/aural hallucinations, but highly physical, not entirely dissimilar to e.  Less head-trippy than LSD, but now that I've experienced this, I don't think I'll ever do LSD again.  A larger dose might be desirable, since I feel like I missed out with visuals/aurals.  But those nightmare stories are good warning against it.  We'll see.  I've got plenty.
/n
/n
6:30am
/n
Can't go back to sleep.
/n
/n
10:30am
/n
Whoa, went back to sleep and had some extremely vivid dreams.
/n
/n
-octo</bodytext></report>