<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>1348</idnum><title>Homesweet Home, But Not Yet</title><author>White Rabbit</author><substance>toads</substance><substance>bufotenin</substance><bodytext>



I'm gonna tell the whole story leading up to this point. It started out a day before when I got offered to smoke some pure bufotinin, tried 8 mg and got shot into a very interesting world full of colour, very tryptamine like, entities interacting and checkin me out in various ways. what a trip. 
/n
/n
The next night I asked to try more, but this time i'll try 10 mg, smoked till my lungs held no more, flew down fractal tunnels, the more I thought about it the the more I realized I controlled the speed and direction of my travel so I ventured onward fast as I could then as it all got brighter and brighter, a bufo conglomorant fractaling tenticle mass stopped me in my tracks, leting me know, 'no offence, but no passin this point' all in tones and vibrations of course. I then concentrated and started to create a horison type tunnel right in the center of this entity and surpassed its hold and flew on further, only slow and struggling this time, bufo blob once again stopped me, and flung me upside down and into other tunnels and corridors all twisting into chaos until all was lost in fractal seas, melting slowly into reality. I came out of this one kind of preturbed, wondering why these entities keep on stopping me in my tracks, and why me. 
/n
/n
As I stood up and told this to my friend, he smiled and asked if I knew of smoking toad venom, and if I would like the experience. This all fits together perfectly with the last two trips. I accepted, he filled my lungs with smoke to mass capacity, I let out the toke lay down closed my eyes, light tingling buz, then without warning I had totaly misplaced my body and physical reality, and had accepted my death as nothing but wholeness and oneness with all, bliss, flowing like water calmly all melting, and whisping together complete feeling of home and very fimillar, I had always been and alway will, never thinking once that I would return to the physical. then voices and tones came from dark drippy caved feelings of sacrifice, dark and serious beings of ancients and their dark serious knowledge of sacrifice, want a metephore, you like it here, ya know how to make it happen boy, they handed me the knife and made me watch myself do it sound pictoral feeling and all, this all scarred the living shit out of me so much it shocked me back into my body to leave trembling for another half hour pondering this emense metaphore which had been pounded into me. They let me know all may dissapear if you are not there to witness it happening, all pain happiness feelings people babylon all of it gone with you.
/n
/n
And so what to think of this? I was on the road searching for answers and when the bufotenin didnt take me quite there these entities of death worlds pushed to make sure I got there and understood what I had asked, offered me the venom the knowledge of the toad, I soon afterward took a trip to the desert to take peyote to make sure the energy rose to the sun and the knowledge became enlightened instead of dark and wondereing, I have been reborn from this experience and thank the toad for my allowance into the closest realms of death I have ever experienced, they all lead to the same place, tryptamines that is, some are just more direct, each with different teachers of the underworld, all with separate signatures and metaphores of this world. and yet within that trip I got a message, jerry, and terrence wish us luck warmth and happiness, the journey never ends, and all will fade into light once our fear of darkness is totally wased away, see you on the other side.
/n
/n
peace and love the white rabbit.</bodytext></report>