<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>14642</idnum><title>My Great Trip</title><author>Experienced_Tripper</author><substance>morning_glory</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>General</tag><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



The reason I am writing this is because back in Febuary 2002 I
/n
decided to experiement with Morning Glory seeds. I accidentally
/n
came upon this website and actually researched the seeds before
/n
trying them. You guys gave me so much good information that I
/n
decided I should give back.
/n
/n
Here's how it all happened for me. On 1 afternoon I went up to
/n
the local K-Mart to look for MG:HB seeds. While in there I found
/n
Martha Stewart brand MG:HB seeds. I proceeded to buy 4 packs
/n
(6grams, roughly 240 seeds). Then I came home and prepared the
/n
seeds. I washed them with dish washer soap, then dryed them on a
/n
paper towel, then ground them up in a coffee grinder.
/n
/n
At 9pm I poured the seeds into a cup of water. Then drank the
/n
potion and ate the remaining chunks of seeds. It was pretty
/n
nasty but definetly wasn't that bad. At about 20 minutes the
/n
effects started to kick in. But these were mild effects. Also
/n
though, my stomach started to hurt and my limbs became very
/n
heavy. So i drank some pepto to help my stomach. At about 1 hour
/n
the effects really started to kick. And once the trip began to
/n
take over all stomach pain just left. At 1st I began to think of
/n
it as just a mild acid trip, which I was happy with. It wasn't
/n
untill about 2 or 3 hours into it that the MG trip REALLY began
/n
to kick hard. Then it felt exactly like an acid trip. Walls were
/n
rolling and breathing. When i walked around the house the floor
/n
began to slant. It felt like the world was tilted. Once I turned
/n
the kitchen light on I was very light senstive. It felt as if
/n
everything was glowing around me. Best way to describe it is,
/n
imagine walking out into the street in the middle of the night,
/n
standing directly under a street light, you can feel the light 
/n
beaming down on you. Honestly, the peak lasted from about 11pm
/n
to 5am. It was very intense and lasted for a very long time. and
/n
i mean peaking, I'm not counting the 'afterglow', which as
/n
everyone knows goes on for many hours after the peak is gone.
/n
/n
In conclusion, I highly recommend it, it was fantastic. I've
/n
read many negative reports on here, and I've come to many
/n
conclusions. Maybe they had to low a dosage, got bad seeds, or
/n
weakened the seeds during the extraction process. My advice,
/n
get at least 6grams, clean them, dry them, grind them, drink
/n
them. And don't forget the pepto.</bodytext></report>