<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>14761</idnum><title>Addiction (Second Dose)</title><author>DrozzWilliams</author><substance>opium</substance><bodytext>


Anyways, this story I am about to tell you is of my first time using opium the magical nectar of life.  Since the beginning of time -- that is to say of when I have started abusing substances, I have always been curious about opium from what I have read about it.  So, a couple of weeks ago I decided to buy an amount of poppy heads and grind them up and soak them in water.  Now this is what I understand is the technique used to make opium tea.  
/n
/n
So I looked around for poppies for a while but I only found the wrong ones.  Now an easy way to tell if you have the real poppy is for one thing, their foliage that grows at the base resembles more of lettuce looking than the other poppies.  Second, the pods are usually much larger than the others, although some of the other kinds may have larger pods, but rarely.  Third, the somniferum stems grow much more taller than others.  It takes some time to really know how to differentiate between them but practice looking as much as you can for them.  I just found i was tired of looking, at searched online for a supplier of dried pods.  Success!  I have and did find a source that was reliable.  
/n
/n
So basically when they arrived since i knew that opium could still be extracted from dried pods, i ground the pods up into small as I could.  I then stirred them into water in a pan, and heat it up.  But warning, you should not heat it too hot.  To be honest, i kept the heat at a low setting most of the time.  I kept a very very close eye on a thermometer that i stuck in the pot too.  The ones for cooking.   I made sure that at all time i kept the temperature lower than 150 F otherwise I knew that going higher could possible destroy the chemical structure of codeine and morphine -- the two chemicals in opium that I want most of all.  Anways, I would just like to say that i boiled off the water and was left with gooey opium.  I have taken it three times orally and have smoked it a couple of times. I noticed, if I smoke it properly, then I will feel good, but just not as intense as eating it.  All in all, the time consumtion was worth this delicious treat.   And, by the way, I am writing this pretty fucked up on the extract right now.  So if my spellings off, forgive me.</bodytext></report>