<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>1545</idnum><title>Showing Me My Place in the Universe</title><author>Triode</author><substance>dob</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



Two good friends and I decided to take a weekend and trip on DOB.  My
/n
initial expectations were of a trip very much like 2C-B, but spanning
/n
sixteen to twenty hours and fueled by the presence of amphetamine.
/n
What occurred was something not entirely different, but not something
/n
I'd been anticipating.
/n
/n
[T+0h] Saturday noon.  After I munched on a breafast of bacon and eggs, 
/n
we three wanderers each ingest 2.5mg DOB dissolved in distilled water.
/n
Mixed with orange juice; taste imperceptible.  Here goes.
/n
/n
[T+0:30] First twinges of a psychedelic drug in my system.
/n
/n
[T+0:45] The psychedelic is clearly taking over my brain.  Interacting
/n
with the world around me is difficult.  If I know nothing else, it's
/n
that I'd better get the hell outta public view.
/n
/n
[T+1h] Two of the three of us arrive at a Safe location.  We have a
/n
friend who'd volunteered to drive us around that weekend, and so we
/n
wait for him to get ready to take us home.  We step inside (out of the
/n
sunlight) and immediately my field of vision explodes into
/n
characteristically 2C-B visuals.  I notice as well a wave of
/n
amphetamine crash over my body, and I am soon feeling like the
/n
strongest man alive.  I help my chauffeur lug some very heavy cargo to
/n
the van -- effortless.  This shit is SPEEDY.  I am smoking pot because
/n
I am compulsed towards it; it seems like a good idea to head off any
/n
GI discomfort at the pass.
/n
/n
[T+1:30] We two arrive at home and meet the third, who's been coming
/n
up on the same schedule.  At this point, when I am in a darkened area,
/n
I am completely unable to distinguish visual effects from real
/n
objects.  Amphetamine high is still CRUISING.  
/n
/n
[T+2h] I am so amped, I could gnaw the head off a puppy.  Fortunately,
/n
the fact that my entire perspective is moving, breathing, pulsating,
/n
billowing, and crawling keeps me from doing anything useful.  More
/n
smoking, and it is noticeably hard to keep it together long enough to
/n
pack a bowl.  I am floored.
/n
/n
[T+2:30] I am thanking my lucky stars that I am going to have to
/n
interact only with people I know very well for the next 20 hours.  I
/n
am quite sure that I am having a good time, though -- still feels like
/n
2C-B, but HARDER.
/n
/n
[T+3h] I would trade a kidney for a pack of Bazooka gum.  I have been
/n
becoming more and more disoriented with my surroundings throughout the
/n
whole three hours, and it is here that I would call myself 'lost' in
/n
my own house.
/n
/n
[T+4h] A delightful, non-tripping-his-eyeballs-out friend shows up,
/n
and we three enjoy talking to him.  I think it is at this point that
/n
the trip begins its second leg; the 2C-B visuals start to fade (very
/n
slightly, at this point) and get the hell out of the way, and a very
/n
profound, intellectual DOB experience begins.
/n
/n
[T+4:20] I pack a bowl.  'See you in 12 hours, guys.'  *rrrrrrrip*
/n
/n
[T+5h] I can feel a slight tension lifted from my body as I
/n
simultaneously feel my brain kick into high gear.  I eat something
/n
because I can somehow tell I need to.  
/n
/n
[T+6h] Over T+5-6h, I am able to clear the visuals out of the way
/n
(although they're still _very_ strong) and think, think, think.  I
/n
suddenly questioned every fact about reality I'd taken for granted.  
/n
/n
[T+7h] The amphetamine din has settled into a dull roar, and I am
/n
leading my appreciative brain through an odyssey of metaphysically-
/n
deep insights into the real and perceived worldview I call 'Reality',
/n
leaving open at every corner the chance for anything to be possible.
/n
The three of us are happily and hungrily announcing and discussing our
/n
current thoughts.  We are settling down into a dark room in the middle
/n
of our house, almost like a cocoon, each person in turn putting on the
/n
music he believed to be perfect for the situation.
/n
/n
[T+9h] We are devouring any knowledge we can, eager to share our
/n
amazing experiences and contemplations.  We eat when we need food,
/n
drink when we need water, smoke when it feels right.  I feel as though
/n
I'm overseeing my body at a higher level than I ever have; I have a
/n
good and innate sense of how to take care of myself (food, water, 
/n
pot, music) without dwelling on the individual feelings and pains in
/n
my body.  It is apparent that the 'peak' (T+1-8h) has passed and the
/n
effects are beginning a very slow, gradual taper.  Three non-tripping
/n
friends appear, and it is very comforting to see faces from the
/n
outside world.  We talk and enjoy each other.
/n
/n
[T+12h] Less visual, more brainy!  DOB thoughts are leaving me
/n
dumbfounded.  I am anxious to wrap my brain around any scenario I can
/n
conceive.  I have a correct and instinctual understanding of
/n
electricity and magnetism, quantum mechanics, thermodynamics, organic
/n
chemistry, algorithmic mathematics in such a way that I can simply
/n
'feel' in what trend a particular system will act.  By possessing this
/n
deep understanding of physics and mathematics, the rules of my
/n
universe, I can detect patterns shared among wildly different systems
/n
(the ties that bind between social, chemical, and physical
/n
interactions).  I cook pasta for the six of us, and as it is
/n
well-received I ponder the satisfaction of crafting something for my
/n
friends and having it appreciated.  
/n
/n
It's interesting to note that this experience was more what I would
/n
call 'Ecstasy' than MDMA is.  My past drug experiences were
/n
embarrassed and belittled by the DOB's gravity, its unique
/n
characteristic of allowing me to invent a constant stream of Heavy
/n
Shit for my mind to happily plow through.  I felt like I'd never
/n
thought about anything so important; my most fundamental concepts of
/n
reality were shaken to the core for the first time, and in comparison
/n
it makes the visceral high of a 'quality' MDMA or mushroom trip seem
/n
positively rude.  Whereas MDMA might allow me to reach a comfortable
/n
synergy with the people around me, DOB provided a glimpse of what it
/n
might be like to achieve Nirvana, to exist as pure thought.  When it
/n
comes right down to it, this is why I ingest psychedelics.  This is
/n
what it's all about.
/n
/n
I had some very momentous insights into heritage and family ties, from
/n
my relationship with my dad to my kinship with the creatures from
/n
which I evolved.  I was given a chance to grasp the infinity of the
/n
universe; understanding its specifics was clearly out of reach, but I
/n
understood why it was acting how it was acting, on the whole.  DOB is
/n
completely orthogonal to the emotional realm; it does not alter my
/n
mood at all, and only allows me to enjoy it because I enjoy thinking.  
/n
/n
[T+14h] 2am Sunday, and it is here that things really begin to screech
/n
to a halt.  Our conversation becomes less frequent, and I become more
/n
introspective.  It's time to let the music take over.
/n
/n
[T+16:20] 4:20am and I'm keeping true to the previous afternoon's
/n
promise.  We are content to keep ourselves warm, hydrated and fed, and
/n
bathed in music.  Very faint visuals.  Coming down, no question about it.
/n
/n
[T+20h] It is around this point in time when each of us three dozes
/n
off in turn; we're right on the tail end of the DOB's effects.
/n
/n
[T+22h] At 10am Sunday, I declared the DOB's mental effects 'over'.
/n
/n
[T+33h] After a full day of doing stuff and feeling generally ok, it's
/n
sleepytime. :)
/n
/n
DOB tore me a new asshole.  I cannot describe it without its power
/n
making itself apparent in my speech; DOB will forever hold a special
/n
place in my heart, a place earned as a Truly Psychedelic Drug.  If
/n
treated with respect, I believe DOB can show us how awesome the
/n
human condition can be.</bodytext></report>