<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>15463</idnum><title>Werid Cactus Mix</title><author>Urbanhog</author><substance>peyote</substance><substance>cacti</substance><bodytext>



Earlier this year, I had the most weirdest, oddest, and the most profound experience, I have only tried Acid about 7 times, only taken shrooms once, smoked/eat pot about 3 times a month last 5 or so years. I have never tried other sorts of drugs, I'm not really a 'drug user', I'm more of wine/beer drinker. But I'm a cactus grower, been growing cactus as hobby.
/n
/n
I fasted for 18 hours, didn't eat anything, just plenty of water and apple juice.
/n
/n
I had some peyotes, San Pedro, and Peruvians cactus, I used 6x 2.5cm wide peyote buttons, about a foot of San Pedro and half a foot of Peruvian, I peeled, took the core out, boiled with water for approx 4 hours, then blended,drained thru fine cloth, etc the lot, and I added some Apple juice and heaps of Lime juice.
/n
/n
I managed to drink 4 cups of the most awful crap that I have ever tasted, it was the hardest thing I have ever done, about hour later I felt really really sick, I thought I was actually being poisoned and was dying, I was in mild panic state, but my girlfriend calmed me down, repeatly telling me thats its all OK, etc...and I threw up very voliently, and after approx 15 mins of throwing up, I felt way better, and the visual effect suddenly came up into my visions slowly getting stronger and stronger, it was unexplainable, it was very odd, had a lot of 'mental chat' with some sort of god, and that 'spirit' I was talking to was 'guiding' giving me insights into my life, and I was sort of in dream state, but with my eyes open...very strange but interesting experience.
/n
/n
It was kind of personal, the 'trip' gave me a different outlook towards the everchanging world...I really can't explain in words, it was very profound and very highly personal. I would recommended anyone to try this, as long they respect these visionary cactus, I'm starting to understand why it's very important to the American Indian's culture.
/n
/n
The strong visuals last about nearly 8 or 9 hours, it was very powerful, very realistic, it was visuals from the spirits, somewhat emotional. I think this cactus isn't suitable for anyone who has a lot of mental or emotional problems, you have to be strong minded to consume this special cactus. This is not a PARTY drug, it's a personal drug you take in quiet and comfortable surroundings.</bodytext></report>