<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>1548</idnum><title>I Thought It Was E...</title><author>Brian</author><substance>mdma</substance><bodytext>



I had purchased 4 pills of what I thought to have been e, from 2 different dealers that day. I had taken e many times in the past, so I know what to expect.
/n
/n
Me &amp; a friend went to a rave that night, sober, and came back home to ingest our drugs at around 3:30 am that morning,  much later than usual.  (we were already tired from dancing, and hungry, as we hadn't eaten since breakfast).
/n
/n
I had tested both types of pills using a reagent.  The first pill tested normally (quickly turned dark black/purple), but the second was weird... it turned dark organge, and then slowly turned brown, then purple/black.
/n
Orange would normally indicate the presence of speed, but I assure you that wasn't the case.
/n
/n
We both took one of the same types of pills, and started coming on within about a half hour, at which time we took the other 2 pills.
/n
/n
After about an hour into the roll, the other pill started to take effect.  Tactile pleasure was still there, but it seemed different than the usual 'roll'...  Within an hour my friend had to leave to vomit in the bathroom. Soon, we started to hallucinate.  I felt like I was still at the party, yet still at home.  I would have a conversation with someone (or think i did) and the next minute I would be back in my room still talking and just realizing there was no one there.  Sometimes when I looked at the walls in my room, they looked like a wall of smoke, and then it would disappear.  At one point, we both swore we saw something resembling christmas lights (but red and green only) strung around the door frame.  (We both saw the exact same thing, after the experience we were both remembering the same minute details of how it looked -- has anyone else experienced something similar?)  Also saw cops in my bedroom, a pirate...  These effects lasted late into the morning.
/n
/n
The following night, it was extremely difficult to sleep.  My mind was filled with negative, almost evil thoughts.
/n
/n
It has taken about 3 days to completley recover from this substance.  I probably won't do this again, as I now know that it is much more dangerous than mdma.  The mda also seemed to end my roll. 
/n
/n
[erowid note: MDA does not turn orange with the marquis reaction and it seems unlikely that this was MDA alone, if the pill contained MDA at all.]</bodytext></report>