<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>15550</idnum><title>Cactus Practice</title><author>Rock Star</author><substance>cacti</substance><bodytext>



	Hey kids what's up?  I've found this page to be an excellent resource so I decided to add a San Pedro Cactus experience.  I ordered the cactus from a online mail order company. I received three 12 inch long and about 4 inch wide cuttings of  Trichocerus pachanoi amazingly, 4 days after I placed in the order.  I spent a significant amount of time researching different methods of preparing the cactus for ingestion and decided on making juice with the blender.
/n
/n
First, I notched out all the short spines with a knife which was easier than I had expected.  Next, I began the task of removing the plastic like skin.  In all the reports I've read folks talk about the ease of peeling san Pedro's, for some reason I found it to be extremely difficult.  I couldn't seem to get the skin to peel in large pieces like so many people write about.
/n
/n
After about 2 hours and a huge mess later I was able to cut it into strips and remove the core.  I stuck the whole thing in the freezer for about 1.5 hours.  I then began dropping the frozen pieces into the blender on slow setting.  The blending caused the juice to foam up so I put in on the stove  on low heat to make the bubbles dissipate. I then strained the juice through an old sweater and blended the remaining pulp again with a little water and strained again.  There was only about 1 cup of pulp left after all the straining so I just tossed it.  
/n
/n
	I have to tell you I have a lot of experience with psycadelic drugs and I have a pretty high tolerance to most of them.  I couldn't have picked a better setting for my first san Pedro experience.  I was seeing Yonder Mountain String Band at a beautiful venue called Mishawaka.  Its located next to a river in the beautiful poudre canyon.  The vibe was very happy to say the least.  Many of the folks in attendance had eaten their psycadelic wheaties as well.  I started by taking a little pepto to avoid nausea.  I then slammed 2x 16 or 18 ounce cups of the tasty brew.
/n
/n
Everybody says it tastes so bad but I found it to taste quite well kinda resembling tea.  Just joking this shit tastes bad, imagine drinking an entire bottle of liquid dish soap with snot in it, mmm.  I then chased the poison with a cold delicious beer which has never tasted better let me tell ya.  After about 15 minutes I could already feel the nausea coming on.  for about 1.5 hours I didn't much feel like doing anything but sit next to the river.  It took a full 2 hours for the mescaline to take effect.  the effects weren't very strong but they were very enjoyable.  Colors were very vibrant, the lights and smoke on the stage were very entertaining and the music sounded great.  I remember feeling perfectly at peace and having a thought that everything was right.
/n
/n
After I came down I couldn't remember what it was I was thinking, it was really weird.  After the show I decided I wanted to be a little higher so I munched some mushrooms and tripped and drank beer all night.  This about the time everything went nut-balls, usually a direct effect of psilocybin mushrooms.  But this report is about san perdo so we'll stop there.
/n
/n
	My next run in with the gag juice was only a couple days later.  My girlfriend really wanted to try it so we split what was left (probably about 28 inches).  We decided to stay home because it was already 11:00.  The nausea wasn't as bad this time for me but it seemed to effect her pretty strongly (she has a weak stomach).  She threw up about 1.5 hours after ingestion.  This trip was stronger than the first but I think it would have been stronger if I had waited a few more days so my tolerance could have gone down a bit.  She said she was tripping pretty hard and her pupils were huge.  I would compare both trips with eating about 1.5 hits of blotter acid.  I didn't have any strong visuals but colors were VERY intense and fun to look at.  Also, a friend brought over a huge digital projector and we played x-box all night on the wall (a very entertaining trip toy).
/n
/n
Well, it wasn't as strong as I had hoped but it was still awesome.  I will definitely try it again but next time I will probably try to eat as much as possible (18inches+) to see what San Pedro really has to offer.  I think a Juicer would be ideal for making the slime, it might not make it so foamy.  It was a lot of work, but I was drinking beer and rocking out to music while I was concocting the funk that is cactus juice.  The nausea was more like motion sickness so I don't believe the pepto really helped much.  
/n
/n
I enjoyed the trip better than LSD or psilocybin.  It seemed more mellow comparable to very low does of MDMA in combination with acid or mushrooms.  Another thing I would suggest is to eat the potion at home and let the nausea take its toll before leaving the house because you'll probably want to lay down.  I tried to add the answers to all the questions that I still had after doing research, I hope this is useful to someone.  Have fun and stay safe y'all.</bodytext></report>