<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>15594</idnum><title>Whoops, There Goes Reality</title><author>Moniax</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>dxm</substance><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
Okay, this little adventure started out by me making a trip to my local Shopko and getting a 5-fingered discount on a couple boxes of Coricidin.  I've done quite a bit of research on DXM and wanted to see if I could reach the ever-elusive Sigma plateau that us roboheads dream about.  So I dosed 16 pills at 9:00pm on Sunday, thinking that it wouldn't fully metabolize for another day or so.
/n
/n
So I woke up Monday morning and shipped off to school.  I waited until about 10:30am to take the remaining 16 pills, figuring that the trip would kick in just as I was out for lunch.  Well, me and 3 friends went out at lunch and my friend treated us to 3 bowls of some of the best bud I've ever smoked, he said it was called 'Train Wreck', apparently some hybrid that his friend grows.
/n
/n
We were driving around during lunch when all of a sudden I had an urge to puke, so I told my friend to pull the car over and let me out.  I didn't really puke, I just kind of coughed for awhile and spit up.
/n
/n
By now the familiar feeling of the DXM's initial peak was hitting me.  DXM always (for me anyway) works the same way acid does, peaks hard for quite awhile, drops me back into reality for a couple minutes, peaks hard again, and so on and so on.  This time it was a lot more intense than it usually is however, my eyes went into 'huge-fucking-glass-orbs' mode and all of a sudden I couldn't control any of the muscles in my body, my neck went completely limp, leaving me staring contently at the roof of the car.
/n
/n
Then the open-eye visuals started.  I noticed a small orange spiral appear in my field of vision.  'Cool, tracers' I thought.  Well, then another spiral appeared... both of them spinning in sync together.  I closed my eyes for a couple of seconds, opened them back up and suddenly there was nothing left of my reality but 2 enormous spirals, whirling and twisting in front of my bewildered face.
/n
/n
My friends asked me if I was okay to go to class, and of course I said yes.  So, I went to my locker, trying to avoid people, (which is an extremely difficult task during lunch in a school where EVERYONE knows you) grabbed my binder and slowly robo-walked off to class.  Well, I didn't quite make it there.  I felt the drugs build up in my body, feeling like ice shooting up my veins followed by a feeling of complete and total euphoria.  My eyes rolled up into my head, ready to be launched into space.  Well, I got my wish.
/n
/n
My eyes rolled back into their normal position to see that EVERY locker down the hallway was open and swinging like fucking crazy.  Well, in my state, I thought this was actually happening, and for the first time in my long life of entheogen-taking I suddenly wondered if I could handle this.  Not only were the visual hallucinations some of the most extreme I've ever had, what was happening in my head was a completely new ballpark.  I felt the fabric of time rip apart, watched myself spiral into an oblivion while memories, thoughts, dreams, expectations, all flew past me and I felt totally connected with myself...like I had finally found that inner peace I had been questing for lately.
/n
/n
This was far from over.  I found myself laying in the hallway a couple minutes later, thinking how lucky I was nobody walked by to see me in my near-comatose, drooling state of mind.  Walking was out of the question, so I crawled my way into the boy's bathroom, and eventually into a stall where I sat...for an hour and a half.
/n
/n
There was the usual bathroom-wall scribblings, an occasional 'Fuck your mom' and 'Jeremy takes it up the butt'.  It's funny how much damage to my consensual reality one blink can do when I'm hallucinating.  As soon as my eyes reopened, the entire wall was covered with writing, over-lapping, humming with a 1000 different stories.  I felt connected again, like I was viewing the entire history of this stall and was somehow connected with everyone who had ever written something out of anger or defiance... suddenly understood it all.  Yeah, I know, it's a strange place to find inner peace, but I figured it was better then remaining in the halls to be discovered by the portfolio-toting nazis.
/n
/n
The colors were spectacular, and always present, even when the drug teased me with a temporary grasp on my sanity.  Everything was sharper and had a unique aura to it.  Looking at my own hands I was warped into a feeling of despair...my existence on this Earth has been anything but innocent according to what's supposed to be normal.  But I won't get into that little tirade of mine. For some reason my hands triggered a deep guilt, and stinging empathy for anyone I had ever wronged.  This feeling passed within minutes I'm sure (it felt like I was in this bathroom for about 3 days), and was replaced by another peak, coupled with euphoria.  None of my senses were working the way they usually do, auditory hallucinations that accompanied the visual ones made this new world of mine completely believable.
/n
/n
Every so often I would hear someone come into the bathroom as I sat in total silence...slowly peaked my head over the stall to see someone that I have never seen in my life.  Hallucinating again.  This happened 8 or 9 more times, confusing the hell out of my each time.
/n
/n
I remember laughing like an escaped mental hospital patient during certain parts of my trip that I don't really recall.
/n
/n
Well...that's about all the extreme happenings of the day.  I left the bathroom an hour and a half after I had entered it and walked off to my last class of the day.  We had a test and I kept hearing people whisper my name through the walls, and of course people could tell I was far past gone, so I was the main distraction for the other test-takers, whipping my head around to make sure there actually WASN'T somebody over my shoulder.</bodytext></report>