<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>1594</idnum><title>Burning Man Aliens</title><author>Anonymous</author><substance>ketamine</substance><substance>mdma</substance><substance>tma2</substance><substance>2cb</substance><bodytext>



I had been attending the Burning Man festival in the Black Rock Desert for over 14 days.  Burning Man is like another planet.  It is also the most comfortable place in the world to trip.  There are thousands of strangers everywhere, and they are all on an insane variety of drugs.  They expect you to be as well.
/n
/n
I had been using Ketamine nasally every couple hours for over three weeks, and I'd tripped on mushrooms, LSD, and GHB earlier that week.  I'd also been using benzodiazapines, barbituates and opiates often in the preceeding week. It had already been a helluva binge, and I felt that since it was the last night of the festival that i had better do something to top off the week.  At around 9pm I ingested 200mg MDMA HCl orally, 100mg Ketamine nasally and 75mgs of TMA-2 orally.  A half hour later, just as I was really coming on to the E and the TMA, I headed out to watch the Man burn.
/n
/n
It was spectacular, but not overwhelming.  The visuals were strong, but nothing I wasn't used to.  As the man fell I drank my dosage of liquid 2-CB.  After the Burn, I headed back towards a friend's camp.  When I arrived no one was present, but I took advantage of a mirror and razor they had laying around.  I snorted two more tenths of E and two more tenths of Ketamine.  As I walked back out onto the playa, the 2-CB, E and K all hit me at once.  Suddenly I noticed many spatial dimensions that I had never experienced before.  I decided to sit down, as I suddenly feared that I may walk off on some spatial tangent, and may not be able to return to the normal three dimensional world.
/n
/n
As I sat and hallucinated vividly, I lost all sense of what was 'actually' around me.  I soon became conscious that i was in a space inhabited by some sort of half-mineral, half-vegetable-type creatures that shared a bizarre collective consciousness.  They sort of resembled a large garden of sandstone carrots connected by jelly-like tentacles.
/n
/n
As soon as they recognized my presence they tried to communicate with me.  Their form of communication consisted of disjointed telepathic images and a strange method altering the color hues in the gaseous atmosphere that filled this bizarre space.  I translated their greeting as meaning something like, 'Ha, ha, ha - we don't see many of your kind here!'  They then went on to try to tell me many things that I absolutely could not conceive.  The only information that got through to me was that these entities had to somehow use deceased members of their collective to perpetuate their sleep cycle.  Without their dead, they could not sleep and would soon die.  At the time I translated this as 'We stuff our dead and use them as pillows.'  
/n
/n
Then, as soon as I had departed, I was sitting back on the playa.  I was still hallucinating intensely, but I could make out some semblence of reality around me.  I had no great insights or revelations during the experience, only a sense of having experienced something utterly and totally alien.  This combo made DMT look like baby asprin.  If you have a hard head for psychedelics and sometime find yourself camping out in the desert with 23,000 other drug-crazed freaks i definitly suggest this combo. 
/n
/n
Any other scenario would just not be bizarre enough to accomodate it.</bodytext></report>