<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>1599</idnum><title>Weed doesn't mix well with all drugs</title><author>Munky</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>methylphenidate</substance><bodytext>



I dropped by my friend's house yesterday. We were just sittin back, listening to music when we decided to go over this other guy's house. I was pretty tired and I've taken his Ritalin before when I was tired so I asked if I could get a few to take before work. He gave me 5 pills which I ground up and snorted. After that I went to work. Work was no big deal, I just talked and fidgeted a lot, but no one really noticed. Ritalin gives me a strong optimistic feeling, like I love everyone and everything will work out just as I want it. This is the exact opposite of my true philosophy on life, so I enjoy these periods of happiness. I've heard that you can get the same feelings from other drugs, but I haven't had the opportunity to test that. 
/n
/n
So after work I took a friend of mine home. We were almost to his house when I got a great idea. 'I wonder what it would be like to smoke-up when i'm flyin on ritalin?' So i voiced this question aloud and he said, we can find out if you want. So we went up to his apartment and rolled a blunt. It was only a nick but it was some pretty good stuff. When the high from the weed combined with the high from the ritalin it was the greatest feeling i have hever had. I had the energy, optimism, and focus from the ritalin and the soothing, sense enhancing qualities from the weed. It was the most incredible feeling i have ever had, and it didn't cost me a dime. I got in my car and drove to Fridays. 
/n
/n
My eyesight was completely shot. I was meeting some friends there and it took me a very long time to find them, in a small, open restaurant. I was starting to get hungry and the waitress was taking forever so I figured I should probably go home and eat all my food at home. I took the long way home because I was entralled by the wind, speed, and loud music i could feel like never before. It all went downhill from there. I started feeling a little nausious so I started for home. It got worse and worse the longer I was in the car, my chain smoking probably didn't help much, but i didn't think about that then.
/n
/n
As soon as i got out of my car i started dry heaving. I made it about half way to my house before i collapsed on all fours and puked over and over for about 10 minutes. I stumbled into the house and fell into my bed. All the ritalin i had recently put into my system prevented me from sleeping the entire night. I still feel like crap, and i can't risk eating for fear of vomiting again. The great feeling was definitely not worth it.</bodytext></report>