<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>16011</idnum><title>Worth Watching TV For</title><author>Echo</author><substance>mda</substance><bodytext>



In preparation for my second MDA experience I tried not to do any other drugs the preceding week.  Mostly this meant not using my prescription Xanax or Valium, as Benzodiazepines tend to decrease the intensity of hallucinogens.
/n
/n
My goal was to take the MDA with a friend who I am very comfortable with.  However, she was feeling anxious and having massive headaches that evening.  So she and I intended to have a fun time together while only I took the MDA.  I had received the MDA from a reliable source (as I had the last time) and took a dose of roughly 100mg.
/n
/n
There was an hour before I started to feel any of the effects.  But within 30 minutes of the first inklings, I was at the plateau where I remained for four or five hours.  That first 30 minutes I felt slightly nauseas, but I have been experiencing this more frequently lately and I can not be certain how severe the nausea would normally have been.
/n
/n
During the trip, we watched Hitchcock's film 'North by Northwest' for the first time.  During any standard trip I would not have been able to follow the plot.  However, due to Hitchcock's masterful use of suspense and the Amphetamines, I was glued to my seat in rapt attention for the whole two hours.  From evidence such as this, and my first trial with MDA, I feel MDA is a psychotropic but not a psychedelic.  However, I do know people who like it for its ability to greatly lengthen the empathenogenic effects of MDMA.
/n
/n
Over the five-hour peak I had some mild psychedelic effects, but nothing at all substantial either in thoughts or senses.  But for about ten hours after the initial effects began I felt a strong Amphetamine quality.  I have done a good range of Amphetamines, with no particular regularity, and this is my least favorite.  I had a psychedelic experience equivalent to half a standard dose of LSD and an anxiety response equivalent to about four doses of LSD.  I find this to be its major downfall, but if you like Ritalin or Methamphetamine (for fun not studying) you would probably love MDA.
/n
/n
The day after this experience I was nervous and had a lot of lower back pain form MDA-based muscle tension. I am a curious psychotropic explorer, but I will probably just give the rest of my MDA away.</bodytext></report>