<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>16602</idnum><title>AMT + Blood Sugar Disorders = BAD!</title><author>Camp8GeetarGuy</author><substance>amt</substance><bodytext>



this didn't happen to me, first off.  it happened to my buddy-chick.  we'll call her Frud.  we'll also call her hyperglycemic, since she is...  Frud doesn't do drugs often at all, in fact, she doesn' really like them, but she got curious...  we were all trippin on AMT, i, myself, at around 110mg.  my standard dose.  she took a single cap at 27 mg, and waited.  after roughly a half hour, the stomach weirdness kicked in, and that didn't seem strange to anyone else, considering we had no concept of time and that point.  we'd dosed about three hours prior.  in about another hour, she started getting visuals.  way too early, for us, anyway.  she started tripping hard as hell in about another 20 minutes.  also fast, if you're experienced.  now, as time went on, she continued her ascent into tripland.  it got harder than anyone else there, and she weighs no more than me, and i'd had three or four times her dose.  after roughly three hours, she got up and darted outside.  to my dismay, my peeking out the window after her revealed a vomiting Frud.  she walked back inside stating that she was trippin even harder, and sat down.  afterward, we all walked outside to stand in the rain and i noticed her sitting on the porch complaining about her stomach...  myself and my friend, Grocken, walked across the street to chill under the gazebo by the river.  a cop goes by and charlotte pauses her vomiting, then continues.  after the expulsion of said gastric acids discontinued, she walked inside to the bathroom to regain her former glory in the wacky world of puke.  i walk in twenty minutes later to find her lying on the floor, quivering and wheezing and vomiting.  she requested that cold water be poured over her head and face and back, and i found on examination that she was incredibly hot to the touch.  after about an hour of this, she crawled to the toilet to continue puking.  then, after another hour she migrated to the living room.  things began to return to normal then, though she complained of hearing a certain song for the next two days.  she also couldn't keep any food down (not even rice) for the next day or two.  it sucked.  don't take or allow anyone to take AMT if you or whoever has Hypo/Hyperglycemia or Diabetes.  It kicks the metabolism into hyperdrive and then after it sucks it all up, you fall.  hard...  it's not nice o have some one you care about fall apart like that while you're trippin ballz...</bodytext></report>