<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>17352</idnum><title>3 Tries</title><author>Aztec Cricket</author><substance>dipt</substance><tag>General</tag><tag>First Times</tag><tag>Difficult Experiences</tag><bodytext>



My friend and I both ingested 6mg DiPT orally with no effect.
/n
/n
A few weeks later 24mg DiPT was ingested orally, on an empty stomach, with minimal mental and auditory effects.  40 minutes after ingestion I became nauseous, the stomach tension would come and go every minute or so.  After an hour I tried to vomit but could only dry heave air.  The dry heaves seemed to be propelled by a powerful force.  The task of actually vomiting was simple as laying a napkin down on your plate, signaling the end of your meal.
/n
/n
There was somewhat of an increase in the ability to think in metaphors, but this could have just been placebo.  My voice and other voices sounded much deeper than normal; this was the only auditory effect noticeable.  There was no comedown.  The drug wore off quickly, within 4 hours.  The next morning I had an unusual time waking up.  At 9:48 I looked at my clock and thought I heard the radio on, but it was not.  Between waking up and falling asleep in bed I distinctly remember a few more times that morning I thought I heard the radio on.  Dreams seem unaffected.
/n
/n
The next day I ingested 22mg DiPT orally on a half-full stomach.  I spaced the dose out over an hour and this time the nausea was tolerable.  Aspects of familiar music sound more pronounced.  I should note Nils Frykdahls voice on the faun fables cd is very pronounced.  Usually I can hardly tell its there.  My moms voice sounds much deeper than it should too.  Mental effects seem very placebo like.  There was very little body effect.  5 hours after ingestion the DiPT had worn off.  I think I would have trouble taking a higher dose, as the nausea seemed pretty bad the first time.  Dosing at this level anymore would be pointless, but it was worth trying.</bodytext></report>