<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>17396</idnum><title>Hell Realms and Liberation</title><author>Fr Moonwatcher 343</author><substance>dpt</substance><tag>General</tag><tag>Difficult Experiences</tag><bodytext>



Late one night we decide to conduct an unplanned experiment.  Snorting 100 Mgs of DPT.  I had zero prep time beforehand.  20 minutes after dosage it kicked in hardcore and I started puking. Having no sense of what was happening I was puking into my hands, rubbing the vomit through my hair and beard.  I didn't know what it was, wasn't sure if it was vomit, mucus, or maybe blood from some animal we had killed.  I felt inclined to start talking in some non-language.  Deep and gutural, choppy yet melodic.  I came to the conclusion that I was absolutely insane.  I remember hoping that no one would come in for the duration as I lowered myself to the ground.
/n
/n
Once I got to the ground I curled up into a fetal ball.  I turned into the same slug creatured described in a previous experiement with DPT and Syrian Rue.  I was laying in the slime, surrounded by other creatures of the same form and ilk.  I remember all of us together becoming aware of the existance of God and the seperation of ourselves from God.  The feeling attached with this realization was horrible.  Every aspect of my being ached with this seperation.  All of us let out a heart wrenching wail in the language I experienced earlier.  I somehow became briefly aware of my physical body and remembered that I was in the midst of the experiment.  I took action by beginning to chant mantra and entering Generation stage.  When the yidam form was established the slugman world and all associated with it dissapeared.  I was in complete no-mind for duration of the experience....maybe 1.5 hours.  The only experience was that of pure light.  Beyond perfect ego-less state.  It can't be adequately explained, but it more then makes up for the pain of seperation from earlier.
/n
/n
During the comedown I became aware of self again.  There was a really pretty girl in the space with me.  Young, and a mixture of American Indian and Spanish descent.  She talked to me, giving me information on genetic breeding programs, similar to that of the Bene Geserit in Dune.  From there I returned back to a fairly normal state of conciousness in 5-10 minutes.
/n
/n
I was a bit out of it the next day, nothing sleep couldn't fix.  My sinuses however were torn up for about 4 days afterwards.
/n
I don't really recommend such an experiment to anybody without the experiences and skills to deal with these spaces.  I wouldn't suggest anyone without years of intense meditation practice even consider it.</bodytext></report>