<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>1741</idnum><title>Alternate Reality</title><author>6th Dimension</author><substance>dxm</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



It was around 10:30 on a Friday night and my friends got me to try DXM for my first time.  I wasn't too sure if I really wanted to do it after listening to their stories, but in spite of this, I took around 500 mg.  I started watching a movie after I took it and I didn't feel anything until the movie was ending.  It felt like my body was floating and everything I said was a thought.  It wasn't much different than a beer buzz.  At that point, I felt like it wasn't going to get much better so I laid down on the couch.  My friends put green lightbulbs in every socket because it was supposed to enhance the trip.
/n
/n
I waited forever, then finally it hit me all at once.  It was the most alien experience in my life.  Every movement I made gave me an incredible rush so I went outside and rolled in the grass.  After a couple minutes of that, I felt like I could no longer stand being on my feet so once again I retired to the couch.
/n
/n
When I got back, that's when I realized that time was going by slower than usual. I had only been outside for three minutes but it felt like a good half hour. Everyone else was sleeping so I stayed up with the green lights.  I had the feeling like I wasn't awake but I could see everything around me.  I stood up to get a watch to see what time it was but only minutes had passed since the last time I checked.  When I walked, my body didn't move like I wanted it to.  I fell a couple times face first into the floor but didn't feel it.  I went to the couch my friend was on and tried to wake him up because I thought I was going crazy and I needed someone to talk to.  He looked really strange and he had a third eye between his eyebrows.  It scared the shit out of me so I woke him up, but the eye didn't go away.  It would blink and look around just like his real eyes.  I talked to him and preached about things I never knew existed until that night.  He fell asleep during this and I paced back and forth through the room for hours on end, looking at the room I knew so well, but still it seemed like it was in an alternate dimension.  I did this until I feel asleep.</bodytext></report>