<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>18042</idnum><title>Advice from an Old Time Fan of Mescaline</title><author>Red</author><substance>cacti</substance><bodytext>



i just wanted to give u guys some tips since im on mesc right now. I think ive sortta found the quickest most effective way to make cactus tea and to live through the taste but maybe this is all in my head lol. Heres how to make the tea u dont have to dethron it or skin it unless u REALLY want to. After that toss it all in a blender withabout a 3/4 cup of water like an actual drinking glass not the measurement. blend it on slow and work your way till fast (im sure u can handle that right?). after you are graced with the sweet green nectar u have to find a way to get it from such a thick sludge to a liquid right?!?! right :-D so grab a pan however big u need and toss the sludge in the pan YUMMY! I guess if your bold enough u can try to eat the sludge hahahha. ok moving on next boil that sludge on VERY low flame cuz we dont wanna burn off any mesc or alks now do we?!?! no! yea good answer so let it boil down if u need to add some water do so (u want the liquid that will become of the sludge to look pretty liquidy yes u will have alot of chunks of cactus but will get into that next) ok so now u have boiled it on low heat for about an hour right? good u need a strainer anything that will strain *i use one of those bowls with holes, hey that rhymed!* now make sure to filter all the cacti through until u have about 3-5 cupz worth of liquid.
/n
/n
once u have that liquid run it through the strainer to get whatever peices or chuncks of the cacti may be afloat. Now comes the fun part hahaha hardly :-) drop some tea bags into that dirty stuff and let it sit for a good 5 mins now add sugar cuz trust aint nothin gonna save the taste of cactus more than sugar im sure people that have tried know...just dont pour to much in or u will get a syrup. now u have a good drink of some nectar of the gods! feel powerful u are with that drink in your hand hahaha just kidding now heres what i do to get this vile stuff down. Grab some grape juice and a green apple take a swig of the nasty and follow it with some grape juice and then bite into a lucious apple....how this works i suppose is the grapejuice mixes with the sugar in the cactus making it berable and the apple cuts the bitter taste fully and your stomach shouldnt be as mad at u :-p anywayz hope u all learned a thing or 2 about making cactus in under 2 hours and having an awesome trip....REMEMBER, BE SAFE, THINK SMART AND HAVE FUN!!!!! later yall - red</bodytext></report>