<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>1858</idnum><title>A Tryptamine Expedition</title><author>Gracie &amp; Zarkov</author><substance>mushrooms</substance><substance>dmt</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Copyright August 1985 by Gracie and Zarkov Productions. We believe that in a truly free society the price of packaged information would be driven down to the cost of reproduction and transmission. We, therefore, give blanket permission and encourage photocopy, quotation, reprint or entry into a database of all or part of our articles provided that the copier or quoter does not take credit for our statements.
/n
/n
Introduction
/n
/n
This paper is about the strangest trip that we have ever had. Furthermore, in our discussions with other experienced heads it became clear that this trip was one of the more peculiar trips that we have even heard of! That in and of itself might not warrant an article. However, the possible implications of this trip are such that we have decided to write about our experience to add to the store of 'stubborn empirical fact' that make up psychedelic phenomenology.
/n
/n
We are also aware that this trip was outlandish enough that its retelling may cause our readers to believe that we finally have either lost it or are resorting to creative writing. We would like to assure our readers that what you are about to read happened exactly as described (within the limits of our powers of observation).
/n
/n
In this paper we give a description of the trip, our beliefs concerning the phenomenology, and our tentative conclusions regarding our experience. It seems impractical to reproduce the entire trip narrative written right after the experience since it runs to twenty typewritten pages. Therefore, this paper is a highly condensed version of the trip narrative.
/n
/n
Backqround
/n
/n
The weekend prior to our strange experience, Grace had decided to take 5 grams of potent stropharia mushrooms by herself. While it is common practice for us to trip together, Zarkov's high dose mushroom trips have been uniformly negative ever since he established contact with certain insectoid creatures who claimed to have engineered the mushroom for their own purposes. (See, High Frontiers, Issue no. 2 and Note no. 8). Gracie was going in alone to perform reconaissance. After about an hour and one half of arguing with the voice and being unable to see any visions, she began to 'interview' the voice which seemed quite amenable to questioning. Gracie called in Zarkov and together we interviewed the voice in Gracie's head for about two hours. One of the raps was that Gracie had trouble entering the vision state because she hadn't practiced enough visualization and was afraid to leave her body.
/n
/n
Now it is true that despite how much talk there is about how hard it is to get into the far-out mushroom states, Zarkov would just 'fall down the rabbit hole' on any dose over 3 grams without knowing how he did it, while Gracie had much more elusive contact with the mushroom vision states even at doses in the 10 gram range. However, given Gracie's consistent ability to see the 'visible language' on DMT (which Zarkov has so far only briefly glimpsed) and her other visionary experiences on DMT, this rap seemed rather unlikely. 
/n
/n
But, the mushroom voice held out hope. Gracie should practice building a fantasy world in her head and maybe, if we both took mushrooms together, she could 'show' her fantasy world to Zarkov. Zarkov was extremely skeptical of the whole rap. It seemed very enticing and very unlike his experiences with the mushrooms. That week Zarkov went to the East coast on business and left Gracie to work on her fantasy world.
/n
/n
Upon Zarkov's return on Friday, Gracie announced that she had worked diligently on her fantasy world and would like to show it to Zarkov that weekend using mushrooms. The only description she gave of the world was that it was a barbarian bronze age planet run by Goddess-worshipping group of priestesses and that he was cast as a high-tech off-worlder.
/n
/n
Zarkov was apprehensive, since he didn't want another 'alien space wars' trip on the mushroom. The experimental protocol that we agreed on was to do a DMT shot at noon on Saturday and if the experience seemed positive, to take the mushrooms later in the day. The first shot was inconclusive because Zarkov didn't get off but he did get a terrific case of the tryptamine giggles. He decided to take another dose. The visions in the noontime sunlight were exquisite. Over the next half hour, we each consumed betweeen 100 and 150 mg of DMT in four separate 'trips'. The experience for Zarkov had been glorious. His relationship with the DMT over the last four months of regular usage had been uniformly positive even when it had been terrifying. The idea had came into his head (from where?) that by presaturating himself with the DMT, his previous problems with the mushroom could be avoided.
/n
/n
We had fasted since Friday night and had been especially careful with our diets all week. At 2:00 PM, we both took 5 gms of potent stropharia mushrooms. We washed down the 'shrooms with ginger ale. We stayed in the bright sunlight until the closed eye visions began to come on strongly (about 30 mlnutes). We then went into our darkened trip room.
/n
/n
The Trip: Content and Comments
/n
/n
The basic phenomena of the trip were as highlighted below.
/n
/n
/n
/n
/n
Conclusion
/n
/n
Zarkov has not attempted to repeat the experience. Gracie, however, has used the DMT predose before a lower dose of mushrooms (3 grams) and found herself in an irresistible trance with a series of faint visions. This was outdoors at night with a friend who did the same mix and also found herself in a trance, although her visions remained state-bound.
/n
/n
We don't know what Zarkov's vision means or how he got there, but we encourage anyone with visionary tendencies to try exploring these modes.</bodytext></report>