<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>18752</idnum><title>Outgoing and Happy at the Right Dose</title><author>Anonymous</author><substance>tramadol</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>



Total Basics For Those In A Hurry (don't rush!) :
/n
/n
50mg - little if no buzz
/n
100mg - good buzz, lasts a while.
/n
150-200mg - ready to feel it all nite, next day.
/n
250-300mg - stronger, not as enjoyable to me.
/n
300mg+ - no need really.
/n
/n
Ultram (Tramadol) is a synthetic opioid used to treat severe to moderate pain. Personally I'd compare it to vicodin, but perhaps a little stronger. I am fairly experienced in the drug world, although I am clean now, and have been for several months. Go me. Anywho, when I wanted to learn about Ultram, I had a rather hard time, so I'll break down all I can for you all. 
/n
/n
I first tried 50mg, and felt almost nothing. 
/n
/n
Once I tried 100mg (2 50mg pills) I felt a nice buzz, my body was tingly and sort of jello-like. My vision seemed a little affected, and my preception a bit altered as well. Talking was more enjoyable to me, and I sometimes felt quite a speedy effect. Much more outgoing and happy, and just buzzing all day. Also, sleeping on these gave me great and happy dreams, and I always woke up feeling well rested, almost without any sleep at times. I felt 100mg was good for a nice nitely or so buzz, and sometimes enjoyed it during the day. I was able to handle it very well, talk normaly and whatever...but that was after a little using...a few weeks. I'm sure most people can handle it, but you get more used to it over time. 
/n
/n
In excess, 100-250mg it seemed to be a little stronger, more tired and a lot heavier body buzz, but not essentialy more enjoyable. Another report of 500mg I belive said constipation was a problem. I've never taken 500, but 350 at the most, and never had any problems with constipation. It doesn't seem addictive except mentally to me...once I didn't have any, I'd sure miss it a lot, but that can come with anything. I also sometimes experience itching all over, not a bad itch but it can be annoying. Possibly a mild allergic reaction, not sure. Hope this helped anyone wanting to know.</bodytext></report>