<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>19752</idnum><title>Group Salvia Experience</title><author>letsrun</author><substance>salvia</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



I had heard intersting things about salvia and its effects, but the details remained very fuzzy. I bought a gram of 5X extract for 12.00 and one night, devoid of cannabis my three roommates and I decided to try it.
/n
Even though we were a bit nervous, due to the tales of 4 hour halucinations that surround this plant, we used two identical expansion pipes and packed in a half gram into each. We dimmed everything but the christmas lights, and turned off the television. It took a bit to calm outselves, but after we did thats when we started smoking. The salvia was very fragrant, but not a pleasent aroma, and it billowed smoke into the chamber very quickly. I took a huge hit, and it tasted wretched, intensely bitter and acidic, I held it for a bit and started coughing. My roommate took a hit then we each had one more and the salvia was nearly gone as was the bowl my other two roommates had smoked. 
/n
/n
As soon as I exhaled the second time I felt incredibly dizzy. I went to stand up but I felt like I was being pushed back into the couch. I looked at the tapestry, and it started rippling, our christmas lights also seemed beautiful. I went to say something but I could only talk in two or three words. One roommate tried to talk back, and I only made out vowel sounds. The other two were trying to talk as well and one fell over and said simply 'stop pushing me'. 
/n
/n
That made me laugh and I couldn't stop, for the next few minutes I was paralyzed and rolled on to the ground laughing, drool coming out of the side of my face. I looked up and saw I had made everyone start laughing, and it felt like somehow the laughter was holding me on the floor.
/n
/n
Then as quickly as it came on the effects left and I was functional just a little dizzy for the next 20 minutes. If you have a vaporizer smoke salvia in that, It can't taste worse then the smoke. It was a very fun experience, because of the company but it could easily have been a bad and panicked one. I would recommend smoking with some good friends and not by yourself until you know what its like.</bodytext></report>