<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>21090</idnum><title>Written on a Napkin</title><author>Mason M.</author><substance>tramadol</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


I found this written on a napkin in a bar that I frequent:
/n
/n
First I must give some background beging that this drug is a codeine analog. I'd like to start by saying that I am very experienced with opiates/opoids. I have used many forms of opiates in the past three years - especially hydro and oxy codone. I've had my share of pure morphine, codeine, and opium, and have also experimented with the synthetics like meperidine and fentanyl and last but not least (the 'worst' one of them all) diacetylmorphine. However; this is my first time touching base with the codeine analog Tramadol. I am going to do this experiment in real time, (meaning that I have just eaten the drug in pill form) and fully document the effects. And so it starts....
/n
/n
75mg tramadol hydrochloride taken by mouth at 1:50am: I have had some alcohol this evening (~7 beers over the course of 5 hours) so I am near baseline, but it still may add to the effects.
/n
/n
2:05AM: Feeling a slight relaxation between my shoulderblades. Similar to other opoids.
/n
/n
2:10AM: Feeling of slow warmth washing over my body, starting with my head and working its way down.
/n
/n
2:15AM: Feeling a nice buzz now... very similar to other opoids. Body feeling numb to pain. Slight euphoric feeling.
/n
/n
2:20AM: Slight nausea and definite opioid feeling in the pit of my stomach. Body buzz still going strong. Feeling generally good besides the slight nausea.
/n
/n
2:25AM: I am feeling VERY good right now. No adverse effects such as itching or nausea common with codeine or any other opiate for that matter. That slow, tired-warm feeling has crept throughout my whole body now. Now I feel would be a good time to smoke a little of my cigar.
/n
/n
2:30AM: Feeling very sociable right now. Just had a nice chat with a friend while smoking. Full body buzz at this time. Seems to have a slight 'speed' effect and at the same time the classic opiate effect which makes for a very nice combination. All in all I am loving this right now.
/n
/n
2:40AM: Starting to feel tired. I have an exam tomorrow so I think I will nod off to sleep now. :)
/n
/n
-This drug seems to parallel effects of other opiates, but it also seems weak. I think I'd save this for when I don't have anything else... I am thinking about trying a larger dose later on next week.</bodytext></report>