<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2118</idnum><title>A Positive Experience</title><author>Anonymous</author><substance>nutmeg</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>



The Natural Highs FAQ made Nutmeg sound like a substance definitely worth avoiding, but after talking to a friend of mine, I decided to give it a try. It didn't do much, but I was extremely groggy for the remainder of the following day (something I didn't relate to the Nutmeg for quite some time)...
/n
/n
I didn't give up, however, and I decided that I had a neat alternative to watching the Super Bowl... I kept a little account of what happened - it reads as follows:
/n
/n
January 31, 1993 -
/n
/n
/n
/n
/n
February 1, 1993 -
/n
/n
/n
/n
/n
I went back and edited that a tad, because a few of the errors I made were embarassing - I dropped some punctuation, spelling, even a word or two...
/n
/n
Anyhow, I really enjoyed this. I used pre-ground nutmeg, bought relatively recently... It's not something I plan to use regularly, but I have some whole nutmeg I plan try try freshly-ground... I've also heard good things about mixing it with mace. I never felt sick, apart from certain times during the hangover on Monday (I had P.E. that day at school - somewhat nasty, I'll admit.)
/n
/n
For those of you that missed it, 'Acidwarp' (which I referred to) is this wonderful PC VGA kaleidescope program written by Noah Spurrier. I always liked it, but I am definitely glad I thought to watch it while I was on the nutmeg. Also - I went to sleep listening to music (Skinny Puppy, actually..) That was nifty, as I heard things differently. Most of the new things I heard were in the higher ranges, which made the entire CD sound different. I noticed some spoken words I'd never heard before and can't find again - either they're not meant to be heard consciously, or I was putting it there myself.
/n
/n
The only unpleasant part of this at all was the hangover, and that was even kind of nice - it was refreshing to have something to do at school... I found that I felt as if I was falling, most of the time. If I leaned to the side, I kept going that way for quite some time. If I leaned to the left, and then the right, I kept falling in both directions for quite some time. I would have to say that this was, all together, a positive experience. Anyone else have a story to share?</bodytext></report>