<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>21302</idnum><title>Psychotic Gods</title><author>merry &amp; winter</author><substance>dxm</substance><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
It was halloween and I felt the need for trips but the town I live in was completely dry except for ecstacy. Ecstacy was no good for this evening. I needed something less expensive and not so happy.
/n
/n
I had experimented a little with dxm but only with puny 200 mg doses of Coricidin, which I have learned is a terrible source of dxm.
/n
/n
This evening I was inspired by a friend to take an entire box. Having never done this I was intrigued by possiblities because I had recently learned of the different plateaus of the drug.
/n
/n
The night began at approximately 6:00 p.m. when I took all 16 Coricidin, a dose of 480 mg of dxm. Within 30 minutes I began feeling the effects. I became drowsy but not desiring to sleep. I was sitting out on the porch with my girlfriend at the time handing out candy to small children. I began feeling a little uncomfortable because it was cold and nausea was setting in. I laid down on the couch inside to relax and calm my stomach. This did not succeed in calming my stomach and I proceeded to vomit up it's contents about 20 minutes after laying down.
/n
/n
After vomiting the hallucinations began. At first things were a little rough but I soon got into the vibe. My body had become completely numb and I was nearly paralyzed, needing much effort to do anything. The body sensation was incredable. Intense and pleasureful but slightly dirty. The open-eyed visuals made no coherent sense. I had difficulty keeping my eyes open because the room I viewed was so distored that I had difficulty concentrating on anything. The close-eyed visuals were even more intense, consisting mostly of patterns and colors. The next two hours were spent enjoying a variety of sensations and visuals completely immobilized on a couch.
/n
/n
At this point my girlfriend thought it would be a good idea to get me up and moving. Which she can atest to later was a very difficult process. The motivation to move was so little because of the difficulty in doing so. I could no longer reason so it couldn't be explained to me that I needed to move around so I could be coherent enough to go home when the time came. After some harsh words from her which at the time seemed to tear through my soul, I agreed.
/n
/n
The next two hours were rather difficult. I was fighting the urge to return to my vegetable state which conflicted with the trip I was having. Nothing other than mind fucks and other uncomfortable situation occured in the next two hours.
/n
/n
Around this time my parents arrived to pick me up and take me home. I told them I was sick and they thought that was the only reason I need support to get into the car. After stumbling back to my room I was able to finally relax again and enjoy the experience.
/n
/n
I feel asleep somewhere in the next hour or two during some milder close-eyed visuals.
/n
/n
The next morning I felt slight off. I didn't feel sick but I didn't feel that healthy either. I had mad stares. These side effect dimished throught out the next few days and I was back to normal in no time.
/n
/n
Look back upon this trip I relize now I made a lot of foolish decisions during the trip such as atmosphere and quality of drugs, but it was my first intense hallucinagenic experience. It completely change my views and belief and taught me a good deal about my self.</bodytext></report>