<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>21690</idnum><title>Six Months of Depression</title><author>Katie</author><substance>mdma</substance><substance>paroxetine</substance><tag>Bad Trips</tag><tag>Post Trip Problems</tag><tag>Difficult Experiences</tag><bodytext>


Took one pill one evening around 7.
/n
/n
I felt fine, was with a good friend, had been looking forward to the experience.  I was at home and felt comfortable. It took about 45 minutes to come on and then seemed very mild.  Had a pleasant evening, some insights, some very good feelings.
/n
/n
We took some Paxil about 4 hours after the ecstasy.
/n
/n
We tried and tried starting around 12 or 1 but could not get to sleep that night.  My friend and i were up all night long staring at the ceiling experiencing mild visual hallucinations - flashes of light - and wishing we could sleep.
/n
/n
About 3-4 am I started feeling depressed and obsessing about my perceived personality flaws.  This got progressively worse until I had to tell my friend why I was crying around 8 or 9 that morning.  My friend has had no negative side effects.
/n
/n
I don't now remember much of that next week but I was profoundly depressed.  I called a friend telling him i wanted to kill myself.  I could not get out of bed for three days ... I had to call in sick to work half the week.  I wished I were dead and the only thing keeping me alive was the idea that this was ecstasy-related and it might get better.  I was so afraid that I would kill myself that on tuesday I called my doctor and she told me to hang in there, it was definitely from the ecstasy and it might last a few weeks and if it got worse to go to the ER.
/n
/n
I found a psychiatrist on the internet and called her and told her what happened, she made an appointment for a few days later and told me she'd seen the same thing with other people.
/n
/n
I thought a few weeks was such a long time but I wasn't significantly better for three months -- only then did I start feeling like myself.
/n
/n
The Wednesday after I took the e, I bought and then took 5-HTP for over a month (and some b-vitamin related thing that is supposed to be good with it) and ate a lot of things like turkey but they were of no help.
/n
/n
I could go to work and function after the first week but I would go out to my car and cry several times a day, for almost three months. I was so sure I was a horrible person and everyone was looking at me and thinking how awful and ugly I was.  I told another friend everything and she tried to reassure me and it was somewhat helpful, but I was so convinced how horrible I was it was confusing to me -- this person i trusted said I wasn't, but I was so sure I was!
/n
/n
I went to therapy for six weeks after this and it helped a little. I did not get on antidepresssants, I don't know why, I think my mind wasn't working properly for a long time.
/n
/n
After three months things improved but I am still mildly depressed, sad, hopeless, and full of doubts.  I still have symptoms of OCD and obsessive thinking, which I NEVER had before. I have finally gotten some antidepressants and will start taking them -- I hope they help.
/n
/n
Things have definitely improved but I am not the same happy, confident person I was before I took the ecstasy. I have a lot of depression and anxiety.  I will never do it again or any other drug I haven't tried before.</bodytext></report>