<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>21990</idnum><title>An Uncommonly Uncomfortable Experience</title><author>Dex</author><substance>mdma</substance><substance>dpt</substance><bodytext>


My boy Dave and I each took 2 pills. We were rolling nicely. Nothing to complain about. I had some DPT laying around. I never tried it while i was rolling and i haven't seen any reports of people trying mixing the two.
/n
/n
I blew about 150mg.. all done by eye... this stuff never seemed too dangerous. Dave blew about 75mg. My boy Eric was trying this out with us too. About an hour after we blew the DPT, there were pleaseant effects.. so dave blew the other 30mg i gave him. it seemed like a beautiful mix with the MDMA. Things just kept getting more intense and more intese and more intense.  It was so beautiful at first. It was like DMT, it was those kinds of indole-psychoactive effecs.  Eric came out of his in about 30 minutes.
/n
/n
Dave and I started bugging out. I thought i was gonna die. I went outside in the cold to try to bring my roll down, hoping it would bring the DPT effect down.  But things just kept getting worse and all of the sudden, we were sober again. And from there it progressed again were it got worse than it was before. We felt like we were dying and it was to the point where i was gonna walk down the street and admit myself into  the hospital. Going in and out of the cold seemed to help bring me down a lil bit. It was such a wierd almost wave effect.. it would come, get really intense, and then it would be like we were almost completely sober again. I came down about 3 hours after i blew my line. i'm still rolling which is always a good thing. Dave on the other hand, had blown his other line about an hour after the first. So he's still feeling it quite intensly. But Dave and I are keeping eachother calm I am typing this now, dave is still buggin out on the couch. I feel so bad because I gave him the DPT.   This is truely something i will never forget and others need to be warned.. this was my worst trip possible. I can't even explain the extent of it.</bodytext></report>