<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>22785</idnum><title>Amino-Acid Head</title><author>ictus</author><substance>tryptophan</substance><bodytext>


Today was a most beautiful day- perfect temperature, bright blue sky with big puffy clouds, and the best mood I've been in for a long, long time. I took four gelcaps of 5-HTP, each containing 100 mg, and two gelcaps of L-glutamine at 500 mg a piece. After 40 minutes, I took four gelcaps of L-tyrosine. Honestly, I didn't expect much to happen, but about ten minutes after the L-tyrosine, I found a huge grin spread across my face and I was laughing out loud to the book I was reading, 'Psychedelic Trips for the Mind' by Paul Krassner. I put down the book and decided to go for a stroll about the college campus. Normally, I am fairly reserved, shy, whatever- not one to go out of my way to talk to strangers or anything. Once you get to know me, I'm less reserved. Today, however, I found myself approaching everyone I met, and getting into all sorts of interesting conversations ranging in subject from chaos theory and weather patterns to government control of cigarette prices. 
/n
/n
In one sense, this well-being is a sort of self-fulfilling prophesy, because if you think that people want to be around you, and you're more expressive on account of that, then they will (hopefully) see your true self and want to be around you............After having just written that, I realized how ridiculously idealistic and innocent this whole piece may seem, but that would make sense, as I am still feeling that way writing this, some two hours after I swallowed the last of the supplements. I guess it's true that if I'm under the influence of something, I am in no condition to judge my condition because, as stated, I am UNDER THE INFLUENCE of something. I believed that's called hermanuetics? Anyway, I feel no real intoxication apart from an all-pervasive excellent mood, a desire to write and think alot, and to spread the word about this great combination.</bodytext></report>