<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2359</idnum><title>Riding that train</title><author>Murple</author><substance>cocaine</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>



This was far from my first time using cocaine... I'd had it perhaps 2 dozen times since 1990... but this time I decided to try and document the effects as they occured.
/n
/n
Nov. 23, 1997
/n
-------------
/n
/n
11:27pm:
/n
        I just cut out two medium-to-small sized lines of cocaine. I've
/n
already had about 6 or 7 lines over the past 3 hours or so, the last
/n
being a little over an hour ago. I smoked a bowl of pot about 45 minutes
/n
ago, but its effects are pretty much unnoticeable, except maybe a slight
/n
reduction in the edginess of the cocaine effects. I'm definately still
/n
feeling the effects, although I'm in the come-down stage at present. The
/n
next 2 lines should give me a pretty typical high-dose cocaine experience.
/n
At present, I feel contradictorally wired and tired. I feel as if I could
/n
fall asleep if I wanted, although from experience I know I couldn't yet. I
/n
feel a warm fuzzy feeling all over my body, similar to the feeling of the
/n
second wind you get when you stay up all night, but there is also a mild
/n
feeling of stimulant tension. Euphoria has definately long since passed.
/n
Cocaine makes me dehydrated, and this manifests itself primarily in the
/n
feeling of dry mouth. I will frequently suck on my cheeks, trying to
/n
salivate, I guess. It's not really a conscious thing. Its a bad thing,
/n
actually, as it makes the dry mouth worse, and sometimes will leave my
/n
mouth feeling uncomfortable the next day. I'm going to finish my
/n
cigarette, then do these lines.
/n
/n
11:33pm:
/n
        I snort the lines, and immediately feel both euphoria, and a
/n
passing urge to get the rest of my coke out and do more. I get the urge to
/n
smoke a cigarette, so I do. The high intensifies for a minute or two then
/n
levels. I'm mildly euphoric, but very stimulated. Its a distinct
/n
stimulation, more like amphetamines than caffeine. But definately
/n
different. There is a mild anesthetic property, mainly concentrated in my
/n
mouth and nose, and a generalized tingly, warm sensation. I notice myself
/n
typing alot harder, but pausing more between sentences. The urge to smoke
/n
my cigarette is overwhelming. There is a warm feeling along my spine.
/n
Mentally, I feel both calm and stimulated, somewhat paradoxically. If
/n
there were people here, I'd be talkative.
/n
/n
11:38pm:
/n
        I am feeling a barely perceptible decrease in the high, and decide
/n
to stop typing for a little bit to enjoy it, probably with another
/n
cigarette. The urge to do more coke occasionally pops into my mind but
/n
then leaves just as quickly.
/n
/n
11:53pm:
/n
        I went and smoked a cigarette, and alternated (quite frequently)
/n
between walking around my room smoking it, sitting on the edge of my bed,
/n
and putting down the cigarette to lay down and close my eyes. Laying down,
/n
I felt very calm, and as if my body were floating. The peak wore off
/n
gradually, and not evenly. I would alternate between feeling come-down
/n
effects and peak effects, with the come-down periods becoming longer and
/n
more frequent.
/n
/n
        The euphoria is mostly gone now, and the thoughts of doing more
/n
coke are a little more frequent and longer, but are nowhere near
/n
irresistable. Simply being aware of the craving seems to make it go away.
/n
I took a multivitamin just now, which I always do before bed anytime I do
/n
any drugs outside of my usual ones (pot, tobacco, and caffeine). It
/n
generally reduces day-after fatigue. The stimulation is still quite
/n
strong, and more amphetamine-like, although it is beginning to fade into
/n
the post-peak mellowness of cocaine. I am almost back to the point I was
/n
when I began writing this.
/n
/n
        Physically, the dry-mouth has become more noticable again. My
/n
lungs feel sort of grimy from smoking too many cigarettes (cocaine tends
/n
to make me chain smoke), and my nasal passages feel somewhat clogged and
/n
sore from doing coke all night. I snorted a few drops of warm water to
/n
help clear out my nose, which helped significantly. I can still
/n
occasionally taste cocaine in the back of my throat if I snort or breath
/n
deeply through my nose.
/n
/n
12:05am:
/n
        I'm basically back to where I was at the beginning now. I feel
/n
calm and quiet. I don't really feel bad, although there have been times
/n
when I've felt quite depressed and physically worn when I've done alot of
/n
cocaine in a short time. I feel physically worn out, and mentally a little
/n
tired, but its definately not a bad thing - basically like being
/n
overtired, despite the fact that I know I could not fall asleep right now.
/n
I've probably done about 1/2 gram over the course of about 4 hours, which
/n
although is alot, is nowhere near the most I've done; that would probably
/n
be about 1.5 grams over 2 or 3 hours. Aside from the two lines I did while
/n
writing this, I used the cocaine in a social setting tonight, with a girl
/n
and a guy I'm friends with. Its when doing it alone that I'll sit there
/n
and do line after line until it's gone or I just can't take anymore.
/n
/n
        I plan on smoking a small bowl of pot to relax, and write a little
/n
more. I'm going to take a 3mg melatonin tablet and probably a shot of
/n
tequila before I go to bed, to counteract the stimulant effect that would
/n
keep me from sleeping. I'll still probably be unable to sleep for about an
/n
hour, perhaps more, but it will definately help, though it will probably
/n
make me groggier tomorrow.
/n
/n
        Overall, it was an enjoyable experience, but not outstandingly so.
/n
Cocaine simply isn't my drug of choice. I'm glad I did it, but it'll
/n
probably be a while before I do it again.
/n
/n
12:16am:
/n
        I take my melatonin, and take a hit off my bowl. This experiment
/n
is at an end.</bodytext></report>