<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2364</idnum><title>Gnostic Myths and Furry Buddhas</title><author>Murple</author><substance>5meo_dmt</substance><bodytext>



I hadn't smoked any 5-MeO-DMT in about a month. Frankly, I got a little scared of it. While I don't consider it to be 'Chemical Terror' as I've heard it called, it does have a dark side to it. In a way, MeO is like the Ghost of Christmas Future from 'A Christmas Carol' - it shows you the dark side, but it's for your own good. Ebenezer Scrooge needed to see his grave in order to learn to love life. On the other hand, MeO isn't always like that. It can also be incredibly joyful, with almost orgasmic physical sensations coupled with a total presence in the here and now, thinking unhampered by symbols. Often, 5-MeO-DMT trips combine both faces. I've had many trips which I feel are only describable in terms of the Gnostic myth of Sophia. My ego, symbolized by the All, emanates into something analogous to the Aions, and the story unfolds, like a massive parable on reality. I really want to read the Sophia myth sometime then take an MeO hit.
/n
/n
Anyway, I put on 'Planetary Traveller,' this computer generated landscape video, and took a small hit, and watched the movie. I was pretty damn scared when I felt it hit me, but it was a small hit, so I didn't have anything to fear. There was no terror element to this trip, and I watched alien landscapes fly by. Within seconds, my cat came over. Spanky *always* comes when someone takes a hit of MeO; he seems to know, even when he's in another room. It's odd... animals can sense tripping people. He was purring loudly, licking and biting me, pawing my hand, wanting to play. He does the same to anyone anytime they take a hit. I wonder how animals know when people are tripping? Dogs know as well, and even young human kids seem to know. Its as if animals can sense you've entered their reality, the raw here and now unfiltered by symbols created by humanity. In a way, animals are just furry buddhas. LSD for me has always been very plant-oriented... I remember once knowing what it meant to be a tree, for instance. MeO seems much more mammalian. Both, of course, are just my mind attempting to conceptualize the experiences of the naked, eternal now.
/n
/n
I'm glad I decided to do MeO tonight.</bodytext></report>