<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2370</idnum><title>The Caviar of Psychedelics?</title><author>Murple</author><substance>nitrous</substance><substance>ayahuasca</substance><bodytext>



Subject: Ayahuasca Rules! III: The Rootbark Strikes Back
/n
Date: April 04, 1998 at 16:35:28
/n
/n
I took 3 shotglasses full of /n (a bit 1/3 of the total amount originally made, I think). I ended up having an experience WAY stronger than any I'd had from any ayahuasca before... not even from drinking the same amount from the same batch last week. Perhaps it fermented or something from sitting in my fridge for 3 1/2 weeks.
/n
/n
I began drinking it, and felt no effects for about a half hour. The first thing I felt was nausea. I puked. I puked hard. After puking, I decided to take a few hits off a marijuana pipe, to relieve the remaining nausea. It worked great. About 10 minutes later, I began tripping. All I can say is this was one of the most intense trips I've ever had off any psychedelic.
/n
/n
I lay on my bed, listening to The Orb's 'Peel Sessions' through headphones, in a dark room. Closed eye visuals were VERY VERY vivid, and had the color and texture properties of computer animation a la 'The Minds Eye' movies. The impression was of flying over intensely colored rainbow landscapes. Not quite fractal, but similar. Keeping track of the real world was near impossible. Time distortion was EXTREME.
/n
/n
What seemed like 8 hours for me was in fact 2 hours, meaning there was a time slowing factor of 4:1 (perceived:actual). After about an hour, there was a very slight dropping off, and I decided to take a hit of nitrous oxide, having 3 whippets sitting here. Jesus Christ, that blew me into the next galaxy! Brought me back up to peak level, and a little beyond. I did the other 2 right after the first one. I couldnt really feel any effect from the nitrous, but it did definitely give the ayahuasca a strong boost. 
/n
/n
Peak lasted a total of about 2 1/2 hours. By 4 hours after drinking the vile tea, I was more or less down. I packed a bowl of pot, which cleared away the last traces of the ayahuasca, and went to sleep.
/n
/n
DMT is truly the caviar of psychedelics.</bodytext></report>