<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2382</idnum><title>Ketamine Log</title><author>Murple</author><substance>ketamine</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


11:45PM
/n
-------
/n
        I weigh out 50mg of Ketamine HCl which was obtained pure (not as
/n
an injectible solution) from a chemical supplier. It is a crystalline
/n
powder with some rather large chunks that look like crystals of table 
/n
salt. I crush this to a fine powder, then further powder it with a razor
/n
blade, and divide it into two even lines. This is about my 8th experience
/n
with ketamine, though I've never written a report about it before. Looking
/n
at this 50mg, it appears to be alot more than what I've done before.
/n
Erowid's ketamine dosage page states 'One method for nasal use is to
/n
insufflate (snort) 25 mg in each nostril, wait 5 minutes and repeat until
/n
you reach your desired dosage.' I do not anticipate that there will be any
/n
need to repeat. Looking at this, I visually estimate that most of my prior
/n
experiences have been with around 30-40mg.
/n
/n
12:00AM
/n
-------
/n
        I insufflate the first 25mg. There is a mild burn, but not too
/n
bad. The file mentions doing 50mg at once. I've decided to space it
/n
out somewhat and see how things work out.
/n
/n
12:03AM
/n
-------
/n
        I feel very noticable effects. My body begins to feel strange. My
/n
head has a sort of 'balloon-like' feel to it, its somewhat like nitrous
/n
oxide without the sound in the head. Speaking of sounds... I put on
/n
Orbital's live mix of 'Halcyon On &amp; On'. Normally this song is very
/n
pretty... but now, even with headphones, it sounds muffled or distant.
/n
Ketamine certainly doesn't seem to enhance music - quite the opposite.
/n
/n
12:11AM
/n
-------
/n
        I am getting strange visual disturbances. Hard to explain really.
/n
I have the impression that things are moving, but nothing looks as though
/n
its moving. Corner-of-the-eye type stuff... but much more so. There is
/n
a flittiness to the visual effects that is vaguely reminiscent (I was
/n
completely unable to spell this word myself and had to ask for help on the
/n
Internet) of the visual effects produced by ecstasy. My visual field is
/n
swimming... thats the best word for it, somehow. As if looking at
/n
everything through some kind of moving liquid.
/n
/n
12:18AM
/n
-------
/n
        There is a noticable drop in intensity of the effects. Visual
/n
effects are still present. I still have a feeling of 'dumbness' (not being
/n
able to remember words, etc). In fact I am nowhere near baseline. But the
/n
initial rush is over. My body feels 'weird.' There are no closed eye
/n
visuals.
/n
/n
12:30AM
/n
-------
/n
        I still feel a little unusual, and my visual field is still
/n
swimming a little, but the effects are more or less over. 25mg remains
/n
sitting on my plate. I'm not sure I want to do it... I feel as if I wasted
/n
the first 25mg by sitting in front of a computer and trying to describe it
/n
in realtime - as if the very act of attempting to describe the effects
/n
prevents the more interesting effects form appearing.
/n
/n
12:40AM
/n
-------
/n
        I divided the remaining 25mg into 2 more lines, and put some Orb
/n
on through headphones. I insufflate one of the 2 lines, then go to lay
/n
down and close my eyes and listen to music.
/n
/n
12:45AM
/n
-------
/n
        No significant increase in effects from that  mg, so I insufflate
/n
the other. I go back to laying down, after skipping to a different Orb
/n
tune (Little Fluffy Clouds, Dance Mix MK2).
/n
/n
12:56AM
/n
-------
/n
        The song ends. I get up to start writing. My body feels somewhat
/n
'detatched' - I can't quite explain it. Its not numbness per se, but
/n
shares some qualities. Laying on my bed was very odd. The bed felt hard,
/n
and the pillows felt hard, as if laying my head back on a cloth-covered
/n
rock. The overhead light in my bedroom appears somewhat like the light
/n
over an operating table. Not much in the way of closed eye visuals. Open
/n
eyed, my room looks somewhat stark and my perspective seems odd. Is my
/n
heart beating OK, am I breathing normal? I think. Don't really care. I
/n
find myself thinking of mundane, every day issues, trying to find answers
/n
to things which have been on my mind - no answers come to me that haven't
/n
already come to me sober. I seem to be able to think about things in a
/n
detatched, analytical way, but there is no enlightenment coming that I can
/n
see. Most drug 'spirits' I've dealt with have seemed to be male or female
/n
- not so ketamine. The ketamine 'spirit' seems robotic or mechanical in
/n
nature. This molecule taps into some very different energies than the
/n
traditional psychedelics. I would not consider this a psychedelic at all.
/n
Its something else entirely.
/n
/n
1:08AM
/n
------
/n
        I feel I'm in approximately the same place as I was at the 12:18AM
/n
entry above. Visual field is swimming. Feel physically weird...a slight
/n
sensation of motion, perhaps. Somewhat dulled sensation. Music sounds
/n
mostly normal. But the mental effects have noticably dropped off. I feel
/n
more 'coherent' and though quite a ways above baseline, I'm definately
/n
aware that I'm headed there.
/n
/n
1:20AM
/n
------
/n
        Visual effects are still quite noticable, though dramatically
/n
less than what they were. Other effects are decreasing rapidly. I decide
/n
to smoke some cannabis and conclude this experiment.
/n
/n
1:34AM
/n
------
/n
        I am on IRC... I just had a very intense deja vu experience. I
/n
recieved 2 variations on the same chain email from 2 friends who are
/n
totall unconnected (except through me). Then all of the sudden I realized
/n
that the conversation I was having on IRC was something I had before. I
/n
had the strange feeling that I existed in that time segment twice. Just
/n
thought it was worth mentioning... Strange!</bodytext></report>