<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2385</idnum><title>10 Year Anniversary</title><author>Murple</author><substance>ketamine</substance><substance>lsd</substance><substance>dpt</substance><substance>ghb</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>Mystical Experiences</tag><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


* June 4, 1989 - Beijing, China: Many students are killed by government
/n
  troops while protesting for democratic reforms in Tiananmen Square.
/n
/n
* June 4, 1989 - Washington, DC suburbs: Through a a series of
/n
  coincidences, I ran across a little square of white blotter paper
/n
  containing a sample of Hofmann's magical elixir, and so have my first
/n
  trip.
/n
/n
* June 4, 1999 - Beijing, China: Soldiers raised the Chinese flag over 
/n
  Tiananmen Square in Beijing, as China tried to ignore the anniversary of
/n
  the student democracy movement there a decade ago. 
/n
/n
* June 4, 1999 - Washington, DC suburbs: Unlike in China, June 4 is an
/n
  anniversary full of joy for me, and one which I celebrated quite fully
/n
  this year, as is fitting for 10 years...
/n
/n
        Ahh yes... my 10th rebirthday! This is one that I won't soon
/n
forget. I hadn't had LSD in a pretty long time... about 15 months since my
/n
last mild experience, and around 2 years since my last full blown LSD
/n
experience, which had been a little on the rough side. I've been exploring
/n
other entheogens quite thoroughly in this time, but I stayed away from LSD
/n
for a variety of reasons.
/n
/n
        With my 10th rebirthday approaching, however, I decided it was
/n
time for a reunion. I obtained a hit of green geltab acid, and set it
/n
aside for the upcoming anniversary.
/n
/n
        June 4th finally came, and I felt that old familiar nervous
/n
anticipation rising in me. Acid! My first and most familiar ally... I
/n
found myself incredibly nervous, which struck me as silly. I've done this
/n
countless times. I've done crazy shit like ayahuasca. Why is a little hit
/n
of acid causing so much tension? I guessed just because it had been so
/n
long. I decided on 11PM for take-off.
/n
/n
        Around 10:15, I decided to go on my regular internet chatroom to
/n
relax and smoke some cannabis before take-off. I go on there and find one
/n
person taking AMT, one person taking DPT, one person taking AMT with
/n
mushrooms, one taking DPT with ketamine, someone else taking LSD, and a
/n
few other assorted trippers. Surprise, it looks like the universe decided
/n
to throw me a spontaneous rebirthday virtual-party! Well, alright then!
/n
/n
        I placed the sacrament at the foot of my Buddha carving, and lit a
/n
stick of incense. I reflected upon all that I had been through with LSD
/n
over the last 10 years, and all the wonderful things I have learned from
/n
it. 11PM, down the hatch! Well, like I said 10 years ago, theres no
/n
turning back now!
/n
/n
        I felt a strong alert by 11:15PM, and knew I was going to be in
/n
for a wild ride. I was also overcome by a strong wave of nostalgia about
/n
LSD. I put on headphones and listened to Moody Blues, broke out a folder
/n
of my old LSD-influenced drawings, and began reminiscing. I read old LSD
/n
reports of mine (unfortunately, I've only made a few of them). I thought
/n
about how different of a world it was when I first fell through the rabbit
/n
hole. There was still a Soviet Union. The Internet was still not much more
/n
beyond the wet dreams of a few visionary geeks. Someone reminded me that
/n
the Tiananmen Square massacre happened the same day. 10 years. Wow...
/n
/n
        Around 12:15, I wasn't tripping unusually hard, I was at a Plus 2
/n
on the Shulgin scale. I started to get worried that I wouldn't trip any
/n
harder. By 12:30-12:45, however, I realized that I was about to trip quite
/n
a bit harder. I went to lay down just as I found myself hurled into an
/n
amazing Plus 4. I remembered how much I loved LSD right then, and wondered
/n
why I had let it go so long.
/n
/n
        The peak was spectacular. I was laying in bed in a dark room, the
/n
best way to experience acid I think, and the closed-eye visuals were
/n
mindblowing. At the same time, I felt that high-speed LSD consciousness
/n
train blasting through my skull. The visuals and thoughts were very much
/n
in sync. I thought about many things... how much I had missed acid, how
/n
much I had learned from it over the years... and then into reflections on
/n
my life. Realization that this was my first acid trip as a non-smoker,
/n
which struck me as being an important milestone. After a little while, I
/n
stopped thinking *about* anything and I became just a process of
/n
abstract thinking, accompanied by the fantastic acid visualscapes of the
/n
disembodied eye state. I experienced strange temporal distortions, had
/n
visions of the LSD 'spirit' appearing to me as a yound woman dressed in
/n
white muslin, saw both the dark and the light sides of acid as a sort of
/n
'This Is Your Life' nostalgia session. I had a particularly amusing vision
/n
of people putting tabs of acid to their tongues and immediately sprouting
/n
wings from their mouths and flying off to the 'real' world (a la 'The
/n
Matrix', sort of).
/n
/n
        Sometime during the height of the peak, around 1-1:30AM I would
/n
estimate, I had a very strange experience. I had the sensation that I was
/n
somehow communicating with an entity - which I soon realized was Becky.
/n
This had a strange feeling of being real... some sort of telepathic link.
/n
I found myself talking to her soundlessly in some sort of impossible
/n
space, and rapidly became confused as to which one of us was who. 'Whats
/n
happening?' I felt her think... and I thought back 'I don't know, I just
/n
think our realities are overlapping...we'll just have to ride it out.' I
/n
felt a strong feeling of caring, and soon after, it was as if we zoomed
/n
apart at hundreds of miles per hour and the contact was broken. The
/n
strange thing is that the next morning when I spoke with her, she asked
/n
'So, did you feel us talking about you last night?'
/n
/n
        Around 3-3:30AM, things leveled off enough that I was able to move
/n
around. I returned to the internet chatroom, and soon someone convinced me
/n
to try a little ketamine, saying that the combination was amazing. I cut
/n
some out into two large lines, returned to my bedroom, snorted the
/n
ketamine, and lay down. I waited. I got a strange visual effect where
/n
everything began to 'melt' somewhat - the effect is similar to what would
/n
happen if you sprayed water on a watercolor painting. This only lasted a
/n
short while. I felt a mild increase in the trip's 'weirdness' factor, but
/n
overall it seemed to make no real big difference to the character of the
/n
trip - I think I was already too far out for it to have any effect. I
/n
wasn't very disappointed, not being very fond of ketamine to begin with. 
/n
/n
        I got back on the chatroom and had a great time talking about
/n
tripping with everyone for a while. Around 5AM, I decided to take a little
/n
bit of DPT to boost myself back up a little. It added a little vibrational
/n
signature to the trip, and brought back some intensity, but didn't add a
/n
whole lot to the trip, as I only did a small quantity (25mg at most).
/n
/n
        2 or 3 hours later I got an email from some guy in Serbia who had
/n
emailed us a few times before. It was a picture of a peace sign overlaid
/n
on a potleaf. I decided to go to CNN's web s ite and saw a headline saying
/n
the war in Kosovo could be over by the end of the weekend. I made a
/n
little prayer for peace.
/n
/n
        Around 7AM, I had dropped down to a level where I was mainly
/n
stimulated, more than tripping, and decided it was time to take a little
/n
GHB to make myself sleepy. No such luck! I ended up consuming enough GHB
/n
to tranquilize a herd of elephants over the next 6 hours, and barely
/n
noticed any effect over the lingering LSD stimulation. I finally managed
/n
to fall into a fitful sleep around 1PM, sleeping until 6, when I woke up
/n
physically drained but mentally full of energy.
/n
/n
        This was one amazing trip, totally worthy of a 10-year anniversary
/n
celebration! And it was a spectacular reunion with an old, trusted friend.
/n
I won't be letting it go that long again before I schedule another date
/n
with my beloved Lady Sidney the Divine...</bodytext></report>