<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2389</idnum><title>Another Experimental Route</title><author>Murple</author><substance>5meo_dipt</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>



Well, nobody has tried this yet, so...
/n
/n
8:50PM
/n
------
/n
        I weigh out 6mg of 5-MeO-DIPT, chop it up into fine powder, and
/n
divide it into two lines of approximately 3mg each. I divide each of these
/n
in 2 again.
/n
/n
8:53PM
/n
------
/n
        1.5mg up one nostril, 1.5 up the other! The smell/taste is similar
/n
to DPT - or any other tryptamine for that matter. I'm glad that 5-MeO-DIPT
/n
has a very low dosage range... it would not be pleasant to insufflate
/n
large quantities of this. I have an immediate sense that 'something' is
/n
coming, but the effects are not instantaneous.
/n
/n
8:58PM
/n
------
/n
        Yuck! The drip from this stuff tastes very bad, and also is giving
/n
a very uncomfortable burning sensation in the back of my throat. Neither
/n
saline nasal spray nor drinking seems to help. I guess I just need to wait
/n
it out.
/n
/n
9:05PM
/n
------
/n
        I am beginning to feel a tryptamine lift, and the bitter burning
/n
taste in my throat is subsiding.
/n
/n
9:20PM
/n
------
/n
        The taste in my throat has cleared up, and I'm definately feeling
/n
the effects now. At this point, its still fairly mild, and feels like what
/n
I would expect from the same ammount done orally. I wonder if it will
/n
build any more, or if I should do some more? I decide its best to wait
/n
another 10 minutes or so, just in case.
/n
/n
9:30PM
/n
------
/n
        I'm feeling a rather good effect. I seem to have reached a plateau
/n
now. It feels slightly stronger than this dose would orally - but not by
/n
much. I feel warm, trippy, and happy. I have very mild visual enhancement
/n
(bright colors etc), like I would expect from a low oral dose of
/n
5-MeO-DIPT. The time it took from insufflation to peak effect was roughly
/n
25-30 minutes. I think a little more will do nicely. 2 lines of 1.5mg each
/n
are still on the plate, I think one of them is in order - if not both...
/n
/n
9:40PM
/n
------
/n
        I insufflate one of the 1.5mg lines.
/n
/n
9:50PM
/n
------
/n
        Fuck it. Up with the other 1.5mg!
/n
/n
10:02PM
/n
-------
/n
        This route seems to be about co-effective with oral. Same dosage
/n
range (though maybe insufflated is SLIGHTLY more efficient). Similar
/n
subjective effects, although this seems a little more energetic, and it
/n
hit alot faster. The neck tension and jaw clench seems a little less
/n
prominent. There is no trace of stomach discomfort. This is a very clean
/n
experience compared to my oral experiments with 5-MeO-DIPT. This is an
/n
exceedingly comfortable place. This feels like wrapping up in a warm fuzzy
/n
blanket in front of a fire on a winter night.
/n
/n
10:32PM
/n
-------
/n
        Ahhh... very nice. The last few lines are fully kicked in. I am at
/n
a very solid +2. Warmth, a nice tryptamine body high, a relaxed and mellow
/n
mindset. Some mild visual enhancements and perhaps even hits of OEVs
/n
scurrying past the corners of my eyes. I feel like going to lay down and
/n
relax and think for a while.
/n
/n
11:00PM
/n
-------
/n
        Wow. Laying on my couch and listening to my fan was amazing. A
/n
timeless sense of relaxation and bliss. Thinking contentedly about life.
/n
Everything is good. I feel very introspective, in a warm fuzzy way. Again,
/n
the sensation is similar to the coming down phase of a very good LSD trip.
/n
I do feel that I am lower down now than I was a half hour ago, however. A
/n
few quick tokes of cannabis, then off to lay down for a few more minutes.
/n
/n
11:11PM
/n
-------
/n
        I'm unable to return to that warm, floaty place. I seem to be
/n
coming down a good deal now. I am still quite high but the mental effects
/n
are now taking a back seat to the purely physical sensation of
/n
tryptamineness. The bright colors are still very prominent. But the peak
/n
effects are beginning to subside. I feel I've still got a long glide down.
/n
/n
11:50PM
/n
-------
/n
        I'm a little lower than I was. Its very hard to judge how far you
/n
have come with this substance. Its very difficult to tell if I'm feeling
/n
less effect than a half hour ago, or to tell what effects have dissipated.
/n
But I know that I am alot further towards baseline than I was a half hour
/n
ago, nevertheless. I did notice a sort of laxative effect just now - an
/n
increase in peristalsis, rather. Perhaps the stomach effects of oral doses
/n
are not just because of chemical irritation of the stomach or intestine,
/n
but also due to some sort of neurological process? Perhaps it is
/n
interacting with serotonin receptors in the brain stem. Its a non-issue
/n
though. There was no discomfort whatsoever. This was a far cleaner
/n
experience than oral... except for the bad tasting drip. I think I will be
/n
using this route more than the oral route, despite my usual aversion to
/n
snorting things. Its just a cleaner trip this way.
/n
/n
12:30AM
/n
-------
/n
        I'm pretty far down now. Could probably sleep without too much
/n
effort now. This experiment exceeded my expectations quite a bit.</bodytext></report>