<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2391</idnum><title>Phen Phun</title><author>Murple</author><substance>mdma</substance><substance>2cb</substance><substance>2ct2</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>



11:30PM
/n
-------
/n
        I've been fasting since early yesterday evening (~30 hours). I
/n
have here one Mitsubishi pill (MDMA), 10mg of 2C-B (as 5mg pills), and 4mg
/n
(1/2 pill) of 2C-T-2. The plan is to take the MDMA first (as 2 halves, 15
/n
minutes apart), then the 2C-T-2 when that begins to decline, then wait 20
/n
minutes or so for potential nausea, then eat the 2C-B. This promises to be
/n
a good night! I've never had 2C-B before, so I'm trying to go for the
/n
Shulgin classic combination from PiHKAL. The 2C-T-2 is only to make up for
/n
the low dose of 2C-B, and hopefully will not too much color the 
/n
experience.
/n
        Well, half the MDMA is down the hatch!
/n
/n
11:45PM
/n
-------
/n
        Other half down! I think I'm already feeling the first half of the
/n
pill! Must be the fasting... fasting can make a massive difference. Alot
/n
of butterflies in my stomach. Bees. Wow. I've been wanting to do 2C-B for
/n
years, since reading the old Reed College 'bromomescaline' thing. Nexus.
/n
The elusive Erox. I hope this is as good as I've heard!
/n
/n
12:10AM
/n
-------
/n
        Damn, the MDMA is really beginning to kick in. Only 40 minutes in!
/n
Fasting definately makes a difference. Its been a while since I've fasted
/n
over 24 hours.
/n
/n
12:30AM
/n
-------
/n
        Wow... I'm going pretty good! I'm getting alot more than I have
/n
off these Mitsubishis before! I think I need to begin fasting before trips
/n
again. Not only does it make the onset faster and the effects stronger,
/n
but you feel alot 'cleaner' with an empty system. I wholeheartedly endorse
/n
a nice fast of 24 hours (or more) before most entheogens.
/n
/n
1:00AM
/n
------
/n
        Down the hatch with the 2C-T-2!
/n
/n
        I'm in a great place. I read some email a friend sent me today
/n
which I found very touching. I spent some time thinking about that friend,
/n
and realized she truly is one of the treasures of my life.
/n
/n
        Spent some time laying down, just thinking. I love to do
/n
MDMA-class drugs alone or with a small group of friends. Doing it at raves
/n
or clubs is a waste. Too hectic for some of the sublter, delicious
/n
effects. Doing it alone is especially luxurious... you can melt into a
/n
wave of pure feeling. Lay down in a nice quiet dark room... maybe some
/n
mellow quiet music... nice!
/n
/n
1:23AM
/n
------
/n
        I think the 2C-T-2 is coloring the MDMA some, hard to tell.
/n
Anyway, I just ate about one and half of one of the bees... I cut off
/n
about half of one and crushed it, to snort. Might as well, considering the
/n
small ammount I have. The stuff I powdered, I put into 4 *very* small
/n
lines.
/n
/n
1:40AM
/n
------
/n
        Schnorrrt! First bump, not too bad... Second, not too bad there
/n
either. Two more... Third, in the other nostril - little sting. Nothing a
/n
squirt of saline nasal spray doesnt fix... All done! Not bad at all.
/n
Little bit of a bad taste, thats it. I assume the filler material in the
/n
pill probably buffered it alot.
/n
/n
1:50AM
/n
------
/n
        Definately feeling alot more than MDMA now! Im feeling sweaty.
/n
Sorta mescaliney, but the body sensations are still all MDMA. But wow,
/n
they're increasing.
/n
/n
1:53AM
/n
------
/n
        Whoops, just went from sweaty hot to cold. Here come the bees!
/n
/n
2:05AM
/n
------
/n
        Wow. Very nice. I feel very cool, almost cold, despite still
/n
sweating a little from the MDMA. I feel very good, physically. It feels
/n
somewhat like a low dose of mescaline, or the latter part of my 2C-T-2
/n
experience. Not outstandingly visual (yet?) but feels great physically and
/n
mentally. Only drawback - it seems to enhance the MDMA jaw clench quite a
/n
bit. Small price.
/n
/n
3:35AM
/n
------
/n
        Im in a really interesting space. VERY nice. Much like mescaline,
/n
indeed! Similar to my San Pedro experiences, but milder on the body. I can
/n
feel the 2C-T-2 in there, and the MDMA... but theybe all melded into a
/n
nice whole. Colors stand out in razor sharp clarity. Very vivid, yet
/n
natural. Mescaline-type visuals overall.
/n
/n
3:45AM
/n
------
/n
        Wow... this has only been 10 minutes? I must be experiencing some
/n
pretty heavy time distorions. Laying down in bed with my eyes closed I had
/n
some great closed eye visuals. I see things flitting around the corners of
/n
my vision with open eyes. Colors are ultra-crisp. I see little fractally
/n
overlays over alot of things. Shimmery and spider-weblike. Similar to what
/n
I've gotten from mescaline. Sounds of crickets outside are amplified and
/n
reverbate - natural music. Physical sensations are amazing. Not quite like
/n
mescaline or MDMA but about half way in between the two polarities. I can
/n
feel the MDMAishness fading some, but the 2C-B and definately the 2-C-T-2
/n
are going strong still! In some ways theres a GHB-ish feel to the physical
/n
aspect. This is very interesting... and nice.
/n
/n
/n
5:10AM
/n
------
/n
        I'm still pretty stimulated, and my visual field is still pretty
/n
crisp, but I'm on my way down now. Out with a little pot and GHB, then
/n
sleep, I think!
/n
/n
Conclusion
/n
----------
/n
        Well, it took me till near 10AM to get to sleep. Perhaps the
/n
2C-T-2 was responsible for that. There was a long lingering effect, with
/n
good visuals lasting the whole time. Phenethylamines are unlike
/n
tryptamines that way... the effects are more spread out and continuous,
/n
rather than the sharp peak, gradual decline, and long tail of tryptamines.
/n
It was definately a nice experience, and I hope someday to get to explore
/n
2C-B at a more appropriate dosage range.</bodytext></report>