<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>24026</idnum><title>Writhing and Clawing</title><author>TheGreenPhantom</author><substance>5meo_dipt</substance><substance>syrian_rue</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><tag>Difficult Experiences</tag><bodytext>


11:07 pm
/n
Finally I have some time alone, so I've decided to drop ~18mg of 5-MeO-DiPT with around 3g of powdered Syrian Rue, which is in capsules. The plan is to meditate the rest of the night, open up my meridians. 
/n
/n
I've taken foxy at this level 8 times before, but never with a MAOI. 
/n
/n
11:18
/n
Starting to feel a little light headed, with a sensation at my solar plexus that's too weak at the moment to catagorize. 
/n
/n
11:25
/n
I'm going to smoke weed now to help me through the come-up. Tryptamines often have the affect of making me feel depressed while they kick in; the weed helps me with that. 
/n
/n
11:30
/n
Colors seem brighter. If I stare at a certain spot, by slowing my breath and breathing out with slight throat friction like I'm sighing, I can make everything in front of me look farther away. 
/n
/n
The moon is low tonight... just below the treetops. 
/n
/n
12:04am
/n
Blood pressure 130/100. 
/n
/n
12:18
/n
No audios. No visuals. 
/n
/n
12:35
/n
Took an extra 1/3 teaspoon of syrian rue. 
/n
...The rue has a definate sedative effect... I feel mellow right now, but I'm not really tripping. 
/n
/n
12:42
/n
The rue has given me slight ataxia. 
/n
/n
12:51
/n
Feel a slight foxy-ish buzz going on... feels like an extension of the pot, thogugh. My limbs feel light -- like they're composed of air. CEVs are dreamy... a little more visual than when I'm just on weed alone. 
/n
/n
12:58
/n
Finally getting visuals! 
/n
/n
1-6am
/n
The come up is hard. Only writhing in orgasmic bliss seems to stop the harsh body load. Breathing is heavy and labored. 
/n
/n
...I'm a total sexual nerve...
/n
/n
...my sore throat is gone...
/n
/n
...sexual charge is enormous!... 
/n
/n
...just watched some porno (man, people fucking look weird when you're tripping) and jizzed about 5 minutes ago. I'm already charged up again.... 
/n
/n
...the body load is TOO MUCH with s. rue! I'm completely tired, but my body wants to writhe continually like I'm about to orgasm... this is very, very annoying! 
/n
/n
I can't stop moving for even a second. When I do, within a few seconds I'm back to twisting around on my bed or floor, moaning. There's complete sensory close-out. 
/n
/n
12:30pm (following afternoon)
/n
That had to be among the worst trips I've ever had. After wacking off, the body load just kept building and building, causing more or less sensory black-out and incesant writhing. I could not stay still, meditate, and enjoy the trip for a second. I basically lost all control of my physical movements (to an extent). I kept having to jerk around and writhe.... I imagine what I experienced was somewhat similar to what people with Parkinson's go through. 
/n
/n
Dreams/hallucinations consisted of very large, squat and round people with severe cases of edema hooked up to blood monitering devices in a nursing home. 
/n
/n
Midway through this excrutiating ordeal, when I threw up raisins and an orange in my kitchen sink, I remembered that AMT is also a MAOI. I'd gone through this experience before when I'd done 60mg AMT with ~12mg of Foxy 6 hours into the trip. Upon realizing this, I could almost hit myself. 
/n
/n
I finally managed to sleep it off around 6am. 
/n
/n
The rue still has me K.O.ed. I have a slight temporal headache, bilaterally; no energy; my heart rate is ~120 bpm; and tingling extremities.
/n
________________ 
/n
/n
Afterthoughts
/n
Shit kids, stay away from mixing 5-MeO-DiPT with any MAOI! At ALL costs!!!! 
/n
/n
The body load was enough to make me go insane for a little bit. I really could not take the incessant need to twist and claw at my mattress nor the visuals of repulsively bloated humans hooked up to blood cleaning machines and catheters. I started screaming at several points that I wanted the trip to be over. If I wasn't a seasoned user of psychedellics, I might have turned myself in to the ER. At points, the trip was downright scary and the thought crossed my mind that I was getting brain damaged.</bodytext></report>