<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>24140</idnum><title>This Is the Beginning, It's Just Begun</title><author>folodaleada</author><substance>amphetamines</substance><substance>quetiapine</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Ive been seeing a psychiatrist for paranoia and recovering from a drug induced psychosis for a while now, I just recently came off anti-depressents but Im still taking 100mg of Seroquel- an anti-psychotic which has helped me loads to think clearly again.
/n
/n
Now my doctor is obsessed with helping me lose weight, he thinks Im gorgeous and if I was slimmer I'd be stunning- I wasnt even bothered that much before but now hes prescribed me Dexedrine (5mg spansules - long acting). Speed. When he knows I have a history of drug abuse and drug related paranoia.  
/n
/n
I dont know whether to big him up or diss him! On the one hand (Ive only been taking it properly for 2 days, on and off for 2 wks):
/n
/n
-I feel really calm, guess Im kind of euphoric, happy and confident.
/n
/n
- Ive already lost a bit of weight.
/n
/n
- I like this feeling and I cant believe Ive be prescribed speed - drugs for free that cant be bad.....
/n
/n
BUT on the other hand
/n
/n
-Ive already started upping the dose jus a little and taking it throughout the day instead of in the morning
/n
/n
-Sometimes I feel good and happy but sometimes I feel a bit down, nervous, tearful, cold hands but I like that and I start getting an anxious feeling in my chest- this is when I want to take some more
/n
/n
-I either feel focussed or spaced, like theres cotton in my head.
/n
/n
It is a VERY addictive drug. Ive never felt this way bout a drug before. Yea I hate running out of coke if Ive got it but I get over it, sleep it off. I think Im a bit alcohol dependent and I have itched to get more alcohol before but I dont drink all day and I wouldnt dream of it. This however...I think I have opened Pandora's box. And I know whats in there, more speed.
/n
/n
All I gotta say is make sure youg know what youre bein prescribed and think carefully about whether you really wanna take it. Dexedrine is great, it feels good but I have to be  able to control it. Guess Ill soon find out if I can or not.</bodytext></report>