<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>24393</idnum><title>Completely Devoid of Any Pleasure</title><author>Metatron's Cube</author><substance>ghv</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


I recently ordered several bottles of Tranquili-G, much to my disappointment. I started with the suggested dose of 1 teaspoon (1/6 ounce) with absolutely no effect after over an hour. I then took successively larger doses with no effect. At the point I had ingested 2.5 oz (out of a $45, 4-ounce bottle), I finally noticed an effect.
/n
/n
First off, this stuff tastes worse than gasoline. Eight ounces of juice is barely enough to disguise the flavor of one teaspoon of the stuff. The flavor is much worse than even concentrated GBL. Aside from the flavor, the high is terrible. The feeling is very sedated and sleepy, like taking too many muscle relaxes, and COMPLETELY devoid of any pleasure. This is not even vaguely like GHB, GBL, BDO, or any of the other precursors. I could honestly get a better high by taking Benadryl or holding my breath. After the lethargy wore off, I got very nauseous. I felt like I had been poisoned for about 2 hours after the 'high' wore off. 
/n
/n
/n  If you are wondering how this chemical can have a 17% higher affinity for the GHB receptor, but not have a GHB-like effect, let me explain. Many chemicals have a high affinity for a receptor site, but do not have any effect at the receptor. These chemicals are antagonists, meaning they out compete the intended molecule for the receptor due to its higher affinity, and cannot be displaced. Such chemicals effectively block the action of the intended ligand. If the claims are true about GHVs receptor affinity, I would wager that GHV is a GHB antagonist. Although the chemical structure of GHV is only one methyl group different than GHB, one methyl group has been shown to completely alter or remove the effects of both neurotransmitters and odorant molecules in vitro.  /n
/n
/n
Even if you are curious, even if you just want to try it once, dont waste your time.</bodytext></report>