<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>24960</idnum><title>Extremely High Dose of Kavalactones</title><author>Am Duirmott</author><substance>clonazepam</substance><substance>kava</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


I take 6mg of clonazepam daily, so the 15mg dose I took this morning was kid's stuff.  I decided to purchase a bottle of kava extract (40% kavalactones, app. 2000mg kavalactones per bottle).  I tried 800mg kavalactones and, pleased with the mild anxiolytic, euphoric, and very strong muscle relaxant effects that were brought on after about 30 minutes, I decided to down the rest of the bottle.
/n
/n
T=0:10
/n
Anxiolytic effects more pronounced; euphoria and muscle relaxation still moderately strong, but not changed since the 800mg kavalactone dose.
/n
/n
T=0:20
/n
Feeling VERY sociable (a wonderful feeling for a social phobic such as myself); euphoria much stronger; muscle relaxation has practically turned my legs to jello.  No cognitive dulling of any sort.
/n
/n
T=0:30
/n
Effects continuing from 10 minutes ago, though exponentially stronger.  I feel as if I could take on the world, if I could just make my muscles work properly, lol!
/n
/n
T=0:45
/n
Just one thing to say--how can this stuff be legal???!!!!
/n
/n
T=1:00
/n
Not much change from the 30 minute mark, aside from some pronounced OEV's, CEV's, and an almost LSD-like distortion in spacial perceptions.
/n
/n
T=5:00
/n
The effects haven't subsided in the least in the past four hours, and I hope they never do!
/n
/n
~Anxiety level (1-10) -- 0; very disinhibited, in fact.
/n
~Muscle relaxation (1-10) -- 10; and this is saying something, considering that not even Flexeril, Soma, Elavil, or Zanaflex have helped with my fibromyalgia.
/n
~Pain relief (1-10) -- 10; I had a moderate headache before taking this, as well as the constant muscle-aches I deal with day to day.  All eradicated.
/n
~Hypnotic effect (1-10) -- 1; I don't feel sleepy in the least. In fact, I feel mildly stimulated.
/n
~Aphrodisiac effect (1-10) -- 10!!!  Jerking off was quite an experience, lol.
/n
/n
T=8:00
/n
Still feeling the effects strongly, though the hallucinations have subsided just recently.  
/n
/n
T=12:00
/n
Most effects subsided, except for moderate muscle relaxation, anxiolysis, and pain relief.
/n
/n
T=15:00
/n
Back to baseline.</bodytext></report>