<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>25390</idnum><title>Perplexed</title><author>DayDreamer</author><substance>syrian_rue</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Being interested in shamanic ways, I was of course intrigued by the most commonly used Amazonian psychedelic, Ayahuasca.  Wanting to understand the subtleties the ingredients had to offer, I decided to try them out individually, and combine them when satisfied.
/n
/n
NOTE:  I seem to have an EXTREME tolerance to psychedelics.  I have taken 1 hit of acid, ingested 900 morning glory seeds at once, smoked several grams of dried Salvia Divinorum out of bong, on several occasions.  Then I wanted to try an extract, smoked 1 gram of Salvia 5x by myself (used bong).   Ingested 14 g of Mimosa Hostilis extract. ALL to NO effect other then a sense of nausea or minor personality changes, nothing magical.  Most of these states I have been able to successfully induce via meditation. 
/n
/n
Preparation:  Grind 14g of seeds, eat them, chase with water.  Also have not eaten in 12 hours.
/n
/n
These are the recorded events in the order which experienced.  
/n
/n
1:18 Syrian rue taken 14 g
/n
/n
1:51 Light mellow high, barley noticeable nausea
/n
/n
2:22-2:40 I had to hurry to the bathroom, (diarrhea), also where I threw up 3x, then to the kitchen trying to get some water because I choked on my own vomit, throw up some more, about 8x, water is 10 feet away but cant move.
/n
/n
2:44 Lot of zoning out
/n
/n
2:45 Ego seems dissolved
/n
/n
3:00-5:30 Laid on bed, had to get up and throw up 2x, tried to smoke weed, couldnt threw up again.  Back to bed, fell into dreams almost at will, no CEV, or any type of visuals for that matter. Slept
/n
/n
6:05 pretty much down
/n
/n
3:09 Peaceful 
/n
/n
Conclusion:  This is not psychedelic!!   Then again NOTHING has worked for me except high doses of cannabis.  Combos have yet to be tried but most certainly will soon.  I didnt have but a joint with me, if I did it most certainly would have been a less painful experience, so I would have some cannabis handy.</bodytext></report>