<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>25909</idnum><title>Confusion Amnesia Hallucinations...Beauty!!!</title><author>android</author><substance>zolpidem</substance><substance>cannabis</substance><bodytext>


For quite some time my girlfriend had been taking this drug called Ambien for her insomnia. She must soon have learned of the trip you can obtain by taking it and not going to sleep.  For the entire school year, she acted bizzar.  I didnt really know what it was until later.  A few days ago, she finally let me try it.  
/n
/n
I took one. I didnt really know what to expect, but thought it might be something like benzodiazapines.  We went to work for a half hour, and I said I didnt really feel it.  We left work, and I decided to take another one.  She took one also.  We drove up to a secret location in the woods where we had a tent set up. We started smoking buds. Upon laying down in the tent, we were sent into a state of EXTREME confusion and trippiness that I have never ever felt before. (bearing in mind I have been an avid user of DXM, LSA, Buds, and many other mind altering substances.)
/n
/n
There is no way of describing a higher dose ambien trip, because, for one, I can not remember one fucking thing. It causes severe amnesia. Even as things are happening, all I can think is, what in the fuck is going on.  The world swirls and spins with WIERD hallucenations. Ambien makes the world fucking beautiful, and makes it look how it has never looked before. 
/n
/n
A few days after my first trip, we decided to go back to the tent, and took 2 ambien each.  We layed down in the tent, removed our clothes and started smoking our 2 person dragon bubbler.  This time, we were sent off into fairytale land. We saw real dragons, and the bubbler was doing things it had never done before. It had come to life.  All around us in the tent were other people, but every time we looked over at them to ask them who the fuck they were, they disapeared.  We opened the tent door to look at the forest.  Let me tell you that a forest is the trippiest fucking thing you will ever experience on ambien.  I can not even describe it, except that the world did whatever my mind wanted to. It changed into anything and everything.  Of course, thats all I can remember do to the severe memory loss.  Later, my girlfriend told me that I was talking to people who were not there the entire time.
/n
/n
All in all, ambien is the most beautiful, and most wonderful substance I have yet taken into my body.</bodytext></report>