<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>27035</idnum><title>Steep, Not Boil</title><author>Fool</author><substance>poppy</substance><bodytext>


Let me start this out by saying I am NOT a hardcore drug user and do not want to be, I've smoked my fair share of pot and I drink, thats about it.
/n
/n
I got interested in trying Poppies after an experience with Codiene got me a little bit interested in opiates. 
/n
/n
I bought a bundle of 25 dried poppy pods on a friday, they showed up on a monday, I tried 3 attempts with them to get effects. The pods where ground up very fine in a coffee grinder so as to get the most out of them.
/n
/n
/n
Attempt 1: took 3 pods and boiled in water (incorrectly I later found out) for a while and drank the substance, it did nothing... except I DID notice one thing... it gave me horrible gas... almost 'chest pain' level gas.
/n
/n
Attempt 2: 8 pods boiled in water (again incorrectly and this I would pay for later on) and drank, again I felt very gas filled and disgusting, this time so strong I vomited (once)... 
/n
/n
----------------------------------------------------------
/n
/n
now at this stage I was ignorant that the boiling of the pods destroys the alkaloids within the poppies, so I thought 'ahh the worst it does is makes ya sick' and I thought 'I'll up the dosage and get really lit' ... I had no idea what was in store for me on a 12 pod dose.
/n
/n
-------------------------------------------------------------
/n
/n
I took aprox 12 poppies worth of the material and decided I would set it in hot water over night and drink the cold tea the next day. 
/n
/n
The next day passed and at about 7:00 in the evening I took tea out and stranged the material through cheese cloth and into a container...  
/n
/n
I downed the muddy brown brew in about a half hour... I didnt feel much effects except the gas so I figured it was a dud just like before...and that I was an idiot for even trying this... boy was I mistaken.
/n
/n
The sick feeling steadily increased and I felt worse and worse, I was sitting in a chair day dreaming and feeling a little spaced out when the gas really hit me and I had to go vomit... well when I got up from the chair I knew I was high because I couldnt even move correctly and the pain in my stomach felt detached from my body... it was extremely weird... I just barfed all over the place and crawled to my room... I remember laying on the floor feeling so incredibly wasted I couldnt even move...and the pain actually felt good in some sadistic way...it was like the last shred of feeling left in my body... I thought I was going to die and I was so high it was scary (in retrospect it is scary, at the time I was too screwed up to know better)...I mean I cannot express this enough that I felt so 'out of it' and dreamy...
/n
/n
I fell into a deep, dream-filled sleep and had incredible dreams... I woke up about an hour later and vomited again... this continued all night long and lasted into the next day... 
/n
/n
I was constipated for about 4 days... it was horrible... absolutely horrible..
/n
/n
all in all? I say screw poppy tea... it was the worst drug or alcohol related expierence of my life.. I thought I was gonna die and I found out later on I *COULD HAVE* died, easily...12 strong poppies had me pukeing and high for over 6 hours and sick for 8 or 9... thats a wicked experience... I'm afraid to ever go near any opiate again and I'm glad of this fear...</bodytext></report>