<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>27088</idnum><title>Welcome to the Party</title><author>Delphizealot</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>2ci</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Age: 21
/n
Mood: excellent
/n
Duration: wait, it ended?
/n
/n
I had an experience the other day; the day started like any other day, but was destined to be less than ordinary.  Its a Saturday, but I wake up at 8am nonetheless, eager to immerse myself in the music of my morning.  I plan that evening to ingest approximately 20mg of 2C-I and to go to the birthday party for one of my friends.  A good day is in the making, so I spend some time relaxing, waiting for the festivities to begin.  In retrospect, Im not entirely sure why I was waiting.
/n
/n
The evening comes and I weigh out the magic powder; my scale is only accurate to 10mg, but Ive found 2C-I to be relatively innocuous in the past and havent minded the variations in dosage.  /n
/n
/n
A certain giddiness overtakes me as I swallow the gel cap, like the first touch before the foreplay begins.  I grab my MP3 playerI always need musicand make my way out the door.  Seems like Im always passing through doors.
/n
/n
The thirty minute train ride to the party is relatively uneventful, as I find that this particular drug takes a while to come on.  Still, the sound of the train and the people on it, it reminds me of something.  Perhaps something Ive forgotten.  Soon, I arrive at the party.
/n
/n
While at the party, I drank very little, but did smoke cannabis throughout the evening.  I find that the cannabis blends rather nicely with the 2C-I, as I almost start to forget that Im tripping.  Im surrounded by beautiful sounds and colors, even though very little has changed.  Pretty soon, I find myself drifting away from the younger people at the party and sitting with the older crowd.  I hardly move, save for my breathing, and I barely speak, but I listen.  I listen.
/n
/n
'Third door on the right there.'
/n
'Yeah, you know, you just have to take out the trash.'
/n
'No, not that cake, the other cake.  Yeah, we sure dont want none of THAT cake.'
/n
'Dont you remember YOUR birthday?'
/n
/n
These people at the party, they were speaking to each other, but they were also speaking to me, to you, to anyone who would listen.  Im listening.
/n
/n
'I dunno if Im gonna show up for choir practice tomorrow.'
/n
/n
Theyre still talking, in fact.  I speak a few words, now, and hear myself saying the same thing.  Im listening to myself.  Im sitting, silent, unmoving, listening to myself.  A friend of mine convinced me to go to the party and I owe him my gratitude.  There are a lot of great people there and it wouldve been a real shame to miss it.  Peace to you all.</bodytext></report>