<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>2756</idnum><title>An LSD Let Down</title><author>Dark Star</author><substance>lsd</substance><bodytext>



After reading on the internet and talking to people who've done it before, my girlfriend and I decided to trip for the first time.  We picked up 2 hits of blotter for free because I ran a couple errands for the kid I was supposed to buy it from.  So, we went back to her house and ate some McDonald's and ingested the paper.  About 20 minutes in, it began to feel like we got ripped off, so we smoked a bowl and began to watch 'The Green Mile.'  About 1 hour into the experience I began to feel very, very anxious about something, but I couldn't figure out what it was.  Everything seemed weird, out of the ordinary.  So, we continued to watch the movie and I caught my first visual in the part where the black prisoner coughed up the bee/wasp things.  It looked like they came right out of the TV and flew past me.  It was quite cool.  I also noticed that the color on the TV, mainly people's skin, was extremely bright, glowing even.  After that it seemed like I stopped tripping until about three hours later, when a friend came over.  He saw the size of my pupils and decided to play with my head for a little bit.  He kept lighting a lighter by his face, and it was extremely amusing.  Then he tried to make it look like he was going to kick me.  He was across the room and I swear I thought he was going to hit me right in the face.  I freaked out and started jumping around covering myself screaming!  When I realized what I was doing, I found it extremely hilarious and cracked up.  I laughed so hard that tears were streaming down my face.  After I calmed down, I got kinda hungry.  I was leaving at 10:30 and it was 9:00, so I wanted something quick and easy.  I don't remember how it happened, but somehow we ended up making spaghetti.  After I ate, my mom came and got me and I went home and just slept.  I remember I couldn't concentrate on one thought the whole night.  I felt if I did I would go insane.  I also couldn't keep my fingers out of my mouth.  
/n
/n
Overall, I wouldn't say that the experience was a waste, or a disappointment, but it wasn't what I was hoping for.  Still, really cool.  I loved it. I plan to try it again in about 2 weeks with a stronger dose.  I'll do a follow up on it.  Maybe I'll even do a comparison.</bodytext></report>