<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>29207</idnum><title>The Giver</title><author>Mr. Nothing</author><substance>alcohol</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


I have long known that Ambien and Sonata have some interesting side effects; maybe from the first time I used it as per doctors instructions and found myself experiencing minor hallucinations.  
/n
/n
Anyway, here is the lowdown on this particular time.  
/n
1.  around 11 pm I go out drinking.  Over the time from 11 to 2 a.m. I drink a total of three and a half Stella Artois beers--a wee bit stronger than the typical bud light crap.  
/n
/n
2.  Around 2 am, feeling kind of tired, I go to my girlfriend's house.  I eat a bag of chips along the way.
/n
/n
3.  I arrive back in my own apartment at about 4 am.  I immedietly take two pills.  I open each gel cap and shake the powder into my mouth, and then place the gel cap in my mouth as well (so I don't miss any of the powder).  
/n
/n
The effects creep up in a subtle way about fifteen minutes after ingestion.  I prefer to be doing something mildly productive, such as drawing or reading to await the effects. 
/n
/n
Effects:
/n
/n
mild euphoria --&gt; moderate euphoria coupled with feelings of dissasociation.  minor hallucinations, such as the bathroom towel waving in the air.  Mental thoughts went crazy.  significant loss of inhibition.  I was thinking in a slowed down way about these crazy ideas to submit the drawing I was working on to a gallery. I went more and more into my fantasy and imagined myself having an entire show in some gallery, and even more crazy ideas.  Everything has a extremly lucid feeling.  Very dreamish.  Dream-like.
/n
/n
Two hours later and everything is fine.  back to normal.  six am I get up, drink a glass of water, and go to sleep.  I have wierd dreams--dreams that feel suspiciously like I was taking sonata when dreaming.
/n
/n
Other:
/n
/n
Cannabis:  I've never tried smoking while under the effects of sonata, but I've smoked and then taken sonata before.  The cannabis seems to deny the effects of the sonata.
/n
/n
This is not a terrably intense drug. The disassociative elements can be surprisingly strong.</bodytext></report>