<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3015</idnum><title>Starter Fluid</title><author>The Reflecting God</author><substance>inhalants</substance><substance>ether</substance><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
One day (coincidentally my birthday) I'm driving around with a couple friends and we're arguing about what we're going to do later on that night.  Well one of the guys with us suggested doing some ether. I was apprehensive at first but since this girl that I really liked at the time was all for it I decided to try it (yes I'm well aware that it's a stupid reason to try anything).  
/n
/n
After purchasing a bottle of starter fluid from a local convenience store we sprayed the contents into a plastic bag.  We then poured in water until the two substances seperated (ether from heptaine/water) and drained off the bottom layer.  We were left with about half a 350ml bottle of ether.  We poured a couple of splashes of the stuff onto a rag and my friend put it to his nose and started huffing.  He became very disoriented and again my apprehensiveness set in.
/n
/n
Eventually the rag came around to me and despite my fears I started huffing.  About 30 seconds later I started to feel light headed but at my friends' urging I kept on huffing.  Less than 10 seconds later I had what could only be described as an incredibly large head rush, huffing anymore didn't do much and it kind of hurt so I passed the rag on.
/n
/n
The head rush eventually subsided but I still felt light headed and disoriented.  I decided to go inside and get a drink (by the way don't try it inside: the stench takes a long time to go away).  This was extremely difficult due to the fact that it was almost impossible to have any type of coordination, making walking a task in itself.
/n
/n
By the time I got back outside it was my rag again and I couldn't have been happier.  The cycle repeated itself until all the ether was gone, and then about 45 minutes after we had finished I started to feel uncomfortable on the edge of sickness.
/n
/n
All in all I had a good time, but on later dates when using the drug the sick feeling afterwards only got worse.  Also it's extremely addictive.  I recommend trying it once but don't let it get out of hand.</bodytext></report>