<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3036</idnum><title>Doozer Vision (now in colour!)</title><author>Catfish Rivers</author><substance>2ct7</substance><bodytext>



Close your eyes and remember what the Doozers look like...yes, those tiny unstoppable workers that build radish architecture which the Fragils like to eat. Well, some months ago I had adopted the little critters for a visualization technique that I use to clear my nose when it clogs up. Now this is mind over mucus...I envision hords of busy little doozers, some pushing carts of 'boogie material' over a cliff, others mining the product from my nasal cavities and dumping into fresh, empty carts. This goes on for like 20 minutes and then my nose is cleared open.Amen. 
/n
/n
Well, this evening I had used my doozer method to prepare my nostrils for some 2CT7...well, let's just say that after each nostril had its fair share, and amidst a decent amount of chemical burning in the beak, those little bastards started to work over time! I was actually spacing out into trances where I would SEE THE DOOZERS a few feet in front of me, pulling at this and that and this and...keep away from my stash you smurf's or I'll crush you all! Ummm...excuse me. Time for my Depakote.
/n
/n
The doozer visions began to fade as my head started to clear away the cloudiness, somehow reminding me of how I feel on K, very dreamish, feels fluid. The concrete walls of my basement started breathing and swirling in pleasant psychadelic eddies. Streaks of wanna-be-lava-lamp-colors would erput from anything stared at for more than 10 seconds. Bizarre geometries would rise and fall from the ether...etc.etc.etc. Four hours later...I have determined through rigerous trial and error testing: the walls only appear to move and swirl and open up into other dimensions where elves tickle ye old peanut pituitary with pleasure devices. Tee hee hee. Ouch, concrete hard. Oh well, I am not Neo.
/n
/n
Snorting this one seems to give off a different experience than orally ingesting for me. There is an annoying body load in the head, headload for short. It feels as if a psychedelic fog has settled over my brain. I can almost feel my serotonin squirting out of my temples. Throb throb throb. Kinda the same sensation as wearing a elastic winter cap around your head for a long time. This feeling settles in ten minutes after snorting, accompanied by the burn, which, not too too long afterwards, passes. The trip is similiar to orally ingesting, except the fog seems to stay with me the whole time. It's definitely not a bad feeling. As if there is a slight electric current pulsing in my pleasure centers. Oral ingestion produces no fog for me.
/n
/n
I wonder if I like...lick a doozer, would I trip forever???</bodytext></report>