<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3040</idnum><title>Nirvana, or Just a Scrambled Brain?</title><author>Ray Aten</author><substance>lotus</substance><substance>salvia</substance><substance>2cb</substance><bodytext>



I put a gram of Blue Lotus extract (5 times normal strength) and a pinch of Salvia extract in some tea. I stirred it round for 15 minutes, drank it and went to a rave. After about 15 minutes I could feel something going on in my brain, like a new program was being installed. Once in the rave I got quite a strong 2C-B pill, took that and then smoked joints until I came up on the pill. I could feel the lotus before I took the pill. But once I was up on 2-CB it really started to show me what it could do.
/n
/n
My mind felt completely still and perfect. My body felt energized. There was no barrier between the energy in me and the rest of the energy at the rave. The music, acid techno, sounded perfect. I made a make shift pipe from a bottle and some tin foil, and smoked Lotus with my friends who were on the same combination as me. The Lotus seems to clear all the crap out of your mind. Usually on 2-CB your mind is jumping all over the place. You are interested in everything and you have all these wierd ecstatic trains of thought going on that you can't catch up with. But when we had the Lotus it was like everything was at peace. I knew that Everything was fantastic so I didn't have to keep thinking 'this is SO cool'. I felt like I couldn't be more in reality, I couldn't be experiencing things any more perfectly than I was. It was so focused and clear. 
/n
/n
After the Lotus we got the Salvia extract out. I had already been putting a little on with the Lotus to prepare us. I did a hit of Salvia extract (5 times extract) and wooooshhhhhh. A wave of pure bliss had swept me into Nirvana. I shut my eyes. I was flying down a tunnel with spirals of light on the walls. But the tunnel wasn't round, it was made out of multidimensional planes of darkness and I was a part of it. Well actually 'I' in the normal sense did not exist. The experience I was having and the thing I was experiencing were the same thing-they were nothing. I opened my eyes after what seemed like infinity but was actually only a minute or two. Wave after wave of bliss. All I could experience was what the Salvia had given me. I could see the rave going on around me, but I was timeless and spaceless. I carried on smoking Lotus and Salvia and Cannabis every hour or so all night. I felt completely in control the whole time. It was like my brain had been made super efficient.
/n
/n
We all found that after smoking the Salvia we kept thinking we had seen old friends, but they were actually strangers. And we were all disoriented. When I wasn't smoking I was wandering around hoping to find where my friends were sitting, but I didn't mind because I was in bliss. We all felt very wise during the rave and we had all had visions of our futures. But afterwards my brain felt utterly fried. Salvia really does push everything to the next level.</bodytext></report>