<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>31753</idnum><title>The Puppet Master of Life</title><author>Joe</author><substance>4_acetoxy_det</substance><bodytext>


I was at my friends house; this was the 6th time I tripped on this 4-Acetoxy-DET and from what I know its almost like shrooms. I was feeling weird and shaky. I just wanted to go home. I was just seeing the walls move a bit. Nothing really crazy. After a few hours I wanted to leave. I almost could not walk. There were 4 friends and 2 were not tripping. I felt that I was the only one feeling f***ed up. I was starting to think that they did something to me and that at anytime they would snap there fingers and I would come out of whatever they did to me. Now of course I was just TRIPPING. So I got the power to say I have to leave. When my friend Josh came up with me I told him that I was tripping hard, and I thought I was going into a bad trip. He said he was tripping too so I felt 100% better. No more bad trip for me. I really thought I was dieing and I took too much. I started to think about how dumb the human race is, and that we have wars over religion. And how we are dumb enough to really believe that the religion that we were born to believe is the correct one. Come on now people think about that. 
/n
/n
Then I started to think that this life, this world, this universe was one big stage and it was run by the puppet master. Now I would think that this puppet master is god. It was as if the dimension we live in was just a few millimeters thick. As if there was a man on the other side of the curtain of life. Just one big illusion and tryptamines are the key to the outside. As if the master made mushrooms to let us understand this. I started to think really hard about how on earth does this stuff make ones brain all fu*ked up and yet after 4 hours you are ok and back to reality.  It was so damn intense that I cant imagine its not bad for you, but lets face it, its not bad at all. When I got home I looked in the mirror and I saw me, but yet a painting of myself in a mid-evil time. Really cool stuff.</bodytext></report>