<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>33729</idnum><title>Not Thrilling, But Nice</title><author>Spicerack-F</author><substance>diphenhydramine</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


For the past two days I have spent the better part of my waking hours on diphenhydramine, and I enjoyed almost every minute of it.  The more I read about its dangers, the more that worries me.
/n
/n
I had never used diphenhydramine before except as a sleep aid in the recommended dose.  I wasn't using any other drug at the time, except caffeinated soft drinks with meals, and my usual quota of cigarettes.
/n
/n
What follows is adapted from the notes I took at the time:
/n
/n
Tuesday
/n
4:00 a.m.
/n
Took 5 Maximum Strength Sominex -- at 50mg diphenhydramine to a caplet, that's 250mg in all.  I may take more in an hour.  I'm going to go out for a smoke.
/n
/n
4:33
/n
I'm watching a movie on TV.  No noticeable effects yet.
/n
/n
4:55
/n
Slight loss of balance (I may be imagining it):  I stood up and found myself lurching sideways.
/n
/n
5:00
/n
I've taken another 250mg.
/n
/n
5:06
/n
A slight, almost imperceptible sensation of warmth in my abdomen; I also feel definitely light-headed.
/n
/n
5:40
/n
Light-headedness is more pronounced.  I am only slightly drowsy. The experience so far is comparable to a 1st-plateau DXM trip or a mild drunk.
/n
/n
5:46
/n
My pulse is normal, but weak.  I feel slightly warm.
/n
/n
6:04
/n
The drowsiness is delicious.  Only, I keep *almost* falling asleep, then snapping out of it with a start.
/n
/n
I just heard three computer-like beeps, one long and two short.  I think it is an hallucination; there isn't anything in this room that normally beeps.
/n
/n
I know I should not by lying down, but I am anyway.  I'm trying not to fall asleep, though.
/n
/n
My legs feel as though they were about to cramp up.
/n
/n
6:53
/n
It's getting harder and harder to stay awake.
/n
/n
My stomach is uncomfortable.  Not painful, and not exactly nauseous, but *uncomfortable*.  The rest of my body feels the same way, though not as bad; still, I can't find a comfortable postion to lie in.
/n
/n
5:18 p.m.
/n
And sure enough, I let myself sleep -- a long, dead, heavy sleep, but surprisingly refreshing.
/n
/n
10:15
/n
I'm trying this again:  5 left-over Sominex and 8 store-brand softgels of the same potency, 750mg in all.
/n
/n
11:16
/n
No noticeable effects yet.
/n
/n
Wednesday
/n
12:15 a.m.
/n
Still no noticeable effects.  Perhaps I should have taken it on an empty stomach.
/n
/n
12:38
/n
I'm feeling *something* now -- a kind of wooziness.  I'm going to take one more softgel.
/n
/n
1:41
/n
I've taken yet another softgel, bringing the total to 750mg. Effects are obvious now, but disappointingly mild.
/n
/n
1:51
/n
This has been happening for a while:  any sudden noise makes me tense up.  *Any* sudden noise, from the elevator bell to people laughing on TV.
/n
/n
1:57
/n
I keep hearing little tapping and clicking noises.  I do not know if they are real or not, but they still make me shudder involuntarily.
/n
/n
2:43
/n
My hands are *light*.  It's rather the same sensation you get when you pick up a cup you think is full, only to jerk it two feet in the air because it was empty, after all.
/n
/n
4:43
/n
About an hour ago I was sitting, smoking, out in front of the dorm and suddenly I smelled pot.  It was only for a moment, though, and there was nobody around and no apparent source for the smell.
/n
/n
I decided to walk to the computer lab.  As I was walking, I saw several people standing in the distance.  (It occured to me that they might be the pot smokers.)  As I came closer, they disappeared, leaving only one.  He was standing behind some shrubbery, so I could only see his head and shoulders.
/n
/n
As I came closer still, the man's head disappeared and in its place there was a white folding chair standing on top of an outdoor table.
/n
/n
I'm back in my room now.  The effects have largely worn off, though cottonmouth, and a kind of tired feeling in my muscles, persist.
/n
/n
5:01
/n
One thing I forgot to mention, but probably should:  this stuff has been playing havoc with my memory.  I'd be in the middle of a train of thought, and suddenly my mind would go blank -- leaving me wondering what I had been thinking about only a few seconds before.
/n
/n
4:18 p.m.
/n
I fell asleep shortly after that last entry, and woke up about half an hour ago. I have 300mg left, which I've decided to go ahead and take.
/n
/n
5:36
/n
It kicked in while I was eating supper about 15 minutes ago.
/n
/n
For 'only' 300mg, this is surprisingly strong -- it almost feels stronger than the 750mg last night.  My head and limbs feel light, as they did before, and I have the sensation of something thick and heavy wrapped around the top of my head.
/n
/n
My memory is going again, too.
/n
/n
8:23
/n
Effects held steady, neither increasing nor decreasing, until shortly before 8.  Then they tapered off very quickly, and now I feel no more than the slightest intoxication.
/n
/n
Of course, I frittered the experience away watching TV.  When will I learn?</bodytext></report>