<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>33999</idnum><title>Mind Expansion</title><author>Crazy Steve</author><substance>dxm</substance><substance>diphenhydramine</substance><tag>General</tag><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


6:00 PM----I drank 4 oz of Robotussin Maximum strength cough syrup at Fred Meyers around 6 PM somewhere on the edge of the Pacific Northwest. 
/n
/n
7:00 PM----At home loading the groceries, the DXM began to take hold. I retreated to the computer/(anti-drug) parents room  and started to robototize rapidly . Surfed to RateMyThong.com and stared at the beautiful asses.
/n
/n
Gave the ol parents a Master and Commander DVD so I could be left in cyber-peace. I love Erowid. Ive grown up with this site and Im proud of it.
/n
/n
7:40 PM----Thought about Rubix cube and what we have in common with it. I just realized I am in a different life than I was in 2002. Maybe its all a big reality show and Im like Jim Carrey in The Truman Show. Nirvana is speaking to me.
/n
/n
Ate (6) 25 mg Benadryl tablets. 
/n
/n
9:00 PM----Master and Commander is almost over. I will retreat to bedroom at sign of parents looking in my googly eyes and booting  my ass out for the |||| |||| |||| || 14th time. Good thing I have potential. Cannabis would be great with this high. If I had weed I would have black butter knives.
/n
/n
9:25 PM----Cant you trip like I do? Fog in the computer room. This keyboard is hard to see with nothing but monitor light. Im so fucking high and my parents are watching Russelle Crowes British George Washington Wig-style Ship crews fight Napolean in the 1600s.
/n
/n
10:00 PM----Parents are in bed. Watch TV with no concentration skills. Mind expanding as I smoke a cigarette and see a big ass white sheet fly by out of the corner of my eye. I am tripping nicely. Happy high. Motor skills altered if not somewhat hindered. Im getting tired.
/n
/n
11:45 PM----Dont know what Ive been doing except for thinking and staring at things. Perfect combo of DXM and Diphenhydramine.
/n
/n
Off to bed to watch the shadows and closed eye TV. Nice tripping with you. Signing out.</bodytext></report>