<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>34473</idnum><title>Two Weeks</title><author>Global</author><substance>melatonin</substance><bodytext>


Background: I'm 20 years old, in OK physical/mental shape, and I don't use any drug with any sort regular frequency. Rarely do I do any drugs at all at this point in my life.
/n
/n
Normally, I have a hard time getting to sleep. It takes me anywhere from 30 minutes to 2 hours to get so sleep after going to bed, usually.
/n
/n
In short, my 'sleeping schedule' is all fucked up. When I have no commitments and I just go to sleep when I'm tired, I end up staying up for about 20 hours and sleeping for around 10 hours. I also tend to be awake more at night and less during the day. My body seems to be happy with this schedule, but socioty does not.
/n
/n
So, I decided to try some melatonin for a while to see if it will help me. I've been getting to bed around 5:00 AM for the last 3 nights (it was a weekend), and I have work tomorrow at 1:00 PM.
/n
/n
These are my notes on 1-day-short-of two weeks of using 1mg melatonin sublingual tablets as a sleep aid.
/n
/n
May 31 @ 2:50 AM
/n
1mg melatonin sublingual
/n
May 31 @ 3:30 AM
/n
Another 1mg melatonin sublingual
/n
Fell asleep: ~4:00 AM
/n
/n
June 1 @ ~3:00 AM
/n
2mg melatonin sublingual
/n
Fell asleep: ~4:00 AM
/n
/n
June 2 @ 2:30 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
I'm finally tired @ 2:51 AM
/n
Fell asleep: ~3:10
/n
I am very tired upon waking.
/n
/n
June 2 @ 2:11 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
Fell asleep: ~2:30
/n
I am extremely tired upon waking.
/n
/n
June 4th @ 2:20 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
Fell asleep: ~3:00 AM
/n
I am very tired upon waking.
/n
/n
June 5th @ around 4: something AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
Fell asleep: around 5:00 - 6:00 AM 
/n
I am very tired upon waking.
/n
/n
June 6th @ 3:30 AM
/n
3mg melatonin sublingual
/n
I am suddenly tired at 3:45 AM, went to bed.
/n
No notes written down.
/n
/n
June 7th @ 1:00 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
I awoke 6 to 7 hours later not 'groggy' or tired.
/n
/n
June 8th @ 1:50 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
I didn't get to sleep for at least 45 minutes.
/n
I slept 12 hours.
/n
I am very tired upon awaking.
/n
/n
June 9th @ 4:09 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
I went to bed at 4:14 AM.
/n
I have to get up at 8:00 AM.
/n
I slept 4 hours and got up, a little bit (but not very) tired.
/n
/n
June 10 @ 1:19 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual (after not sleeping all day)
/n
I have to get up ~7:30 AM.
/n
I got ~5-6 hours of sleep.
/n
I was tired most of the day after waking up.
/n
/n
June 11 @ 3:05 AM
/n
4mg melatonin sublingual
/n
June 11 @ 3:20 AM
/n
1mg melatonin sublingual
/n
I become tired @ 3:41 AM and go to bed. 
/n
I obtained sleep @ 4: something AM.
/n
I got up @ 1:00 PM, but could have sleep for many hours more.
/n
I am very tired upon awaking. 
/n
/n
June 12 @ 5:52 AM
/n
2mg melatonin sublingual
/n
I'm tired anyway, but I'm taking two.
/n
Thank God I don't have work tomorrow.
/n
/n
Basically, this stuff isn't helping, or I'm becoming too tolerant. It would be OK if I wasn't so tired in the mornings.
/n
I noticed no diffence in the frequency or vividness of my dreams when I was taking it from when I wasn't.
/n
/n
Once this bottle runs out, I'm not buying another, but I'll use it untill it's all gone.</bodytext></report>