<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3463</idnum><title>Feels Like I Am Floating</title><author>pinkwarrior</author><substance>hydrocodone</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



It all began about 11:00 at night, I had just got back from Wal-Mart with my friend, we were ready to extract some hydrocodone. I had 14 10 milligram Watson hydrocodone pills. (Watson is a generic brand of pharmacueticals). If we had ate 7 a piece, we wouldve been f**ked for sure due to acetamineophen, so I extracted them using the extraction method described in the codeine FAQ.  It took about 2 hours to fully extract, but it was worth it.
/n
/n
12:30
/n
My friend and I take turns taking swigs of the solution, we get about 3 swigs a piece, I guess we got an even dose, I think we did anyway. I figured we lost some hydrocodone in the extraction, so I didn't know what was gonna happen.
/n
/n
12:40
/n
We smoke a bowl of marijuana out of a homemade bong. Then, I get out my glass pipe and we smoke 2 more bowls.
/n
/n
12:55
/n
I start spinning very fast, the buzz is like being very very drunk and floating at the same time. I am sure that I am going to puke, I run to the bathroom, but I don't puke and I feel better within seconds.
/n
/n
1:10 
/n
My friend and I walk upstairs to his room, I can't walk straight. I feel some nausea, so I lay down, we turn on Dark Side of the Mood by Pink Floyd and start to drift away. My friend chats on the computer most of the night
/n
/n
Heres what the buzz is like:
/n
Emmense physical and mental high. Feels like I am floating.
/n
Some nausea, but I am laying down, and it goes away while I am.
/n
Music is the greatest thing, I start drifting away to the cd and snap back into reality after a while.
/n
It's very hard for me to keep my eyes open.
/n
Euphoria is intense and great.
/n
I have lost all track of time.
/n
/n
3:00? (I am not sure cause time went so fast)
/n
I suddenly feel like a hole has been torn in my buzz, I am still high as hell, but I figure that the weed has worn off.
/n
So, I smoke 2 more bowls with my friend and lay back down, the weed replenishes my buzz and it's just as good as before.
/n
/n
5:00
/n
My friend hits the sack, both of us still high as hell, we probably didn't actually get to sleep until about 5:30, but I didn't want to sleep.
/n
/n
7:00
/n
We are woke up by my friends grandma, my friend is supposed to go somewhere, but he fakes sick and gets to stay home. We are both still very high, I try not to go back to sleep, but I do.
/n
/n
11:00
/n
I wake up with a slight hangover, nothing compared to a night of beer drinking though. I do not feel sick at all, just a bit hungry and very thirsty.
/n
/n
I recommend hydrocodone to anyone, but extract it!
/n
If you don't extract it, you are heading towards a night in the hospital.</bodytext></report>