<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>34644</idnum><title>Walking the Path of Bliss - Briefly</title><author>Genshed</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>nitrous</substance><substance>absinthe</substance><substance>kava</substance><tag>Mystical Experiences</tag><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


This was an experiment.
/n
/n
At approximately 9:00 p.m., I prepared the liquids.
/n
Two tablespoons each of commercial kava kava extract,
/n
homemade marijuana tincture, and absinthe. This mixture
/n
was put in the freezer to chill.  At approximately 9:30,
/n
I removed it from the freezer and added as much cold
/n
sparkling water as the total mixture.  It turned an opaque,
/n
swirling greenish color - the fabled louche of absinthe.
/n
I downed it in one gulp. The aftertaste was not as 
/n
unpleasant as expected - the bitterness of absinthe with
/n
sweet anise overtones.
/n
/n
I was at home, relaxed, with no pressing concerns.  By
/n
10:00 p.m., I was the only one still up.  My lips were
/n
beginning to feel numb, the sign that the kava was taking
/n
effect.  I was feeling slightly numb in my extremities.
/n
By 10:15 p.m., I was feeling quite good - even more relaxed,
/n
optimistic and peaceful.  I set up my Dreamachine (a homemade
/n
device that produces light flickers in the low alpha range).
/n
I then smoked a small bowl of high-grade marijuana.  As
/n
it began to take effect,  I sat down at the Dreamachine.
/n
/n
The visual effects came on quite rapidly.  The initial
/n
entoptic imagery gave way to a ceaseless kaleidoscopic
/n
array of color, shape and light, reminiscent of some
/n
accounts I've read of mescaline's effects.  I began to
/n
see clear images within the swirling vortex, forming,
/n
rising up to full prominence, then being sucked down and
/n
replaced with new ones.  My spirit soared as I began to
/n
see _through_ the vortex, into a calm and glowing level
/n
marked by a stable geometrical pattern. It appeared to be
/n
hexagonal, in glowing green and yellow - although colors 
/n
such that I've never seen with mortal eyes.
/n
/n
After some ten or twelve minutes of this rapt contemplation
/n
of the fiery fractal mandala that lies on the other side of
/n
darkness, I got up, went to the couch and laid down.  Immediately
/n
upon closing my eyes, I began to see closed eye visuals (CEVs).
/n
These morphed and transformed as inexorably as the ones
/n
before.  After settling in and becoming quite comfortable,
/n
I took up a whipped cream dispenser, exhaled, and took in
/n
a moderate lungful of nitrous oxide.
/n
/n
As I exhaled, I could tell the sensation of air passing
/n
through my trachea had already changed. Inhale, exhale. . . 
/n
and my body began to experience Pure Pleasure.  I felt myself
/n
ascending the World Tree and emerging into the brilliance
/n
of the Living World.  Every joy and pleasure of mortal life
/n
was a mere shadow or gossamer simulacrum of this experience.
/n
Even as I soared above the canopy into the clear blue beyond,
/n
I knew that gravity was pulling me back.  A long long descent
/n
back to my body, where simply being stoned out of my gourd
/n
felt like being stone cold sober by contrast.
/n
/n
I put everything away, brushed my teeth, took two ibuprofen,
/n
drank a glass of water, and went to bed. Got up seven hours 
/n
later feeling fine.
/n
/n
Do NOT attempt this if you are going to be in public.
/n
/n
I intend to repeat this experiment, but not soon and not
/n
very often.  It was an extreme experience.</bodytext></report>