<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>35223</idnum><title>Liquid Satan: A Warning</title><author>AEM88</author><substance>anadenanthera</substance><bodytext>


Yesterday I experienced a mix of anger, confusion, sickness, nausea, physical pain, and delerium that I would wish on no one in this world. I am writing this report just as warning to current users of Yopo and future users in hopes that they take this substance correctly and not make the mistake I did. 
/n
/n
I had 25 Yopo seeds I obtained from an online shop and decided that I wanted to try using them. I ground all of them up in a coffee grinder at once. I usually do not enjoy snorting any substance so I figured I could mix the powder into some water and mask the taste with some fruit juice. This is where I made my mistake...
/n
/n
After this concoction was finished I took a sip. I shuddered. The taste of these seeds was not bad or even horrible. The best way I could describe the taste is pure evil. It made me get chills to look at and smell this stuff it was so viciously evil and disgusting. I managed to get maybe half the liquid down before I decided that it was not worth the trauma on my stomach. I poured the rest down the drain and went to my couch. Shortly after I began feeling physical pain in my head, arms, and chest and I began to get extremely nauseated. I layed down on my bed and put on some positive music in hopes that I could fight these terrible feelings. I battled the nausea and body pain lying down on my bed for a good hour with the stench and taste lingering in my senses. I finally managed to get to sleep for a couple hours. 
/n
/n
I woke up in the evening with the nausea still present. I got off my bed and started walking and could barely hold myself upright. It was the most intense dizziness I have ever felt and I could not think of a time when my equilebrium was more offset. I got into the bathroom and things around me started turning dark green and I panicked for a good couple minutes. It finally passed and so did the nausea and body sickness that had tortured me for the past hours. I am thankful and honestly surprised that I did not vomit my abdominal cavity out. I cannot even imagine what would have happened if I had drank the entire amount of liquid.
/n
/n
So please, anyone who is considering trying Yopo. DO NOT PUT IT IN LIQUID. Use the insuffalation method. It's tried, and it works. Keep it to that.</bodytext></report>