<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>36722</idnum><title>3-4 Grams to Hell</title><author>NoMoreDXM</author><substance>dxm</substance><bodytext>


I am not entirely positive about my dose but I no it was over 3 grams and under 4. I no this because I had bought approximatly 10 grams of dxm and there were only 6500 mg remaining in the bag when it was weighed out after my experience. 
/n
/n
That night I had made 3 capsules containing 150 mg of dxm. I popped all 3 of them at once and after about an hour I did not feel the effects so I decided to put it in toilet paper and swallow it. I had made 6 toilet paper balls of dxm which is how I popped the rest of it. at first when the effects came into play shortly after popping the toilet paper balls becasue this was the capsules effects which was a much more reasonable dose. the capsule dose was fun because I wasnt off the walls hallucinating and stuff but once the toilet paper balls came into effect I couldnt see I would randomly lose consciousness and my parents had saw me robo-walking out of the room I was in tripping. naturally if you have ever seen anyone robo walk its quite noticeable. my mom asked me what I was on and I said I had had a whole bottle of vodka. when she heard this she called my father down from his sleep. my father said I should sleep it off but my mom disagreed. 
/n
/n
after a search of my room she found the rest of teh dxm and rushed me to the hospital at this point I was hardly coherent and was slipping from consciousness but I managed to tell the doctors it was dxm. the doctors put a tube down my throat and pumped me full of charcoal and all that nasty shit but at that point I was no longer breathing so they had to put me on pure oxygen and put me on a respirator. once stabilized which took a lot of respirator time about 15 needles and a ton of charcoal I was sent to an intensive care center at another hospital. 
/n
/n
My message is DXM is fun in a lower 500 mg dose but once I pass the third plateau I end up being too fucked up to enjoy it.</bodytext></report>