<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3693</idnum><title>Mandala and the magical masturbation</title><author>Catfish Rivers</author><substance>clonazepam</substance><substance>2ct7</substance><bodytext>



Okay so this has been the most brilliant night I've had in a decade! I will shamelessy anounce to all that I have reinvented the Art of masturbation this evening! That's right, ten years worth of programatic chugging seen finally for what it was. A groping towards something more engrossing (Reminder to reader: we are now living in a land of masturbation.)
/n
/n
I came across a program called Mandala. It was oblivatingly beautiful screen saver type-thingamagig. I was being pulled all over the screen as colors swirled in some crooked  geometric ballet. Drifting like colored waters down a demented drain...I felt the knowledge that something was being imprinted. A fear of being the guy who hypnotises himself forever. Something important, but foggy happened here. (Do we have a president yet?) I was so enraptured in the eddies of psychedelic rainbows, like locks of hair. Meanwhile I am still wanking away, without any connection to sexual gratification what so ever! I felt perfectly synchronized as my energies comingled with the visual display on the screen. I felt myself being integrated mentally into the graphics. I was merely observing a series of fractal type graphs evolving into new forms continuosly.
/n
/n
So, you can kinda see that there was a separation of consciousness. Or so the polls indicate on this election eve after. Part of me realized 'jerk, it's a screen saver. duh.', and then another part of me was lost, I mean lost like underwater. I could feel the waves of color undulate throughout my corpse (i was not really dead though and another part of me knew that piece of info.) There was always a string to bind whatever came next. My vision became a puzzle that put itself together in a blur, only to melt away into o-blob-ian. Yep, a big fat oblivion. I was nothing but the mass of my body. A weird sensation, much lighter without holding your thoughts, your mind, your tensions, etc. Just energy vibrating in synch with the universe. And then across the screen plops up a grey rectangle, decorated in bold text with the following: PLEASE REGISTER blahrdy blarh blarh. End mind trek. The dork has landed. Safe to say, I was still masturbating. At least some things still stay on auto pilot. 
/n
/n
So safe to say, I had a very enjoyable experience. Fantasy came easy, almost natural. Words became worlds before my mind's soggy eye, and I squinted much easier certainly owing much to the klonapin. I felt in touch with emotions at the core of my self, my anger for sure, and my laziness, but mostly a wounded sense of creativity prevailed. Something once loved now forgotton. Some nice music was then recorded (now remembering) with me my guitar, my puppy making puppy noises, and a casio keyboard. There's a definite mood to the music.  Sounds like a junkyard though.  But kinda happy anyhow. As for the rest of the evening/morning. Nothing but good vibes all the way! I am thankful to see the sun rise today. And after only it I will follow to the end of my every day, no matter who ends up acting as our president. Amen.
/n
/n
And for all us science nerds: I started at 12 midnight. First alert was easliy 45 min, as I a took klonopin .5mg concurrent to the 32mg 2CT7. Relaxed going into it, everything developes softly and in a gentel way. At the 3 hourpoint; klonopin .5mg ingested, I am peaking (reference the screen saver bit listed above, up there) my eye balls out. Not puking, peaking. Or maybe peeking. I dunno. But by Shulgin, a++++. Certianly a mystical moment, out of my body for sure for the first time in my life. And back okay. All of 5 minutes couldn't have passed while I was out drifitng. The same song is on the radio.
/n
/n
Thank goodness for anchors. It felt like a days worth of time elapsed, at least!But only six hours had past by the time I figured out that I had indeed been out of my body...It is very hard to distinguish it from something in a dream. And 8 hours later, I'm still kickin it in Tron land waiting around for Q-Bert to show up. Etc. This stuff is the energizer bunny of phenetylalalawhatevrs.</bodytext></report>