<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>36973</idnum><title>Beautiful, Tranquil, Amazing</title><author>harmsolidsnake</author><substance>hbw</substance><bodytext>


This was my first experience with hallucinogens.  I got a 1/2 oz of HBWR from the basement shaman.  I ate four seeds after the third quarter of the football game I was at (about 9:30).  I had amazingly high expectations for this.  About 15 minutes later, mild nausea hit me, but nothing too huge.  I marched out with no problems, changed out of my uniform, and drove home.  At this point, I wasn't feeling anything at all.  Some friends of mine came over to watch Reservoir Dogs, and the entire time I just laid down enjoying it.  One noteworthy thing is that during the 'Ear' scene, I truly felt I connected and, to a lesser extent, took on the persona of Mr. Blonde and had a huge grin to express the sadistic glee he was feeling.  After the movie ended most of my friends left, except one, who I'll call J.  J dosed 3 seeds at the same time as I took my four.  At this point, both of us had a shaky grip on reality.  
/n
/n
We walked around my house a bit, walked outside, talked.  It was amazing conversation, at least it seemed that way.  After about a half hour of that, I looked up at the ceiling and saw many spinning lights, rotating slowly.  I was enjoying the sight of them until J's cell phone rang.  It was his dad asking him to come home.  He was able to be normal on the phone, but it was hard.  I nearly panicked, thinking his parents would get caught, but soon I remembered that you have to keep a positive attitude about the trip, otherwise it could easily go bad.  So J went home, and I just assumed he could handle himself, regardless of the fact that our pupils were about the size of dimes.  After he left, I grabbed my CD player with the 'Requiem For A Dream' soundtrack in it and went outside again.  I headed into a field and laid down, looking at the stars.
/n
/n
The moon was brilliant.  It had gorgeous shades of green, purple, red, and gold all around it.  I just stared at it for about 30 minutes, amazed at the beauty.  Eventually, however, my attention shifted to the stars.  They were rotating slowly.  Very slowly.  It was then that I saw a planetarium ceiling behind the stars,  At this point, I again started to panic, thinking the world isn't real, but I got control of my thoughts again.
/n
/n
I just laid there, staring until about 2:00 AM.  I went back inside and up to bed, which is when the worst nausea set in.  I got over to my garbage can, puked, and went to sleep. In the morning, I had a new vision of life.  I lost reality the night before, and it was very nice to have the concrete world around me back for good.  I will definately use HBWR again, but with better preparation and I won't have people who aren't tripping come over.  Overall, though, it was a postive experience that I would repeat in a heartbeat.  The tranquil beauty of the world on HBWR is completely indescribable.</bodytext></report>