<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3701</idnum><title>A Day in the Park</title><author>The Perfect Mushroom</author><substance>unlinkable</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>



After having tripped on mushrooms a total of about 10 times, I was very interested to try pure psilocybin when it came around (thank god for cool chem majors.)  Although I am not very well versed in the chemistry of psilocybin mushrooms, I had always heard that psilocybin/psilocin were responsible for hallucinogenic/mind altering effects and that other alkaloids such as baeocystine were responsible for whatever 'body high' one might get, whether this be a stimulant or sedative effect.  My experience in this trip brings that seriously into doubt.
/n
/n
I had known several days ahead of time that I would be tripping that day, so I was restrained the night before; I ate nothing, drank very little and resisted the all too common Friday night urge to smoke ridiculous amounts of pot.  I wanted to enter the trip with no mental or physical baggage.  I woke up at noon, and dosed at two when my companion returned.  I swallowed the gel-cap containing the sparkly, clumpy white powder/crystals with a glass of oj.  I swallowed it open, and the powder inside tasted decidedly bitter like mescaline, not chalky like MDMA or pharmaceutical like 2-CT-7.
/n
/n
The first effects were felt within a half hour, but were difficult to pin down.  I 'felt' like I was tripping, but I had not visuals and very little mental distortion.  We decided to go outside as the psilocybin was building up, and were almost overwhelmed by the beauty of the scene outside.  Most distinctly I remember that unlike with mushrooms, where I feel like my whole field of vision is being distorted in the same way, this time the visuals seemed much more specific and 'cleaner.'  Looking at the landscape I was seeing very intense moving visuals over the sky and the clouds, but the grass and the trees seemed abnormally bright, but unusually still.  I imagine that with mushrooms I would have seen this whole scene distorted by the same 'everything's crawling' mushroom visuals.
/n
/n
After sitting for some time my companion and I decided to take a walk through the rhododendron garden across the street.  While walking through the park our body buzz really peaked.  It was a mixture of the tingling skin/loose muscles that is usually felt with mushrooms, but amplified greatly.  At points it was so intense it reminded me of my experience with MDMA, and my companion reported the same feelings.  I particularly enjoyed rubbing my hands and body against the bark of some large evergreens.
/n
We spent several hours in the park hugging trees and examining the local mushroom species before deciding to head back.  We listened to trippy music and watched the ceiling melt for the remainder of the trip.  It tapered off more slowly than a typical mushroom trip, with a lessening of intensity becoming noticeable by 7:00 and the end of noticeable effects by 9:00.
/n
/n
Overall I would consider this a very successful trip, especially in making me question the role of psilocybin in the alkaloidal composition of psilocybin mushrooms.  I want to take mushrooms within a few weeks of this trip in order to better appreciate the contrast.  More experimentation with this chemical, and other alkaloids contained in mushrooms certainly seems like it would be beneficial in understanding where each fits in to the experience of shrooming.</bodytext></report>