<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>37270</idnum><title>Twilight Sleep</title><author>Dysonism</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>codeine</substance><substance>datura</substance><bodytext>


The website 'Codeine Information' has this to say about combining opiates and datura: 
/n
/n
'Tropane alkaloids obtained from Belladonna (Atropa belladonna), Henbane (Hyoscyamus niger) or Thornapple (Datura stramonium) such as atropine, hyoscine (scopolamine) and hyoscyamine, can greatly potentiate the effects of opioids. The combination of the two produces a tranquillised state of consciousness known as twilight sleep.'
/n
/n
Damn right it does.
/n
/n
I had been planning this trip for a while and so I invited a few people over as trip sitters but about 9 people showed up and it turned into a drunken gathering. One of the people there had a VERY dirty pipe and they let me scrape out all the resin and smoke it (aren't I classy). Anyway I smoked about 6 bowls(cones) of it and was rather stoned.
/n
/n
Hearing that datura increases the effects of codeine to a morphine-like level I deceided that it would be interesting to take codeine as well. I assumed that this may lower the risk of datura related heart attack. I also assumed that it might stop me from doing something stupid because I'd be too sedated to do anything at all.
/n
/n
After extracting the codeine from some bright yellow over-the-counter pain killers I drank the codeine dissolved it water. It is much more bitter than other drugs that I've tasted in their pure form ( meth, coke, caffeine monohydrate). Almost immediately afterwards I packed bong after bong full of dried datura flowers and smoked them. I ended up smoking 3 dried flowers. 
/n
/n
Half an hour later I decieded that I hadn't had enough datura so I caught a train to get some more.( It's probably a bad idea to go in public after consuming datura). Just near a train station there is a house with datura in the front yard so I grabbed some and caught the train back.(only took about 15 mins at most)
/n
/n
As soon as I got back is when the datura kicked in. (I felt no buzz but looking back at what happened that seems about right)
/n
/n
In real life I placed two flowers on the table in front of me. In datura world I placed about twenty flowers in front of me. Every time I went to grab a flower to eat it, it simply dissappeared out of my hand. This seemed completely normal (although irritating) to my tripping brain. I assumed that the datura hadn't kicked in.
/n
/n
Just then the codeine peaked so I went to bed (the best way to enjoy opiates is to lie down, smile and melt into the ground :) )
/n
/n
As soon as I lay down I fell asleep. WHAM! Straight away. Except the odd thing is, I was aware of the fact that I was asleep. This was the cool part of the trip. Codeine and cannabis both create cool closed-eye hallucinations. When I took them with datura I was part of those hallucinations. I was in them. Exploring them from my point of view. I felt like I was swimming in them. Imagine that with an intense opiate buzz and a mild cannabis buzz. Cool.
/n
/n
I was floating in bubbling landscapes or strange cities where randow objects were tied in knots. Eventually I woke up. I glanced at the clock and it turned out I was lying there for three hours. When I got up I lit up a smoke and took a drag. As soon as I exhaled, the cigarette dissapeared. It turns out I wasn't holding a lighter either. It was just a hallucination. It was very vivid though. I even felt a headspin from the smoke.
/n
/n
That was the last hallucination I had. From then on I had blurry vision and a very sore throat. It was so sore I couldn't swollow food.
/n
/n
Well that was my trip. It only lasted about 6 hours even though most people seem to feel datura for about 3 days. It turns out that a similar combo scopolamine and morphine was used in the 50's during childbirth. With it the mother could not feel pain and quite often didn't remember anything about the incident at all. A similar state can be reached with much more accesible substances. (not that I recommend datura. It's very dangerous. I'm one of the few people that had a good trip.)</bodytext></report>