<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>37581</idnum><title>Body Gets Drunk While Mind Becomes Clear</title><author>Hartism</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>cocaine</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><substance>absinthe</substance><bodytext>


The following all transpired when I got hired to deliver pizza. In true fun spirit (2nd year Uni didn't start for another two weeks, so any lost brain cells would have enough time to find their way home), I had to host a staff party at my house immediately (two weeks [post-training of course]) upon my acceptance to the world-class team of delivery experts. This was all lots of fun, but also a first time for the particular combination of chemicals I've listed above.
/n
/n
Firstly, everyone had been drinking casually since approximately 4:00PM during a river-floating trip we went on before the festivities at the house transpired. Now, another quick background explanation: I'd attended a staff party from a few towns West a week prior to my hosting of the Grand Event, which gave me a taste of the hardcore party capabilities within the lower-ranks of the pizza industry. At this first staff party to which I was present we'd enjoyed smoking from a Hooka (lookup the address of your nearest 'Persian Teahouse' for a taste of this radicalness) as well as ingesting some MDMA and whatnot (obviously whilst drinking as well) - so in short, I had a pretty good idea of what was taboo (which was not much incidentally [and also to my delight]) for said pizza crowd. 
/n
/n
This preview allowed me to properly plan my own event for the crew back home. It turned out well, as pizza folks are oddly creative and artsy (which was cool since would soon partake in a favorite past-time of the very late Vincent Van Gogh), so we began to sing along with the commendable acoustic abilities of Brad, the guitarist... As I properly prepared (in the 'traditional Czech-slash-Slavic fashion' as specified on the back of the bottle of Hill's, which was easily procured at a government liquor shop in Vancouver, B.C. for the exclusive event) Absinthe to serve to my guests. This was quite successful except for the breaking of a couple nice martini glasses due to rapid temperature changes caused by the carmalizing sugar setting the minty-flavoured liquer ablaze and then dousing the flame with ice-water (the moral of this side-story is don't let it burn too long). Anyways, that was a cool tangent, but basically what we found to occur while under Absinth's influence, is that one's body gets drunk whilst her mind becomes clear or lucid (or 'nonopaque' for any of you radiologists reading this) and hyper-aware. It's as if I became mentally sober but physically messy, and not necessarily slurring my speech unless already super-drunk from previously-ingested booze.
/n
/n
Alright, we're on a roll now. On to substance of the night number two (or three for those keeping track). Good old Cannabis is what we smoked during that fine dusk-time, and lots of it. In the traditional (at least for recent generations) spirit of British Columbian's we definately inhaled its vapour and smoke without an unneccessary adulteration by crushed tobacco leaves (which many Europeans and Americans seem to enjoy). Of course marijuana cannot be simply neglected because of its seemingly harmless softness when compared with other mind-goodies. 
/n
/n
Finally, enter the pack-donkey of the fragile (a whole nother paper on this perhaps to come) Columbian economy, that which is derived from the leaves of the coca plant native to said nation: Cocaine. This mind-goodie is a real special one to me, personally. It has been a catalyst for a steadily increasing GPA (recently anyways) thanks to the all-night cramming binges it permits me to undertake. Cocaine makes me feel very empowered and clears my mind so that I can think, read, write, or speak at an inhuman pace and for a long time too. The only thing that can ruin the fabulous high it produces is the oft-rediculous 'come down' that follows said space-flight. I am currently suffering from the come-down that occurs post-euphoric cocaine experience - which (the come-down) feels quite enormous and somewhat unpleasant.Right now, as I'm scribbling in this inhuman digital manner (through a keyboard), I'm coming-down hard from at least thirteen lines (spread over a five hour time period) of fun with a handful of enlightened semi-new aquaintences. I feel somewhat aggravated, as well as completely incapable of sleep or ingesting any foodstuff whatsoever. 
/n
/n
For the person wallowing in the aforementioned tumble back to earth, sleep is something of  dream or hope, whilst the thought of eating is disgusting or at least unpleasant enough to cause the writer of this sentence to cringe as he writes this nearly-final sentance (don't worry, the end is coming soon). These effects though, are not quite as noticable when mixed with the other substances that I consumed that night. When mixed with a hefty level of liver-saturation by well-distilled wormwood (Absinthe), the effects of pure cocaine's stimulation are both lessened and enhanced simultaneously. Sounds funny I know, but in short, Absinthe plus blow equals a laid-back euphoria in which I might desire to live out the rest of my days. My fervent advocacy of climbing the chemical junglegym within the playground of the mind aside for a moment - this is dangerous! Just a subjective judgement obviously, and it doesn't mean I'll stop combining the two - in fact I look forward to it happening again, and again.
/n
/n
Now it's 7:14am on the morning after a good-sized binge and I'm getting tired of writing this. I need to sleep (but know I can't) because I've got a calculus lecture at 1:00pm today. I regret that I couldn't arrive at any revolutionary academic breakthrough with this script - but what can one really ask for in a narrative of events?</bodytext></report>