<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3780</idnum><title>First Time Mood Elevation</title><author>Mobius</author><substance>betel</substance><bodytext>



I'm writing this in the midst of my first ever betel experience. Today I went to pick up a package from my friend's house containing, amongst other things, 25mL of a 5X betel nut extract, ordered from an online supplier.  I was waiting to catch the bus home when impatience overcame me, and I dropped 0.5mL of the liquid (equivalent to 2.5g of nuts, by my calculation) under my tongue.
/n
/n
I decided to take this rather moderate dose, rather than a full 1mL dose, due to the fact that I had never used betel before, and didn't know what to expect. Anyway, I held the not unpleasant-tasting liquid in my mouth for about 10 minutes, by which time I was already feeling the effects - at first, a slightly dizzy feeling and mild euphoria. The bus came soon after I swallowed, and I felt quite stimulated, both mentally and physically. I had been in a pretty good mood before taking it, and it just seemed to boost that good mood into a fantastic one. 
/n
/n
As I walked down to the back of the bus, I had the feeling that everyone was watching me and knew about the state I was in, sort of like the paranoia I get when really stoned in public, but it didn't worry me at all (actually I found it quite funny). I talked a bit to the guy sitting in front of me, and noticed that I was speaking much faster and louder than I usually do. Another effect was that my sense of time was altered - the 20 min bus ride felt like no more than 5 minutes. 
/n
/n
Walking home from the bus stop (about 10 minute's walk) I felt lots of energy, and was in an extremely good mood. I got home and talked to my girlfriend on the phone, again noticing my fast and loud speach (she didn't notice though). I felt extremely happy that this stuff works so well, and decided to celebrate with a couple of Nitrous bulbs. I hadn't one these for quite a while, and I was very pleased with the effects. More pleasing still, however, is the fact that now, a good 15 minutes after taking the second bulb, I still feel moderate nitrous effects . In all, it's been about 2 hours since I took the stuff, but it feels like it's been about 45 minutes. Needless to say, I will definitely be using this extract again, probably in the very near future.</bodytext></report>