<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>3806</idnum><title>Not Opium, but What?</title><author>Rumi</author><substance>opiates_myth1</substance><bodytext>



Originally searching for hashish, I was instead offered opium.  Knowing that opium is black or brown I contested the authenticity of this dark red solid covered in red powder.  Regardless I would try it.  The first time was with low grade marijuana in a glass pipe.  The effects were strictly cannabis.  I doubted the red rock at that point and was planning vengence.  Conversely, the next experience - same cannabis, same pipe - was eventfull to say the least.  The rock was not crushed and simply placed upon the cannabis.  Immediately after smoking I entered my car to return home.  It was night time.  Soon - approximately 2 minutes - my perception darkened and I realized quickly that I was in no shape to drive, but proceeded anyway.  Driving on a road I cover every day I couldn't recognize where I was.  I would see (hallucinate) a person running across the street.  This seemed real to the point that I reacted accordingly and hit the brakes.  Then I was convinced that I was driving in the opposite direction.  The road was well lit, yet I was having great difficutly  seeing the objects surrounding me and the road.  I feared I would crash.  
/n
/n
I returned home - I can't remember the details of how - and layed down.  I was suffering from visual impairment.  I began listening on my discman to URB vol. 1.  Strangely the only track I could listen to was Goldie's Innercity.  I attempted to listen to some of the others but was forced to return to Goldie.  The music sounded different; I could hear sounds I hadn't recoginized before.  The singer's voice had me hypnotized.  This was a euphoric feeling.  I had lost my anxiety over the strange new feeling and was now at ease enjoying the sound.  Remembering a friend's story of how opium helped him have intense sex for hours, I decided to masturbate.  When I finally ejaculated the feeling was too intense.  My body reacted as having experienced an attempted resuscitation with shock pads.  I felt my consciousness hover above where I was laying. Then I was enveloped by a black hole.  Everything darken and I felt asleep, yet fully conscious.  Throughout this experience I believed I might have been dying.  I did not fight, just passively accepted.  Suddenly I awoke and had reason to believe that only 10 minutes had passed.  
/n
/n
Indeed this was a frightning experience.  I am now aware of red rock not being an opiate, but have not an explanation for my experience.</bodytext></report>