<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>38078</idnum><title>Not a Waste of Time but Won't Do It Again</title><author>Anonymous</author><substance>2cc</substance><tag>Difficult Experiences</tag><bodytext>


* Summary: I'm glad that I did it and I'm glad that its over and I am happy that I dont have to do it again.
/n
/n
Positive effects: 
/n
+ Time seem to slow down [quite alot] so perception seem better and higher.  
/n
+ Extreme sharpness and alert of all bodily senses, things feel like they did when you were a kid - [colors/feelings/time/texture/experience].
/n
/n
Negative:
/n
-- intellectually disappointing, and boring [some benefits were made].
/n
-- strong nausea and sickness especially for the VERY long first two hours.
/n
-  pains in the lower body and internal organs [which I dont have normally].
/n
-  generally uncomfortable throughout the expeirence both mentally and physically.
/n
-  some body load
/n
/n
12:00 T+0: not white-grey powder 40-55 mg 2c-c down the hatch after being dissolved in water.
/n
/n
It was building up for two hours, two very nausiating hours. 
/n
/n
And I felt terrible, not from the nausea alone, but from the aching effects it had on my lower body and internal organs [pains I dont have normally]. [Obviously the body doesnt like this substance, which might explain why people wake up somewhat happy the day after, that its mostly out of their system ...]
/n
/n
T+2: starts to settle, nausea subsides a bit, but some of it is stayed throughout. [nothing was eaten for some hours before the ingestion] 
/n
/n
Vividing of colors and sounds is appreciated. Existance slows down and is waiting for me to establish a connection.  Strong stimulative effects and lack of intellectual properties and personal preparation denies me that.
/n
/n
T+4.5: Byebye colors and sharpness and minimal mental experience and time distortion. Stimulant aspects disappointingly remains.
/n
/n
T+6.5: Almost all gone STIMUALNT is still here. Hard to concentrate and remember.
/n
/n
Note: various herbal teas [camomile, green tea, etc.] helped reduce nausea, but was not taken only after two hours.
/n
/n
At the 3rd the refregerator was open and VARIOUS VERY COLORFUL AND VIVID vegtables were taken out, cut to a fullscale sensory salad.
/n
/n
A short walk in the open outdoor gave a spectacular view of greens and blues and reds and whites. Some strange happyness and reassurance was there, some things were easier to grasp and understand, others not at all.
/n
/n
--
/n
I wouldnt recommend this substance to anyone at any state, unless there are no other possibilities in the universe available.
/n
/n
For me, the best thing mind-alterants can benefit is intellectual property: 
/n
1) that I change things in my life *AND MYSELF* to a positive direction and avoid negative paths.
/n
2) that I may better understand who what where why etc.
/n
3) stop from the flood of day-to-day confusions aka. 'Normal' modern life, and the ability to concentrate on what is right and benefitial.
/n
/n
And maybe the occasional tranquility and euphoria from our ever-angry surroundings but for me its not the major issue. If it doesnt give this, or if I can achieve it in other ways I would not take it or any other.</bodytext></report>