<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>38183</idnum><title>Facial Fuck Up</title><author>------unknown</author><substance>inhalants</substance><bodytext>


Ok, I smoke weed, drink, and take less dangerous methods of DXM (than Coricidin), but freon is the only thing I do not like. Not because of the effects, its actually better than some things, but you will soon find out why I no longer like it, and why I will not be doing it anymore......standing up that is.
/n
/n
6:00 a.m. I am getting prepared for school and seeing as how I have not gotten high in a while/tripped off DXM at school. Yes I do those at school, but can control myself well for the dosage. Anyway, I figured I would try huffing freon. I heard about it from where else...school. I tried it once before, but didn't hold the freon in my lungs. Well around 6:20 I decide to go out back and get some out of the A/C. I walk to the bus stop five minutes early so I can get a couple hits before the bus comes. Well, I take in a large amount, hold it for 10 seconds or so, then the effects came quickly, I felt like I stood up really fast and got light-headed...X10. The ringing in my ears subsides so I take another large breath. I started losing my vision, but was too delerious to notice, I guess I was unconcious while standing....
/n
/n
the second breath was a bad mistake. The next thing I know, I am slowly waking up and trying to pick myself up off the pavement. I look down and see all 4 of my front teeth sitting in a pool of blood. I ran back to my house and called some people, not knowing what my excuse was gonna be..(falling face first in the middle of the street) but I just say I tripped. After a few minutes, I went back outside and got my teeth. I ended up getting 3 re-implanted, they came out with the root. One broke off at the gumline. It has been 2 weeks of hell. Not worth 30 seconds of being high. Now that I look back, I'm actually pretty lucky considering it was still dark when it happened and I believe the bus would have run over me if I had been there any longer. I'm not telling you dont huff freon, just make sure you dont hurt yourself because when you pass out, you dont have a clue what happened after, so at least be sitting and dont inhale too much. Good luck, and be safe....keep your teeth.</bodytext></report>