<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>41809</idnum><title>Harsh Smoke</title><author>New guy</author><substance>nutmeg</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Background:
/n
I am 16 the only drugs Ive tried other then this is cannabis frequently for the last while and alcohol once, t3's orally for awhile (ran out) and I tried taking nutmeg orally. Got about 2 spoon full down then the next one I spit up to no effect.
/n
/n
Earlier this day:
/n
I haven't eaten since about 6 1/2 hours ago so I have empty stomach, I smoked cannabis bout 7 1/2 hours ago (should be back at baseline). Thats the last of my cannabis. I am really bored and I don't like being sober and read both good and bad reports smoking it so if I don't have to taste it decided Id try it.
/n
/n
Bowl Size: 
/n
width and length = 1 inch
/n
depth = 1 cm
/n
/n
Timeline:
/n
/n
t+0:00
/n
I smoked my first bowl, nutmeg is really flammable. When I lit it it stayed lit the whole time, I had to put it out with bottom of lighter. I took quite a few hits, couldn't keep up with the burning but got quite a bit. Also I agree with the statement of it being heavy smoke, I didn't find it harsh on the throat like cannabis the first time but more harsh directly on the lungs. Burns my nostrils when exhaling through nose.
/n
/n
t+0:01
/n
It really stinks just like nutmeg so I wet my pipe. Gonna let it dry but needed stink out. Had a drink of water.
/n
/n
t+0:02
/n
No effects noticed except slight light headedness. Gonna smoke another bowl.
/n
/n
t+0:03
/n
Smoked second bowl doesn't get any easier on the throat really, didn't burn as easily, because I washed it but it did burn but no less harsh but a bit of chunks of nutmeg washed into my mouth while inhaling (ew!)
/n
/n
t+0:05
/n
Mild marijuana like high, spacey mainly. I ate a banana, hungry but not from nutmeg just from not eating for awhile.
/n
/n
t+0:15
/n
No more effects, want better so I did another half of bowl.
/n
/n
t+0:40
/n
No more effects again the same, did another full bowl, decided thats the last if it doesn't work with 3.5 bowls it's not worth it.
/n
/n
t+1:20
/n
Went for a walk to avoid parents, felt a little nauseas but thats gone.
/n
/n
t+1:50
/n
I feel like Im back at baseline.
/n
/n
Good Parts:
/n
mild high
/n
/n
Bad parts:
/n
harsh smoke
/n
nauseas (not too bad)
/n
heavy smell
/n
bit of bad taste
/n
short high
/n
need to smoke too much for effects</bodytext></report>