<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>42008</idnum><title>The Way of the Jogger</title><author>Mirth</author><substance>yerba_mate</substance><bodytext>


PREPARATION:
/n
/n
There are several ways of preparing the mate brew, but the easiest way (while still tasting good and with effects) is to use a teapot. First, I put the mate into the. Mate is very sensitive to 'extreme' heat, therefore I must not use boiling water (only hot), and I also pour a little bit of cold water on the leaves a minute or two before adding the hot water.
/n
/n
I Let it sit for about 4 minutes or so. Letting it sit too long will cause it to taste very bitter. I filter out the leaves afterwards. 
/n
/n
It's also a good idea to add about a half teaspoon of honey to get rid of most of the bitterness.
/n
/n
TASTE:
/n
/n
One could somehow compare it to green tea, but I not sure. What's certain is that it's got a very earthy taste that's just awesome in its own subtle way. It takes some time really appreciate it. A twist of honey makes it easier to like, I just don't overdo it.
/n
/n
EFFECTS:
/n
/n
I know that what I about to write is partially contradictory to what the chemists say about mate, but this is what happens to me:
/n
/n
At first I can feel that something is happening to my muscles, I not sure what, but its kinda pleasant. Halfway down the cup I feel that my muscles start to relax, followed shortly by a mental relaxation as well. I sit there and feel peaceful for a while. 
/n
/n
I've also noticed that feelings of hunger tend to disappear very quickly.
/n
/n
If I then decide to move a little around, like stretching and jogging, then after a minute or so I suddenly get lots of energy. Not like tensing up, I just get an energy kick and I can endure more and longer than before. And it really feels good to run and climb and such.
/n
/n
But, if I choose to perhaps meditate, then that's no problem. If I don't show that I could need some energy, then I stay relaxed.
/n
/n
Actually, one of the first times I drank it I laid down, and suddenly I found myself at the edge of sleeping.
/n
/n
That's probably a coincidence since mate is reported to contain much caffeine.</bodytext></report>