<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>4226</idnum><title>Measure That Dose!</title><author>Wren</author><substance>14b</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



Now that GHB (and so many other mind expanding compunds) has become illegal many people have been searching for legal substitutes.  Always eager for a new experience I (in my dream, of course) found out about a substance called 1,4 Butanediol.  1,4 BDO, for short.  1,4 BDO is a metabolic precursor to GHB, that is, once it gets into your body it's metabolized into GHB.  
/n
/n
9:00(a.m)-Ingested 1.5-2 ml 1,4 BDO.  Had to estimate dosage because I was not at home with my glassware.  Tasted very nasty, although less gag inducing than GHB.  No salty taste, more an oily...something.  Like GHB, 1,4 BDO has very little taste when taken with something like OJ. 
/n
/n
9:20-Felt my first alerts.  Slight numbing of body, like GHB, and less early euphoria.  This was prob'ly because the body has to convert the substance before it's useful.
/n
/n
9:40-Definite alteration of mood, sense of euphoria very present.  Numbness over entire body, and blurring of the visual field.  Very much like a light dose GHB exp.  I wouldn't drive at this point.
/n
/n
9:50-Great loss of coordination, some thought interference...I decide to shower and redye my hair at this point, which was a mistake.  In the shower I got lost and very dizzy.  Kept almost slipping onto the floor.  Finally I get out, stumble into my clothes and get to the living room couch.  Still very euphoric...and pretty horny, just like GHB.
/n
/n
10:20-Feeling just great, like a moderate dose of GHB, thought process definetly skewed because I decide to take a booster dose.  I dropped about (now I'm not sure about this one because my coordination and eyesight were getting somewhat blurry) 1-2 ml into my glass and drank it.  Ick.
/n
/n
10:30-I drop into a strange sleeping/waking state.  My friend videotaped me, so this is how I know what happened, I have no recollection of this.  I began babbling about potatoes.  'I'm a potato, you're a potato...My eyes were closed, but I kept talking, parroting back things she said to me.  My limbs were moving with jerky movements, somewhat like the convulsions brought on by a high dose GHB exp.
/n
/n
10:50-Fell into unrousable sleep (like a slight GHB overdose) my friend turned me on my side, so if I puked I wouldn't choke on it, and then left, checking my breathing every so often.
/n
/n
11:45-Woke from sleep state, babbled some more, thinking was _so_ messed up.  No mental tracking whatsoever.  Eventually fell back to sleep.
/n
/n
12:30-Bounced fully into conciousness, then I puked.  (Very rare for me, through 5 years of experiments I've puked twice.)  After I was sick the world pretty quickly came back into focus.
/n
/n
1:00-Finally close to normal, very little residual effects, no real hangover.  Slow on the uptake though.</bodytext></report>