<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>43421</idnum><title>Extreme Drowsiness and Confusion</title><author>Interfleet Champion</author><substance>melatonin</substance><bodytext>


When staying at a friends house, I noticed a bottle of Melatonin.  I had heard that it is fairly psychoactive, so I decided to take six pills.  
/n
/n
After half an hour, and only a slight sense of drowsiness, I decided to take seven more.  An hour after that, things started to get interesting.  I laid down on the floor for what seemed like an hour, but was probably just several minutes.  I was confused, drifting in and out of consciousness, and I had no idea where my friend was.  
/n
/n
At one point I fell asleep and had an odd and vivid dream about being at some sort carnival or festival.  I was rudely awakened by my friend bouncing a large green exercise ball on my head and saying some weird crap.  This may have been a result of my confused state or just his regular inane blather.  
/n
/n
After a while he succeeded in waking me up and we decided to watch 'Boondock Saints'.  I lay down on the floor to watch the movie and throughout it I was half asleep or completely asleep. I honestly cannot remember anything about the movie.  
/n
/n
After it ended, and he woke me up again, we played 'Goldeneye' for N64.  I noticed that while playing the game, my reflexes suffered greatly.  I was pressing the wrong buttons and sometimes areas of the controller where there were no buttons.  I fell asleep a few times while playing the game, which allowed him to rack up an embarrassingly large amount of kills against me.  
/n
/n
After he destroyed me in a game that I am normally very good at, I decided that it was bed time.  I stumbled to the spare room and collapsed on the bed and instantly fell asleep.  I had another strange dream.  This one seemed to go-over the night's events with a sense of clarity and in the dream it seemed like I was part of some sort of murder mystery similar to the board game 'Clue'.  I thought that I would feel refreshed after waking up, but I was groggy for the next day, which is probably due to the high dose.</bodytext></report>