<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>45624</idnum><title>A Great Combo</title><author>anonymous</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>kratom</substance><substance>caffeine</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


T0:00 3:15
/n
I just filled up a tablespoon (about 14 grams), tilted my head back, and tossed it all in. Chugged coke until I got it all out of my mouth. Not too bad (but not good tasting by any measure). I think it would be worse mixing it with anything as it kinda clumps together (plus changes whatever the substance is too a greenish/brown mush.)
/n
/n
T+10 minutes
/n
Starting to feel something. A little relaxed, seems to have relieved some fatigue I was feeling and I feel like my brain is a bit sharper. Nice so far.
/n
/n
T+20 minutes
/n
Strong desire to work. Play guitar, write songs, anything creative sounds fun. Listening to music. Very clear-headed. Smoked a few puffs of MJ from a pipe to spice things up a bit.
/n
/n
T+25 minutes
/n
Wow, what a difference. I think Kratom should have MJ to go with it. It's very synergistic.
/n
/n
T+30 minutes
/n
The effects have gotten stronger. My body is warm and fuzzy but my mind is still sharp and relaxed. Coffee sounds really good. So off I go. Will probably sprinkle a little Kola Nut in it for a stronger cup of java.
/n
/n
T+40 minutes The warm and fuzzy is still increasing. Feels like a low dose of MDMA body wise. Rubbing, stretching, scratching are all more pleasurable.
/n
/n
t+60 minutes  I think I'm peaking now but it's very subtle. Feels good, I'm very talkative, more patient and understanding with people. Mind is dulled a bit now, I think from taking a tad too much, but this is enjoyable for sure.
/n
/n
4:27
/n
I can tell this will last a while. I could take a great nap, but I think MJ and coffee will be the way to go. I'm actually enjoying playing my guitar scales ;)
/n
/n
4:36
/n
Next time I will probably take a little less. I enjoyed the stimulant effect. I higher doses Kratom acts as a CNS depressant. Plus it's expensive :) Still felling groovy though. ANd still playing scales :P
/n
/n
4:56
/n
Kinda blurry eyed. Not really a strobe effect, but it feels like my eyes are slowing crossing and then straightening out again (slight double vision). Doesn't bother me though.
/n
/n
Overall this felt kinda like codeine. A good body high. I doubt this will be legal in the states for long. It's by far my best bet for a legal high that is safe. A good special occassion drug. Not one to be used everyday (I imagine it could be mentally addictive).</bodytext></report>