<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>45713</idnum><title>Beauty and Freedom</title><author>The Mime</author><substance>5meo_dmt</substance><substance>2ci</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
/n
/n
/n
My friend recently ordered a gram of 5-meo-DMT and a Gram of 2C-I.  He offered me to be the test bunny of snorting the DMT, which I was not to sure about from my previous experience with smoking DMT.
/n
/n
I snorted about 5 mg of the DMT.  I have read that this stuff is supposed to burn like hell, but I felt no burn.  Before the effects had kicked in he started capping out his 2C-I.  I gave him thirty dollars and he cut me out a 60 MG line of 2C-I.  With no comprehension of what I was about to get myself into I slammed it up my nose.
/n
/n
The burn came immediately followed by the intense urge to go to his van and lay in the back until the burn subsided.  I felt as though I had been punched in the nose by Mike Tyson in his prime, and the rage of being hit was right there with it, so being smart I removed myself from the presence of people.
/n
/n
The visuals came quickly.  It was a rainy day and the water drops were dripping slowly down his window.  The stickers in his van had come to life.  I was so comfortable but so irritated that I had this pain in my nose.
/n
/n
Finally the neg. effects stopped and we decided to get in a car and go to my other friends house.  Going down the street at about 90 mph I rolled my window down and stuck my head out.  It was like I was next to the car not in it.  I was looking at the glow of everything around.  The rain drops hitting my head at that speed didn't sting rather it was an indescribable feeling.  The only words I could muster were beauty and freedom.
/n
Me and my friend M spent a long time walking into stores then quickly running out in hysterical laughter cause we couldn't take how strategically placed everything was.  We chased after a dog.
/n
/n
My personal favorite part of the trip was when I wandered into the woods to discover Amanita Muscaria's everywhere.  I have a strange connection with these mushrooms sober or tripping.  I appreciate their beauty and their power so it was fun to see them in this frame of mind.
/n
/n
Eventually we got to a house and relaxed.  We spent the rest of the night taking hits of 5-meo-DMT and laughing.  The whole thing probably lasted about 10 to 12 hours.</bodytext></report>