<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>4692</idnum><title>Coricidin - Nasty Stuff</title><author>Anonymous</author><substance>dxm</substance><bodytext>



I've taken some illegal drugs, and havnt really been satisfied with any of them. A couple weeks ago some friends were taking 'Coricidin - Cold &amp; Cough' so I decided to try it out. We took 2 pills every 30 minutes, and over approx. 2 hours, took 10 pills. It took a long time to get truly fucked up, probably about another 2 hours of building up. For a while, about an hour, it was great, my eyes were about as wide as they could stretch and I kept staring and I was really happy. I noticed from doing it you go on weird tangents and do the same thing over and over until eventually you freeze and forget what you're doing. 
/n
/n
Everything went downhill when one of my friends, while tripping out looking at a table, just dropped his head and busted his nose. He started bleeding and wouldnt stop, we tried everything to slow down the bleeding and it just kept coming out. Luckily it stopped, after losing an amazing amount of blood, he said he was very dizzy and ended up passing out for the rest of the night. We didnt give much notice to it because you seem to not have a care in the world while you're on it.
/n
/n
Next my other friend started vomiting. About every 5-10 minutes he'd go back to the bathroom to throw up. All the while another guy was just staring blankly into a flashlight for god knows how long, and my whole body went numb. I kept hitting myself in the face, humored that I couldnt feel anything, then just flipped out and punched my friend (the one with the flashlight) he didnt even notice. Then I proceeded to take a knife and attempt to thrust it through my finger. I had no idea what I was doing, all I knew is I couldnt feel anything, luckily before I cut myself too bad my friend with the flashlight took the knife and put it away when he realized I was about to hurt myself.
/n
/n
So now it's down to 1 passed out bleeding guy, one sick vomiting guy, 1 guy about to cut his finger off and another (weighing 200 lbs) who actually had a good trip messin with a flashlight. The night seemed to pass without any casualties and the next day we all woke up around 6 or 7pm, sleeping about 17 hours, and completely disoriented the whole next night. Now we've switched to DXM only drugs, and havnt had any problems so far.  We are going to stay away from the CPM.</bodytext></report>