<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>47114</idnum><title>Frightened Parents with Hospitalized Child</title><author>Mom</author><substance>inhalants</substance><bodytext>


My 15 year old daughter has been in the same school system all her life but doesnt have many personal friends who visit the house but she has a lot of people to talk to at school.  Shell usually follow what any new friend does - from style of clothing, to attitude - and we fear she would do the same with drugs.
/n
/n
Shes dated the same boy since she was 13.  She remains a virgin, drug-free, goes to church, has brought many of the students to church, doesnt hesitate being the good, clean kid and it surprises us that she is kind of a loner, bringing over one or two new friends a year and never wanting to do much of anything outside of the house.
/n
/n
Most girls at her high school she labels as sluts.  Many, many have gotten pregnant prior to 15 and she says most 'do' everyone.  She also says nobody would share their drugs since it costs them money to do so, and that its cool to say no.  She seems to have the right attitude to stay away and so far her friends have been good girls.
/n
/n
Until......she met the 18 year old.  After years of not letting our daughter roam the streets and meeting parents when she wanted to stay overnight, teaching her all along fears and what to look for and how to judge, we chose to start letting go of the reins and trusted that she had the knowledge she needed to say no. We interrogated her new friend and let her spend the night without a parent there, since they were having to babysit the three-year-old brother.  I drove up to the store to get dinner and drove by the trailer on the way home and said to myself, No, I told her Id be coming by to check on her but its too early.  I checked on her at 8:30pm.
/n
/n
My daughter seemed to have woken up from a sleep with a dream still on her mind that I thought would take her a minute to snap out of.  When I realized she wouldnt and that her actions were that of the worst drunk Id ever seen, I screamed at the other two girls to please tell me what she had taken.  All my daughter could say was something about hearing a marble rolling back and forth.  She tried to snap out of it and went right back to the marble, holding her head and falling back on the bed.  Once she stood up and hugged me and said she was scared.  I called her father immediately, and she asked me not to and then started talking about the marble again.  She was sweating and there was water dripping from one of her eyes.  She could not keep from repeating this time warp.
/n
/n
Suddenly, she snapped out of it and was normal again.  I knew drugs didnt do that and it finally dawned on me that the two girls said they thought maybe she had a seizure.  I hadnt heard them tell me that four times.  They had called the next door neighbor up to check her out and he just told them to call us and that he thought she had diabetes or something.  He was leaving, and at that moment, I walked in the door to see this.  She had just snapped back from having a seizure and crawled off of the couch when I walked in the door and she was holding her head talking about a marble.  Within ten minutes, the girls elaborated about this so-called seizure and said her eyes were rolling around and the man there said she was flopping all over the place.  They tried to keep her from hitting her head and one of the girls tried to give her mouth-to-mouth.  The man told me later, when I questioned him, that the girls were standing there laughing at her while he was telling them to call her parents.
/n
/n
I decided to take her to the hospital because there was something wrong with her in her brain.  When we were driving she kept saying over and over again very calmly, Mom, stop the car, let me think.  But there was moments of silence in between.  I didnt know then what I know now - that her mind was stuck in a time warp, reliving the last minute of her life of Mom stop the car, let me think.
/n
/n
While in the emergency room, she went into a second time warp of, Okay mom, Im awake now, really, please just tell me what you said first.  This is the first time warp that was repeated through the first hour in the waiting room, and although the conversation is cut short here, the entire story from after school until the emergency room was repeated by me throughout the first hour until I was exhausted and shortened it.
/n
/n
Sarina: Okay mom, Im awake now. Tell me what you first said.  Just tell me.
/n
Mom: I let you meet Amanda halfway up the street so she could come over.
/n
Sarina: Amanda came over?
/n
Mom: Yes, and you went to spend the night with her.
/n
Sarina: I spent the night with her?
/n
Mom: Yes, and either you had a seizure or you did drugs?
/n
Sarina: I dont remember that.  I dont remember anything.
/n
Mom: Its okay.  Were going to find out if something happened inside of your head and youll be okay.
/n
/n
And she cried and let me hold her head on my shoulder and rub her and hug her.  She never lets me do that - not since she was 5!!  And there was some silence.  I asked her for her boyfriends phone number and his best friends.  She rattled them right off.  Her long term memory was there but she was reliving the last two minutes of her life.  Then she would look at me and say:
/n
/n
Sarina: Okay mom, Im awake now, really. Tell me what you first said.
/n
Mom: I already told you.
/n
Sarina: Just tell me.
/n
Mom: You went to Amandas house.
/n
Sarina: Amanda house?
/n
Mom: Yes, and you went to spend the night with her.
/n
Sarina: I spent the night with Amanda?
/n
Mom: Yes, and either you had a seizure or you did drugs?
/n
Sarina: I dont remember that.  I dont remember anything.
/n
Mom: I know you dont remember, honey.  I know.
/n
/n
We were called into a room.  Sarina had a second set of time warp questions, but she had heard the above for an hour so she was able to retain a bit of it but added additional questions on top of them.
/n
/n
Sarina: Is this Saras shirt?
/n
Mom: No, its Amandas.
/n
Sarina: It looks just like Saras
/n
Mom: Your shirt got wet and you changed it at Amandas house.
/n
Sarina: I went to Amandas house?
/n
Mom: Yes.
/n
Sarina: Is this Saras shirt?
/n
Mom: No, its Amandas
/n
Sarina: Sara has a shirt just like this.  Did I have a seizure?
/n
Mom: We dont know yet.
/n
Sarina: How long have I been out of school?
/n
Mom: About three hours.
/n
Sarina: I went to school today?
/n
Mom: Yes
/n
Sarina: I dont remember that.
/n
Mom: I know, honey.
/n
Sarina: Whos shirt is this?
/n
Mom: Its Amandas
/n
Sarina: Did I have a seizure?
/n
Mom: We think so but theyre going to test you.
/n
Sarina: Did I do drugs?
/n
Mom: We dont know, honey.  Were going to find out.
/n
Sarina: How long have I been out of school?
/n
Mom: About three hours.
/n
/n
They drew blood and asked for a urine sample.
/n
/n
Mom: Take out your tampon, put in this new one, and THEN wipe yourself so no blood get in the cup.
/n
Sarina: Im not on my period.
/n
Mom: Yes you are.
/n
Sarina: I am?  I dont remember that.
/n
Mom: Are you alright in there?
/n
Sarina opens door: What am I supposed to do?
/n
Mom: Take out your tampon, put in the new one, and THEN wipe yourself so no blood get in the cup.
/n
Sarina: Im not on my period.
/n
Mom: Yes you are.  Let me come in and help.
/n
Sarina: No.
/n
Mom waits.  Door opens.
/n
Sarina: What am I supposed to do?
/n
Mom: Take out your tampon, put in the new one.
/n
Sarina: I did take it out but I need a new one.  I dont have one.
/n
Mom looked in and saw the empty wrapper on the sink: Yes you did.  The empty is right there.
/n
Sarina: Okay
/n
Door opens: Sarina: What am I supposed to do again?
/n
Mom: Wipe yourself and pee in the cup.
/n
Sarina: I need a tampon.
/n
Mom: You just put one in.
/n
Sarina: No, I just took it out. Get me another one.
/n
Mom: Okay
/n
Sarina: What am I supposed to do again?
/n
Mom: Did you wipe yourself?
/n
Sarina: Yes
/n
Mom: Pee in the cup.
/n
/n
Finally, she succeeded and lays back down on the bed.  They came to get her for her CT-scan of her head and rolled her down the hall in a wheelchair.  She later didnt remember doing that.  She also didnt remember getting a chest x-ray.  Her white blood cell count was elevated and the doctors thought she had a major infection somewhere that might have caused the seizure.
/n
/n
All tests came back negative.  No alcohol. No drugs.  No anything.  She was clean and her brain had no bleeders.  The doctor was confused and had to call a pediatrician who recommended her to stay overnight for observation.  They labeled her as a confused child and kept her overnight rather than sending her home even though none of them saw the repeated question and answer sessions that by that time had gone on for seven hours.  But they believed me that this was happening.  They asked her questions that she did get correct like who is the President and shed say Bush.  Silly questions that I thought maybe some other 15 year old wouldnt know.  I thought their questions were rather stupid and wanting to scream out, Why dont you ask her what happened in her life today!!  But they took this seriously.
/n
/n
We laid back down and watched TV for a split second.  I decided to call the 18 year old girl, Amanda, from the hospital to ask her to tell me the truth about what happened.  She said she didnt know and thought she had diabetes or something.  I told her EVERYTHING my daughter was going through.  I said it was life or death.  I said they were calling in other doctors and maybe a neurologist and that I wouldnt tell anyone, but to please tell me what they did.  She said nothing.
/n
/n
Sarina: Does Benji know Im here?  
/n
Mom: Yes, but daddys on call and is at home with Sierra. (He had yet to be informed that shed lost her mind and the phone was busy because the 18 year old little liar was on the phone checking on her)
/n
Sarina: Does daddy and Sierra know Im here? 
/n
Mom: I just told you they didnt.
/n
Sarina: I didnt remember that. (laughed) What day is it?
/n
Mom: Thursday.  Ive got a job interview in the morning.  Remember?
/n
Sarina: No, I mean what day is it?
/n
Mom: October 13th, well, now the 14th
/n
Sarina: What time is it?
/n
Mom: One A.M.
/n
Sarina: Does Benji know Im here?
/n
Mom: No, his phone is disconnected.
/n
Sarina: What day is it?
/n
Mom: Thursday, Oct 13th.
/n
Sarina: What time is it? (Laughed)
/n
/n
Mom: One A.M.
/n
Sarina: Does Benji know Im here? (Laughed)
/n
Mom: No
/n
Sarina: Oh no! Im on my period and I havent changed! (Kept looking at her crotch when the doctor was in there a minute ago and I asked if something was wrong but we got interrupted)
/n
Mom: Its okay.  You just changed your tampon.
/n
Sarina: I did? I dont remember that.  Does Benji know Im here?
/n
Mom: No
/n
Sarina: How long have I been out of school? (Laughed and smiled like she knew she was asking questions over and over again but realized it only after the question escaped her mouth again.)
/n
Mom: You havent been out of school.  You went to school today but then went over to Amandas house.
/n
Sarina: I went to Amandas house?
/n
Mom: Yes to spend the night.
/n
/n
Sarina: Whos shirt is this?  It looks like Saras.  Why am I wearing Saras shirt?
/n
Mom: Its Amandas.  Your shirt got wet.
/n
Sarina: Mom, I just had a dream.
/n
Mom: What was your dream?
/n
Sarina: Nah, nevermind.
/n
Mom: What was it?
/n
Sarina: I dreamt that I was asking if Benji knew I was here and a bunch of other questions.
/n
Mom: Honey, you did ask a bunch of questions.  All night youve been asking a bunch of questions but you cant remember anything.  Im tired.  Can we stop talking now?
/n
Sarina: Okay.
/n
/n
Mind you readers that this was more like 20 to 30 sets of questions repeated constantly without interruption unless the doctors came in.
/n
/n
The original male nurse came in again and sat down very concerned. He talked about how all the test didnt show anything but he got to thinking about Sarina really hard.  (Hes our neighbor and his girl goes to school with mine).  He said there was only two things he could think of that wouldnt show up on these test and one was ecstacy and the other huffing gasoline.
/n
/n
I freaked out! Oh my God! I just realized that I smelled a very strong gasoline smell in that trailer.  I also smelled a very powerful ether type of smell on Sarinas breath in the emergency room when I held her close and she said she was scared and didnt remember anything.
/n
/n
Mom: Sarina! Sit up.  Hurry! Did you huff gasoline tonight with Amanda?
/n
Sarina: I dont know.  Amanda?
/n
Mom: I knew I smelled something.  Is that what you did?
/n
/n
Sarina just didnt remember anything.  I ran to the phone and called Amanda.  I told her thats what we thought and that I smelled that.  She denied it again.
/n
/n
We were moved from the emergency area to the third floor.  I had to repeat every situation, the whole story, play act, repeat the questions and answers to at least three more people, not to mention Amanda on the phone.  I was so exhausted.  Sarina was so tired now.  She didnt want anything to eat or drink and just wanted to lay down.  We had been there now for eight hours.
/n
/n
It took the hospital another two hours to get me a cot to lie down in.  I was tempted to go into the bathtub and lay there except I couldnt find a blanket, so I laid on her bed at her feet after calling home.  My husband relieved me in the morning to go home and get some sleep before my interview.  He was on call from the hospital where he works and called in that he wouldnt make it and asked if someone else could take his call.  Ive been a stay at home mom for two years and it was the perfect time, when Sarina had matured enough to babysit and I could go back to work.  I had an interview with our local TV station as their accountant.  I really wanted that job and may still get it.  The interview went well on three hours of sleep.  I hadnt cried yet and had remained strong until the end.  Then I broke down.  I would have stayed with my daughter but all of the money Im making is going toward her college and darn if I was going to let Amanda ruin me from getting Sarina to college.  I knew she was in Gods hands and my husband works in surgery and Sarina was thinking fairly straight after two more hours in her new bed.  I couldnt sleep but knew I had to for my familys sake.  The bank account had been in the red and I knew that everything was going to be okay.
/n
/n
Before leaving or calling my husband, Sarina was remembering quite a bit. I said I was going to call daddy to come in for me and that I was leaving.  This was the final conversation:
/n
/n
Sarina: Mom? Dont you think Ive learned my lesson?
/n
Mom: What lesson?
/n
Sarina: About what I did.
/n
Mom: Why, what did you do?
/n
Sarina: You know.  Why else do you think Im here?
/n
Mom: Why are you here?
/n
Sarina: For huffing Gasoline.
/n
Mom: No, Sarina.  Youve been reliving the past five minutes of your life all night long and youve just heard me and the doctors talking about that and youre just repeating that.
/n
Sarina: No mom.  Thats what I did.
/n
Mom: You did?  You huffed gasoline?
/n
Sarina: Yes.
/n
Mom: Then lets call Amanda and have her tell me that.
/n
Sarina: No, dont call her.  Shes got school in the morning.
/n
/n
Mom: I dont care.  Shes lied to us.  This is your life and if this is true we need to know and have to hear it from her because your heads been messed up and I have to make sure.
/n
Sarina: Okay
/n
I dialed and gave the phone to Sarina saying, Just tell her to tell me what happened tonight and to tell the truth.'
/n
Sarina to Amanda: Hey, tell my mom what we did today. She doesnt believe me.  
/n
Amanda must have said, You mean the gas?
/n
Sarina: Yeah.  Just tell her please.  She wont tell anyone.  Mom, tell her you wont tell anyone.
/n
Mom: I wont tell anyone!!! I just want to know what happened!!
/n
Amanda saying into phone while it left Sarinas hand and was at my ear, ...probation and cant, have to watch my three year old brother...
/n
/n
Mom: Hello, this is Tina, Sarinas mom, what did you do today?
/n
Amanda: We huffed gas.
/n
Mom: You huffed gas.
/n
Amanda: Yes.  This is what I do but I cant tell anyone.
/n
Mom: You do know that Ive told you everything Sarinas been through and you never told me this and you could have caused her to die and you still didnt tell me?  You do know that you cannot be friends with Sarina anymore, dont you?
/n
Amanda: Yeah, I kind of figured that.
/n
Mom: Okay.  Thank you.  Bye
/n
/n
I dont know why I thanked her.  It must be my upbringing.
/n
/n
I left to tell the nurses.  I pondered this.  I was mad.  I was lied to.  Shes an adult.  My child is 15 and never did anything before this.  The drug tests proved it at least over however long it would take to get drugs out of a system.  Shes never been anywhere where she even had the chance!  This girl was an adult that we interrogated and voiced concerns and told her she was responsible and that we trusted her.  She put that gas can in front of my child!  My child found a new friend, an older friend, a cool friend, one that she could live in a more grown up world with, and she followed after her.
/n
/n
I called my husband to tell him what Sarina said she did.  He said Amanda called concerned and still pretended with the diabetes.  I asked the head nurse about prosecuting this girl because I remembered there was another 15 year old girl in that house that night. I remembered she was watching her 3 year old brother.  I know it took three days of befriending Sarina to get Sarina into the hospital.  This could happen to anyone.  It could happen to Amanda! What should I do?  How can I make this situation worse on the kids to teach them something?  I couldnt just leave it like this not telling anyone!  Look at the bills were faced with!!  Look at the damage done to my childs brain and other organs!  Look at how we were lied to!
/n
/n
Then I heard the nurses stories about others who died from this or got stuck permanently into a three minute time warp never to come out.  I found out Sarina couldnt get her drivers license for a year unless she was seizure free.  I heard that she may have to take Dilatin for years to come.  I heard that she has to now see a pediatrician and shes never even had a doctor before this.  
/n
/n
God put something in my path right when I was telling myself, No, Im not going to go up there.  Ill just call.  Im going to let Sarina know we trust her.  God put something in front of me that I cannot disclose here where I found out that Sarina lied to us about another little girl she stayed with.  Immediately I said, No way.  Shes not going to stay up there without supervision.  My husband agreed.  Sarina had been bad and lied to us about a friend that we didnt think did bad things.  I would go get her and let her know she had to be honest with us.  If God hadnt put in my face facts about another girl at that exact moment, my daughter would have lived through her situation never to tell me and do it again and could have died the next time.  I walked into the house and found this situation.
/n
/n
The hospital called in the Sheriff for me - who never came and I went down to see after my interview was over with.  We wait until Monday to see what the D.A. has to say.  Its likely that Sarina will also be charged and I told the deputy that I didnt care what the costs were or if my own daughter ended up with a probation officer.  If anything, it would tell the kids at So-and-so high school not to mess with Sarina because her mother is crazy!!  Ive learned around here in Tennessee that these hillbilly parents who live here let their daughters run loose and get knocked up and on drugs wouldnt give a crap about my daughters life being in jeopardy like this and the lives would go on and danger would be brought to others.  Nobody would pay except for Sarina who now could possibly have some brain damage and future seizures.  She got four As in school this semester and she loves math!!  Shes beautiful and wants to be a doctor or nurse or Veterinarian.  Can she now??  We can only pray.
/n
/n
Today I spent all day warning the parents of the other two.  I watched more lies and one parent get really mad.  I heard horror stories from Amandas neighbors about Amanda.  I heard truths and I heard lies.  Ive read articles and web pages.  
/n
/n
I took my little girl out to dinner the next night for some normalcy.  Shes still dazed and still cannot eat.  She knows we love her.  She knows were disappointed. She knows she was trusted.  She knows she could have died.  (I heard her on the phone telling a friend she could have.)  She still asks me to repeat stories and is trying her best to fill in her evening and cannot remember even being at school that day.  She says she wont do it again because why do it if you cant remember.  We do not believe she wont try something else and she hasnt even come close to saying shell never do anything like this again.  She just simply is dazed and doesnt know what to think of it all and is probably wondering if this is a good escape from reality.  We can only pray that she doesnt think like that.  She doesnt seem to care too much about life and is a ho-hum kind of girl but is smart and bright, but lonely, brought on by herself, and could have many friends if she would have more self-esteem.  Shes fragile.  Seems suicidal sometimes, but she chooses nice clean geeky type of friends who are sweet and innocent and still play like little kids....until Thursday trying to gain a grown up friend by doing such a dumb dumb thing.
/n
/n
Please tell others it took my daughter one good time to land her into a state of confusion and brain damage that she easily could have remained in for the rest of her life.  Please tell others to warn parents if you know their kids are hanging around with people who do drugs and inhalants.  Please do not put your parents through this.  Please stop letting kids over 13 spend nights with each other.  Thats a sex and drug age and most parents just dont care to watch out for your kids or their own.  Please remember, we have no real friends, only families who will love us and hang in there through thick and thin.  Dont trust anyone that things arent dangerous.  And if you know that, please dont do it.
/n
/n
Please pray for my two daughters.</bodytext></report>