<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>47835</idnum><title>Odd Feelings of Happiness</title><author>pissed jacker butter</author><substance>hydrocodone</substance><bodytext>


Lets start with some background info I'm a small dude long hair very skinny... Bipolar depressed and 14 yrs old... So my father has been passing kidney stones and was prescribed hydrocodone... So I took a pill to relax (I was pissed from a breakup earlier that day). Now I dont really do drugs just pot... Looooots of pot but not lately... After about 15 mins. I thought I would have been feeling sumthing but I wasnt... So I took another pill... About a half hour later I felt strange (like floating) I felt invincible like an ogre or sumthing... I was reading about sleepy grass and wanted to check it out so I went outside and found some (I live in new mexico) I found some and looked it up on the net to make sure... I was right I made some tea with it and drank a glass...
/n
/n
By this time I was fucked up I was running around just to run (odd) I jumped off my house and didnt feel a damn thing. After about 10 minutes I was on the internet and I was pretty much trippin out the computer was spinning almost like the exorcist or sum shit. It started to rotate to the left and I couldnt figure out why. I hit the computer and told it to shut the hell up... It didnt work I was fucked up
/n
/n
I decided to get some food to chill out a bit as I got up my body felt like jelly I felt like was gonna melt and boil on the floor. The phone rang about 30 seconds after I got up...I thought people were screaming at me. (very strange feeling) after I got some food I went to lay down in my room. As I watched tv I felt a great euphoria take over I felt like I was floating on my bed I liked it too. As I was watching cartoons I felt like being in one too.
/n
/n
After a while I chilled out and had control over myself
/n
/n
Long story short: I got fucked up and u can try it if u want
/n
/n
Peace out and dont do any tripped out shit that I would</bodytext></report>