<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>48547</idnum><title>Will it do the Job??</title><author>Ringen aka g00se</author><substance>alcohol</substance><substance>aet</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


I was sitting at home, drinking som Cognac and playing socialgames, on the net.
/n
I decided to take just half the pill i had, coz of the drinking i've been doing. Swalloved half (50mg) the pill AET, playing psycedelic music wich a love! Been drinking about 6-7 shots(4cl  peice) of 40% Cognac. 
/n
/n
10minutes nothing.. 
/n
15minutes something..
/n
20minutes having thoughts about yesterdays DXM trip... 
/n
/n
That DXm did really give me a brainjob, but today (about 20hours later) it's really no hangover from that. Dxm is not something i recommend, it's just too hard(nervotoxic) as it is.   
/n
/n
less then 25 min has gone by. Feeling a MDMA effect in my brain, euforia, wanna dance, 
/n
not as nice as MDMA, but kinda like Methylone but a better high feeling . 
/n
/n
35min, cant keep the rest of happiness waiting, I drop the rest another 50mg.... 
/n
/n
I'm sitting with my computer, listening, changing tunes, digging with my legs and body.. no sound hallusinogenic yet, just an ok feeling on/in top of my head.
/n
/n
60 minutes.. feeling fine soft, wanna chat with others, (chatting). No enhanching just enyoing it.. I'ts  a gentle feeling trouhg my system that passes, no max just middle all over... great party drug(with alc) if u ask me.. not to much and none the less..
/n
/n
Now 1hour n 45mins it's no bettre than when 45mins had gone by. Kinda soft .. but not much.. a filling feeling all over.
/n
/n
3 hours.. feeling fine.. a bit wasted, a slow comedown...
/n
Feeling is like a fever, warmth.. feeling sleepy.. no pain , just tired n used.. 
/n
/n
Well it's  surely working and it's pretty nice, if compared to E and Methylone, not at all the comedown of E and methylone, but then again not as nice. Sure i'll give it:
/n
For mental use a 6/10, for party use also a 6/10.</bodytext></report>