<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>50718</idnum><title>Preliminary Reconnaisance</title><author>Gazza</author><substance>cacti</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Subjects condition:
/n
/n
Subject 1: Took it very easy on the beer and smokes last night so relatively good. Slightly 'just got up' feeling if anything.
/n
/n
Subject 2: Mild Headache and slightly unsettled stomach.
/n
/n
Time - 13:00
/n
/n
T+0mins
/n
/n
Weve just measured out 25gms each of Peruvian Torch powder. It looks like a lot of powder to eat Were going to try taking spoonfuls then chasing with water/blackcurrant squash. 
/n
/n
T+30mins
/n
/n
After a failed attempt at consuming teaspoons full of the powder, the biggest problem with which was avoidance of inhalation of the fine dust, subject 2 hit upon the idea of form the powder into a paste, then consuming small amounts of the paste followed by water. This method was successful. So far. We now await a sign.
/n
/n
T+1hr 30mins
/n
/n
Both subjects report feeling slightly altered. Vision slightly altered though nothing definitive. Confident that the initial effects are being felt. Stomach feeling a little uncomfortable though nothing unbearable. More waves of suggestion whilst writing this.
/n
/n
T+2hr 10mins
/n
/n
Both in good spirits though no significant progress. I feel some MDMA like effects  constant grin (especially when watching Bill Hicks), nervous excitement, the yawns.
/n
/n
T+2hr 55mins
/n
/n
No change  Slight MDMA like effects thought nothing spectacular. Going for a walk to the shops.
/n
/n
T+3hrs 30min
/n
/n
Pleasant walk on a beautifully bright winters day. Slightly heightened awareness of colours and happily content with life.
/n
/n
T+5hrs
/n
/n
Both feeling minor buzz but not tripping per se. Having a joint to see what happens. All cool though and still enjoying the day.
/n
/n
T+15hrs 20mins
/n
/n
Going to bed now after a fair few joints, and a few beers. Still quite up but dont want to have to write off tomorrow totally. All in all a very pleasant day, akin to taking  an MDMA pill which lasts for 15 hours (pretty cool!). Will try upping the dose to 40  50 gms next time.</bodytext></report>