<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>54091</idnum><title>The Inner Adventure</title><author>Revolvmg</author><substance>hbw</substance><substance>coffee</substance><substance>ginger</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>General</tag><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


Previous experience: Loads of alcohol &amp; cannabis
/n
/n
/n
The very first time I took HBWR seeds, I wanted to avoid the nausea.
/n
I didn't eat for 6-7 hours. I removed the light-brownish husks with
/n
nails and a knife. I chew 4 seeds for 15 minutes and then I spitted
/n
everything out. It didn't work so well. In one particular moment I
/n
felt like I was totally numb and later on I felt like I was going
/n
to fell asleep. I also smoked some hashish because I didn't really
/n
believe the seeds we're working. And while I was doing this I drank
/n
couple of beers. I usually drink &amp; smoke alot, but this time I was
/n
so tired after all this shit I just wanted to get some sleep. I
/n
can't truly tell if I was intoxicated by the seeds or not.
/n
/n
The next morning, I prepared for the nausea. First I removed once
/n
again carefully the light-brownish husks from the seeds. Then I
/n
ground up 6 seeds in 3 different cups, each holding 2 seeds.
/n
I boiled some mineral water, let it cool down to 60 celsius and
/n
added that into every cup. I waited for 2-3 hours for the mixtures
/n
to cool down into room temperature. I also didn't eat anything for
/n
4 hours. Just 10 minutes before I started to ingest the actual
/n
mixture, I ate a teaspoonfull of ginger. Some people claim it
/n
helps avoiding the nausea. The taste of ginger is not so pleasant.
/n
It burns all the way down my throat and into my stomach.
/n
/n
After the 'ginger hell' I drank 2 cups of my mixture, so I had
/n
ingested total of 4 seeds. After 15-20 minutes, I started to feel
/n
light-headed. I had to resist the vomiting. Ginger was still burning
/n
and the seeds really did make me wanna throw up. I knew I had to.
/n
Still, I resisted. It was quite difficult to relax or to walk, I
/n
felt like I was a bit drunk and I wanted to vomit. I decided to wait
/n
for 60 minutes, and then I would throw up if I had to. Right after
/n
this I realized, I could control my feelings quite well. I could
/n
sing along with some piece of music and forget the urge for vomiting.
/n
I believed I could control these kind of feelings, I believed it was
/n
all in my head. I carefully chose good songs to make me feel better.
/n
And it did. I also did some things I really like, playing guitar,
/n
singing &amp; such. All these things made me feel even better. Then
/n
suddenly, I remembered last night, and I recalled I had feelings
/n
quite like this, and I enjoyed it.
/n
/n
The only downside, besides the urge for vomiting, was the feeling
/n
of drowsyness... I even made some coffee just to keep me awake.
/n
Then I wanted to drink the last cup of 2 seeds mixture I made earlier.
/n
I drank it and went to see my friend. I still felt like I was only a bit
/n
drunk. When I reached my friends residence, we watched a video and smoked
/n
some cannabis. I told my friend what I had done and he didn't seem to care,
/n
I felt like I had no-one to tell this.
/n
/n
Then, from out of nowhere, appeared a new world in front of me.
/n
I started to realize things from a totally new perspective.
/n
I knew I had to leave immediately. The information that kept
/n
coming from things I did there was too much. I told my friend
/n
I couldn't concentrate for what we we're doing because I was
/n
somewhere else, doing something else. And then I left.
/n
/n
When I was walking back home, I saw a group of people who were
/n
sitting in a bar nearby. They all arose and left the bar as soon
/n
as I walked by. At first, I thought to myself, am I that horrible?
/n
Then I realized they split up because they were going somewhere else.
/n
It was the relief of my life. And as I continued walking back home,
/n
I saw some elderly people as well, they looked at me and I swear,
/n
I knew exactly what they were thinking. So I reacted differently,
/n
and I saw how it affected them. I believed I could control this
/n
situation. It was all just a matter of understanding gestures.
/n
And those gestures had always been there for me. But only now, I could
/n
understand those gestures so well that I could control the situation.
/n
I was quite polite and I enjoyed it. And it made me feel good too.
/n
/n
When I got back home, I saw my entire life like a book. It was all
/n
there. I just never realized it, because it didn't have any meaning.
/n
By looking any object I own, I saw where it had come from, why it
/n
was there, why I liked it and why I chose to keep it. I remembered
/n
all the things it had been through, where was it made, who had played
/n
with it and so on... In my everyday life, I pass by many things
/n
I have gathered throughout my years of existence like it didn't
/n
mean anything to me. Well it does. I just never stop there to
/n
see and understand the meaning of it all. But this time I could see.
/n
I was so overwhelmingly happy of all the objects I had received from
/n
thousands of different sources it made me smile. It made me cherish
/n
life itself.
/n
/n
Then I got an another idea. I wanted to record a video of myself
/n
thinking these kinds of things. In case I would forget how happy I was.
/n
It was a difficult task. I had to remind myself of what I was doing
/n
for every 5 seconds. I just saw the camera and I remembered every little
/n
recording the camera had ever recorded and every little detail of the
/n
camera made me remember where it was damaged and so on... When I finally
/n
managed to assemble it, I started recording. It was impossible to speak
/n
those things which were inside my head. It was all too much. When I
/n
opened my mouth and said something, my mouth froze and I was left
/n
speechless, dreaming. Every sentence I started, ended prematurely as
/n
my mind drifted away with the memories I encountered everywhere I gazed
/n
upon. This is when I decided not to record anymore.
/n
/n
I went to my bed to lie down and enjoy. I have no idea how long I was
/n
there, since time had no meaning at all. Or at least, I didn't care.
/n
The rest of my trip I embraced life and tried to focus my thoughts
/n
to gain understanding of life. And I did understand. The trip
/n
was over in about 6 hours or so, and I started to feel the after
/n
effects. I called my friend to come see me and apologized why
/n
I was so rude earlier. He said he understanded why I did it, and
/n
I understanded it too. We smoked some pot, watched some videos and
/n
had a great time. Afterwards we just fell asleep.
/n
/n
/n
Conclusion:
/n
At the first time, I didn't take enough seeds and my technique was
/n
totally incorrect. The next time I drank the seed mixtures I was
/n
successful and had just the right amount. I had some slight visuals
/n
too, not worth mentioning though. The inner adventure I had was so
/n
much more. I still feel happy about my journey, and I believe my
/n
journey was successful because my timing was right. My life was so
/n
perfect at the time it reflected my trip very pleasantly. Also I would
/n
like to point out the side-effects I had, the terrible nausea at first
/n
and the hangover which included 'foggy' mind, thirst and numb legs.
/n
Still, it was the price to pay and I will certainly do this again.</bodytext></report>