<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>546</idnum><title>Fond Memories</title><author>Empster</author><substance>inhalants</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
I have worked in computer shops...tech work..for quite a long time now..and it's a common thing to keep a case or 2 of this stuff on hand.  
/n
/n
When i first started using it, I would get a somewhat nitrous-like experience...distorted sounds, little visuals (i'll let it be known i've not done much nitrous, just a few balloons at concerts etc., so I may not be relating this very well).
/n
/n
OOOH BOY did things start to change.  I mean, I've done shrooms, lsd, all that, but OOOOH BOY
/n
/n
The first sign was a tightening around the temples..and my eyeglasses would seem to move further from my point of view. Things would start to look familiar, but VERY different.
/n
/n
Soon I met ZEB..a quick little 4' mischevious dude, always just running around a corner, and with a devilish laugh that i can still hear.  How did i know his name?  These creatures, they tend to repeat words or phrases in an echoey sort of manner.  Zebzebzebzebzeb..etc.  I remember chasing him around the small office several laps (thank god nobody was there), before saying to myself..ITS NOT REAL.  is it?
/n
/n
He never meant harm, but I swear he wanted to drive me crazy.
/n
/n
Keep in mind, it wasn't during every session that i would trip this hard, but it came in spurts, usually while i was alone, with some sort of background sounds, tv, radio, other voices.
/n
/n
There were others:
/n
/n
Blah : somewhat of an ogre, dimwitted but scary, liked to sing along with van halen
/n
/n
Little green fairies:  when they spoke i was overcome with a sense of joy, peace.  very sentimental to me.  they lived among the empty cans.
/n
/n
The little old lady:  wanted a beer, so did i, but it was working time ;(
/n
/n
The seductress:  always came up behind me..humming softly, soothingly, while I sat or stood facing a wall.  When her mouth came close to my ear and her arms encircled me was the best, and as the buzz wore off she would slip away.  Never got a good look, but long hair, very slight, loving.
/n
/n
I could go on forever here
/n
/n
The sunbeam forcefield, shocked me when i tried to cross it.
/n
/n
Occasional fear of just having swallowed metal shavings
/n
/n
Time frame of buzz : not long, 30sec to maybe 2.5 min..but intense(duh)
/n
/n
I would really love to hear from anyone with a similar experience, I don't do this any longer for fear of damage, but it is really a fond memory..I do not regret it in any way.
/n
/n
This was true hallucination to me, not distortion of reality, but the real thing.  
/n
/n
Had a major trip listening to 'my woman from tokyo' during the funky solo part..tick tock tick tock, everything started moving like a pendulum, too sweet.</bodytext></report>