<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>5614</idnum><title>Detached From Everything Around Me</title><author>K2D</author><substance>opium</substance><bodytext>



First off, a little background information.  I am very active in sports teams, so my usage of drugs or alchohol is very limited.  I don't want to get caught doing something that would jeopardize my spot on the team.  I only drink occasionally and i smoke weed once in a great while. Usually only about once every 4 - 5 months.  The only other drug i've used is MDMA. (only used once)
/n
/n
Last night I was out with my friends and we ended up smoking weed.  We sat around for a few hours after that until another guy came over. He had opium, so we all decided to smoke it.  I'd never done it before so i was kind of excited.  I smoked 2 bowls and just kind of sat around.  After a few minutes, everythign seemed to get really quiet and calm.  My ears were really sensitive to things and it was just like in the movies.
/n
/n
Everything seemed to be happening all at once. I could listen to one person talk but still be listening to the people 10 feet away's conversation. We were in a garage so everything kind of echoed. That was interesting to hear. I had a really limited attention span, where i would ask someone a question and while they were explaining it i would zone out and not really hear what they were saying.
/n
/n
I would still appear to be listening and i would make comments but i didnt really hear them talk. I just kind of stared at them while i was focusing on something else.  It's hard to explain.  During this whole fiasco, i felt like i was watching everything happen from a small window up in the corner of the room.  I was very detached from everythign around me.  My hands and arms seemed to be tingly and i kept rubbing them.  (Maybe it was just because i was nervous)  My memory was pretty shot.  It was hard to have a converstaion. I would be talking about one thing while listening to the conversation behind me and forget what i was talking about. I was pretty happy and was hugging a lot of people.  It was really easy to act normal if you were sitting down.  While standing, i felt like i was kind of drunk in my movements.
/n
/n
Overall it felt like i had a high like from weed but way mellower.  The high lasted only a few hours and i was able to go home and talk to my parents 3 hours after taking it. My friends were ok to drive also.  Its hard to describe.  But today, the day after, I have had no side effects.  I'm just pretty tired but no more than what i would usually have had from weed.</bodytext></report>