<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>56658</idnum><title>The System Cleaner </title><author>Enigma</author><substance>kratom</substance><tag>First Times</tag><tag>Difficult Experiences</tag><bodytext>


I write this, about 20 minutes after a terrible end,...
/n
/n
I got the Kratom on advice from the seller at the local SmartShop.
/n
/n
I asked for a relaxing tea, I had bought and tried Passionflower tea about 6 weeks earlier, but I just added hot water rather then boiling it, so it was just a very relaxing, but nasty tasting tea.
/n
/n
He said he didn't have anything really tea like, only brew things.
/n
/n
But, he said, he had something he uses himself when he needs a nice calm.
/n
/n
He showed me a 10 gram pack of Kratom, explaining that he takes 5 gram mixed with yoghurt in the evening.
/n
/n
I already read about Kratom, and knew it had nauseating side-effects, so I asked whether there were any bad or strange side effects, besides the calming down.
/n
/n
Where he replied there were none.
/n
/n
I trusted him, thinking 5 grams of a 10 gram, which should be the full dose, is a light dose and probably just relaxing, like the Passion Tea.
/n
/n
I got time to try it with yoghurt that friday evening.
/n
/n
But it totally failed, it tasted so bad I couldn't get in more then 3 small spoons of it.
/n
/n
The next week, now that is.
/n
/n
I decided to try it with some juice, as described on the website of the store, and other places.
/n
/n
T+0:00
/n
I had put the remaining 5 grams in a large glass and filled it up with chocolate milk, at first the powder floated on top.
/n
/n
But after stirring a lot and waiting, it settled through the chocolate milk and became drinkable.
/n
/n
It had a bit of a bad taste but not super awful.
/n
/n
/n
T+0:10
/n
When I had finished drinking it up, I looked through some music and made a relaxing playlist to chill on.
/n
/n
T+0:30
/n
I lay down in bed, my hands were cold from working behind my computer, so I warmed them up.
/n
/n
After my hands were warm, I relaxed, closed my eyes and felt sleepy, I was relaxed and tired, even without the Kratom.
/n
/n
All that comes now could as well 've been placebo,... very likely actually.
/n
/n
T+0:45
/n
With my eyes closed, I was very able to visualize lots and lots of imaginative things, pictures, moving to the music.
/n
/n
I usually do this anyways, but it went extra good, seen I was very relaxed.
/n
/n
T+1:00
/n
It got boring after a while, opened my eyes, looked at my video arcade cabinet and decided I wanted the music from there, as well as the winamp visuals displaying in the screen.
/n
/n
I got out of bed, a bit wobbly in my legs, probably placebo, I had this with Passion Flower tea too, but not with mushrooms.
/n
/n
Started opening the cabinet and working on it.
/n
/n
T+2:00
/n
As I was messing with getting stuff installed, I felt a nausea coming up.
/n
/n
I sat down and I started moving my leg neurotically, it made the nauseous feel go away, but it didn't make me feel any better.
/n
/n
My mood wasn't really relaxed, my hands were shaking and I knew it was going kind of wrong.
/n
/n
Was just a matter of waiting till it went away, then go to bed or write this experience thing.
/n
/n
T+2:30
/n
I was chatting with a friend in canada on msn, told him about the kratom and that I felt like shit.
/n
/n
I paused my typing and I knew I was gonna throw up, I looked around my room, to decide where to leave my stomach fillings.
/n
/n
The floor was the best place, my garbage bin was full, and I had linoleum, or well, easily cleanable floor covering, so no real problem.
/n
/n
I bended forward from my chair and waited till I actually had to puke, avoiding unnecessary moaning sounds.
/n
/n
After 3 throws I was done, I didn't feel nauseous anymore.
/n
/n
Cleaned up, and talked to the guy on msn again.
/n
/n
Floor is still smelly.
/n
/n
God this sucked, I didn't get any relaxier then the badly prepared Passion Flower tea, it tasted far worse, and I had to throw up.
/n
/n
Not for a retry!
/n
/n
It could've been miscellaneous things that contributed to the nausea, but it's mainly the kratom.
/n
/n
Because I barely throw up,... even if I'm VERY sick, nauseous, dizzy from a boat ride, or bustour that's taking ages, I just have a nasty feeling in my belly, and sit that out for as long as it takes.</bodytext></report>