<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>5869</idnum><title>Mexico Madness</title><author>Rock Star</author><substance>mdma</substance><substance>sildenafil</substance><substance>ghb</substance><bodytext>



It all started at about 7am. I took my first cap of G, and by 9am I had taken 3 caps. I was feeling fuzzy and simlar to being drunk. I had a lot of fun dancing and goofing off with my friends. We were in a condo on the beach in Mexico. I was feeling agressive, but not sexual in any way. We were all on the balcony yelling and people on the beach when we decided to take a  pill of MDMA and 50 mg of Viagra. We took both pills oraly at the same time.
/n
/n
Very quicky I started to feel the Viagra. I could feel the blood rushing through my body, espacially in my hands and head.  I felt like the biggest bad ass ever, and I was on top of the world. The best way to describe it was a very long adrenaline rush. I did not feel horny or sexual in any way. I felt more like a boy. I never really felt the effects of the MDMA, but I didn't really care, I was having the time of my life.
/n
/n
About 10am we decided to go down to the beach and light fireworks. I was then I noticed that my vision was blurred and my depth perception was off. I couldn't focus on an object. We ran, and played on the beach for a very long time. We weren't really looking at our watches, so I don't know what time it was, but I started to feel like I was going to throw up. I just sat down for a few mins. and the feeling pasted. 
/n
/n
We came down around 11am-noon. It didn't really last very long, but it was the most fun I've ever had. It was the last night, or morning, of 3 days of heavy partying so maybe that's why it was so short. We went to bed later that after noon around 4pm. 
/n
/n
I recommend Viagra to everyone. I'm sure the effects on men are much different, but girls have to try this one. I have done MDMA before and this is WAY BETTER!! It's my new drug of choice.</bodytext></report>