<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>5877</idnum><title>Leafy Guy</title><author>dumb00footer</author><substance>salvia</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



 It was only a few days ago and the memory is still clear as day. I had ordered my salvia online and I had gotten it a few days later. A couple days went by and it was the weekend, I was fairly anxious to try it. Two of my friends came over and we hung out until it was pretty late. Then I decided it was time to do it. We had no other means to smoke it other than just a regular pipe. They decided that since I knew a bit more about it than them that I would try it first. I had no idea what to expect because everything I read said it was too hard to explain and that you just had to try it for yourself. I took a few big long breaths to stretch out my lungs so I could get the best hit possible. After I felt ready I lit my lighter and took the biggest longest hit I have ever taken with anything. I held it until I felt a horrible pain in my lungs. When I felt ready again (only a few seconds later), I took another hit, this one ever bigger than the last. 
/n
/n
Right after I took in the smoke I felt something weird come over my body, so I laid back as this incredibly intense full body high took me over. I couldnt believe how incredible it felt. Once I closed my eyes I saw vivid visuals of a spiral. So I got in the spiral and followed all these small particles of things deeper and deeper into the spiral. Soon I was brought to this land were I was a plant being. I had a big flower on my head and my body was entirely covered with leafs. Well I guess my job was to throw stacks of leafs onto a wagon so me and all the other plant guys did this. As soon as it was finished we all got onto the wagon and leafy horses pulled it. Only when I got off the wagon I couldnt move I felt like my roots were being held down. So all my leafy buddys just decided to chill with me where I stood and we talked a bit about the sky. I eventually said good-bye to my new friends as I felt myself leaving and opened my eyes still feeling a little out of it. 
/n
/n
I explained to friends that it was incredible and told them of my story. They both felt fine in taking it then and did so. One friend explained a scene of dancing macaroni and the other felt he was in the sky floating through it and all that he knew was himself, Anything else was just merely a distraction.
/n
/n
I will definitely do this again. I really believe in this plant and would definitely like to gain a deeper understanding of it.</bodytext></report>