<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6410</idnum><title>To look in the eyes of a dead friend.</title><author>A Broken Soul</author><substance>dimenhydrinate</substance><substance>bupropion</substance><bodytext>



Ok... It was me Jonathan my friend Travis and my other friend Corey and we went laser bowling. We were just chillin and we met up wit some people that we know and we eventually got seperated for a couple minutes. After we met back up we all found a place to sit down and decided to take out dramamine b/c we've heard that you can get a pretty straight trip offa it. Well im sure that none of us had in mind what was fixin to change our lives forever. As we were goin out side my friend Corey started to tell us that he felt wierd, and that his stomach hurt.  We thought that it was just the drmammine b/c they can make you sick on an empty stomach. So we just sat down and sparked up a smoke.
/n
/n
Everything was goin ok until my friend started complaining about a lot of muscle pain.  We were freaked out and didnt know what to do and then all of a sudden he went into a seizure.  I tried to stop his shaking and calm him down but he couldnt breath and i couldnt make him stop shaking.  It was violent and he was tearing and scratching me and Travis.  Me and Travis did everything that we could do.  Which was nothin but watch Corey die.  Then somebody came outside and they saw him and i told them to call 911.  Soon after that i was sittin on the table and he was still siezing, and i pulled him onto my lap with Travis on the other side trying to hold his arms.  Then as he started to calm down he look directly into my eyes as i did to him.  He was blue and not breathing, and as quickly as it all started it was over.  His heart had stopped beating. Right there he died in my arms.  I pulled him closer and grasped him as tightly as i could and i heard a breath come out.  I looked back at his face and the color was coming back.  His lips were no longer blue and i think he was lookin arround a little.  Then the paramedics arrived and they gave him oxygen and brought him back to consciousness.  Then they loaded him onto the ambulance and we said bye and i told him that id see him when we got to the hospital.  A cop drove me Travis to the hospital and there we sat for a couple of hours.  Then Corey's parents showed up and i told them the whole story.
/n
/n
We all sat in there for a while before they told us that there were going to take us home.  Now im home and its 6a.m. in the morning, and i never even tripped.  The whole experience sobered us up.  Im goin to the hospital today and see how he is.  As far as i know he is ok and will make a recovery.  This will definitely be the last time that i will have an encounter with nothing like this. I suggest that you dont have a first.</bodytext></report>