<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6490</idnum><title>Xtreme Euphoria</title><author>Fear&amp;Loathing</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>cocaine</substance><substance>hydrocodone</substance><substance>ether</substance><bodytext>



I must say that Dr. Hunter S. Thompson was right when he said: 'There is nothing more helpless and irresponsible than men on the depths of an ether binge.'  My evening began at 7:30 with a large dose of good ether base coke.  I sat undisturbed in my room for several hours enjoying the very powerful feeling of the rich man's drug.  I enjoyed my high until approx. 9:30 when I began to come down.  I usually have some trouble sleeping when I have good coke, so I knew if I timed it right I could smoke some weed covered in 500mg of Hydrocodone and sleep just fine.  Smoking pills produces a very nasty chemical taste and smell for me, but it also produces a strong feeling of numbness in the body and often times I see tracers.  
/n
/n
The clock said it was 10:15 and I realized that I still wasn't tired just very numb and relaxed.  I knew that there was one other thing I could abuse to aide in my deep sleep.  So, I went to my closet and broke open me bottle of 100% raw ether.  I am unsure of my exact dose on the ether but I soaked the rag throughly and huffed for at least 6 or 7 minutes.  When I first huffed the ether it burned my sensetive nose and made a very nasty taste in my mouth.  The one warning I will give over this experience is to be careful with the ether.  After huffing I fell into an xtreme euphoric haze.  I could here the lights of my room buzzing all around me and tiny specs and dots flashed across my eyes.  It was 11:20 and all wanted to do is huff more ether, since I had begun to come down.  Ether is very addictive and can cause permanent damage.  Don't let yourself be weak and allow the drug to control you.  I finally fell asleep at approx. 12:30 and awoke in the morning with a slight headache.</bodytext></report>