<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6523</idnum><title>LSAyahuasca</title><author>Renwick</author><substance>hbw</substance><substance>syrian_rue</substance><bodytext>



After ordering a large number of Hawaiian Baby Woodrose seeds, a friend of mine asked me if he could have seven of the seeds to try. I gave them to him with the promise that he would call me the next day and tell me how they were.The next day my friend called me and told me they didn't work. (Days later found out that he didn't chew the seeds and that was why they didn't work). I proceeded to call another friend and ask if he wanted to try an experiment with me. The experiment I had in mind was consuming 10 Woodrose seeds as well as five grams of Syrian Rue to potentiate the Woodrose seeds and make sure that they would work. My friend agreed, so I picked him up and we went to the park to ingest the seeds. 
/n
/n
After arriving at the park we chewed up and swallowed the seeds. The Woodrose seeds tasted slightly like peanuts and the rue tasted like old coffee grounds. We continued walking around the woods and half an hour later the effects started to kick in. We ran into some kid who had a pipe with him, he looked like he was hiding from someone. My friend and I wandered around for a few more minutes before we agreed that we were getting way too high to be walking around the woods and decided to head back to the car. As if to confirm my suspicions about the boy we saw earlier, the next person we came across was a police  officer. By this time we were very high, but decided we needed to leave anyway due to the presence of the cop.(DISCLAIMER: The author of this report thinks it is a bad idea to drive under the influence of any psychedelic or intoxicant and does NOT suggest that anyone do so.)
/n
/n
The drive home was crazy. Trees melted into the road,  colors changed and altered in intensity, and an incredible   nausea was growing in each of us. We arrived back at my friend's house and sat down on his couch. I was growing more nauseous by the second and crawled my way to the bathroom to vomit. After vomiting up the entire contents of my stomach and then some, I crawled back to the couch. I was overcome with a strange urge to sleep and could hardly keep my eyes open. This was very different than my previous psychedelic experiences where I felt incredibly stimulated and unable to close my eyes or sleep. 
/n
/n
An overwhelming sense of fear came over me. Thoughts such as 'did I poison myself', 'if I go to sleep will I ever wake up', 'do I have serotonin syndrome', and 'am I going insane' all crept through my mind. I began freaking out more than I ever had before. I wondered if there was some reason I had never heard of anyone doing this combination of drugs before. I tried to use the computer to search for answers but it was impossible. 
/n
/n
My friend tried to calm me down but eventually I just accepted my 'inevitable death' and laid down on my friend's bed. A few minutes later I was happy to realize that I couldn't sleep at all and was afraid for no reason. 
/n
/n
The visuals were very different from the neon visuals of LSD or the sea green and earthy colors of mushrooms. I watched the colors form before my eyes mostly in shades of red, gray, and blue, with a small amount of yellow. After a while my friend came in the room along with another friend of mine who was there to drive me back to my place where I'd feel safer. The first friend said he would meet us there in a few minutes when he could get a ride with some of our other friends. I happily ran to the car and drove off with the other friend. The car ride was semi-hectic because my friend drives pretty fast and we passed several cops, one of which looked like he was following us. 
/n
/n
We arrived at my place only to find that my brother was there and needed the insurance card for my other car because he had gotten pulled over while driving it. I had to dig through my wallet for this card while tripping so hard I couldn't read anything, which took quite a while. My brother had brought an annoying friend of his over who kept asking me questions about the trip. An hour or so passed and my other friend showed up with some more people, and my brother left. I took out a cigarette and decided it would be a good time for a smoke. All of a sudden I saw my body decaying and growing sick and saw all of the future consequences of my smoking flash before my eyes. I threw my cigarettes in the garbage and never smoked again. I sat on my bed talking to my friends about life, death, and other weird existential things that come to mind while tripping. 
/n
/n
I tried to relax my mind into as much of a meditative state as I could, this was a challenge being as hyper excitable as I was. All of a sudden a strange feeling came over me and I felt as if I had been reborn and now shared some strange bond with all the people there that I still cannot describe accurately. Somehow, I knew that that was exactly how I felt when I was being born. It was an incredibly weird sensation. The rest of the trip consisted of talking with my friends and lying in bed. The next day I felt incredibly shaken and worn out but not bad. 
/n
/n
Over the course of the next months I made many changes in my life. I changed my major in school; I broke up with my girlfriend, and changed in many other more subtle ways.The friend that I tripped with also made many changes to his way of life. Subsequent experiments showed me that Woodrose Seeds cause a lot of nausea by themselves but not nearly as much as when they are taken with the Syrian Rue. Also the Syrian Rue adds a blue color to the hallucinations not normally found with the Woodrose Seeds alone. The significantly higher with the Rue.</bodytext></report>