<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6538</idnum><title>My Body Is Rebelling</title><author>Typhon</author><substance>meth</substance><substance>morphine</substance><substance>methaqualone</substance><bodytext>



It started on a Wed. night after work.  Now I have been using drugs of almost all forms for about 7 years.  I've done 5 day crystal binges before so I knew what to expect when my freind showed up with a whack of ice.  You see I live in a small town presently so it's tough to find good ice.
/n
/n
Meth is everywhere in the larger cities that I lived in.  But in this town I havn't, (until this wed) got any good stuff.  So I bought a few caps.... and snorted about half of one.  It burned like hell, just like the good stuff.  Within minutes I could feel the meth racing through my viens. My leg starting bouncing and I rollarcoaster began.
/n
/n
I snorted that first load at around 2300... I snorted the rest of the first cap between 0200-0300... I was also smoking weed all day... I smoke all the time so it's hard to conieve it as drug use.. but... non-the-less.... around 5 or so in the morning I wanted to chill out a bit so I muched 2 quaaludes.... 
/n
/n
After a bit I was feeling the drunkeness of the barbituates and stil racing strong on the meth... it was quite interested to be so out of control of ones motor skills and yet have the energy to run a marathon.. crazy...
/n
/n
I did not sleep that night at all... just partied all night... drank a bit as well but not too much.. I don't like to drink while on any barbituate especially...  I started to snort some more meth at about noon thursday... to keep it up ya know... snorted anohter cap and a half over the course of the day and evening... 
/n
/n
Stayed up all night again... snorted some more...  you get the idea.. now my body was starting to feel quite poisoned and quite useless... but... anything I'm doing; i'm gonna do it right.... ha..
/n
/n
So... now it's friday... I bought some junk.. Morhpine pills actually... crushed up one and stuck in which a bowl of weed... superb... I've smoked lotsa opium in my day and that's what it most resembles... even tastes alot like it... yummy... so then I freebased some meth... more bumps... you get the idea... I was quite out of it... 
/n
/n
A superb expeience on all fronts... now It is saturday... still havn't slept... and am planning on buying more meth to conitunue my little binge... and I worked every night this week. and still am.. .i work tonight... and am still snortin cyrystal.... good stuff...
/n
/n
I don't think I'll repeat this again soon.. because my body is rebelling... but... I didn't die... so... Definitely fun....
/n
/n  
&lt;BR&gt;
Enjoy
&lt;BR&gt;

&lt;BR&gt;
Typhon  /n
</bodytext></report>