<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6624</idnum><title>Stimulation, Tension, Concentration Affected</title><author>eveningguru</author><substance>amphetamines</substance><substance>caffeine</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Total Water Drank throughout the day:  3,552ml (Every little bit needed.)
/n
/n
6:40am-8:10am  No pronounced heart-rate changes.
/n
/n
8:00am-  200mg Caffeine
/n
/n
8:10am-  Beginning Effects (light mental effects)
/n
/n
8:30am-  36-40 beats/minute
/n
/n
8:50am-  Beginning of pronounced mental and physical effects.
/n
/n
8:50am-12:00pm  Strongest effects prominent.
/n
	-General sense of well-being.
/n
	-Time speeds up.
/n
	-Shaking of legs.
/n
	-Perfectionism (Could just be natural inclinations released, as I usually do not have the drive.)
/n
	-Very strong mental and physical drive to succeed/do well.
/n
	-Focusing power and depth increased, also able to focus on multiple topics.
/n
	-Slight boost to strength and endurance.
/n
	-No hunger from 6:00am-8:10pm
/n
	-Talkative, but not overly so.  Very slight stumbling over words.
/n
	-Am able to find interest in any subject.
/n
	-Very mild dry throat.
/n
	-Extremely clear-headed.
/n
	-No loss of patience no contempt or disgust possible.
/n
/n
9:17am-  64 beats/minute
/n
/n
9:32am-  Able to focus on bodily sensations much more than usual.
/n
/n
9:40am-  60 beats/minute
/n
/n
9:50am-  Very slight light-headedness when moving or standing.
/n
	-Tingling in the back of the head.
/n
/n
10:10am-  Slightly tensed neck muscles.
/n
	-Slight feeling of being flushed. (Not visible)
/n
/n
10:12am-  Tingling moved to neck and top of head also.
/n
/n
10:25am-  Tingling moved to shoulders and mid-back.
/n
/n
10:28am-  All effects increased slightly.
/n
/n
10:30am-  Tingling moved to throat also.
/n
	-Very thirsty, but water doesn't help dry throat.
/n
/n
10:32am-  Tingling moved to face, arms, and lower spine.  
/n
	(More pronounced while standing)
/n
/n
10:34am-  Tingling on the sides of my neck, and lower arms, and hands.
/n
	-Tingling also moving into chest and ribs.
/n
/n
10:35am-  Whole upper body tingling and moving into legs.
/n
/n
10:58am-  Tingling comes and goes like an electric massager.
/n
	-My stomach does feel empty, but there is no hunger associated with it.
/n
	-Heart-rate jumps wildly even at low exertion levels.
/n
/n
11:03am-  Very slight headache gone by 11:27am.
/n
/n
11:16am-  200mg Caffeine
/n
/n
11:32am-  68 beats/minute
/n
/n
11:38am-  Whole body is tingling
/n
	-54 beats/minute
/n
/n
11:44am-  200mg Caffeine
/n
/n
12:00pm-  72 beats/minute
/n
/n
12:11pm-  64 beats/minute
/n
/n
12:13pm-  Whole body is tingling, but I feel flushed, and there is no hunger at all.
/n
/n
12:23pm-  108 beats/minute after brief walk between english and friends at lunch.
/n
/n
12:30pm-  Slight stomach ache.
/n
	-Flushed feeling is gone.
/n
/n
1:00pm-  Being with Carla at lunch and felt more affectionate than usual.
/n
	-90 beats/minute
/n
	-Noticeably higher sexual drive.
/n
/n
1:15pm-  Effects still strong, but plateaued.  
/n
	-Still tingling at touch.
/n
	-Mild sweating, due to raised body temperature.
/n
/n
1:22pm-  Concentration, and drive effects still strong.
/n
	-The elated, almost giddy feelings are completely gone.
/n
	-Face tingling like crazy.
/n
/n
1:27pm-  Neck muscles very tense.
/n
/n
1:31pm-  Very light difficulty swallowing due to tight throat muscles.
/n
/n
1:35pm-  66 beats/minute
/n
/n
1:55pm-  Mild light-headedness after short exertion.
/n
/n
2:28pm-  Fast heart rate (unmeasured guessing around 60-70 beats/minute.)
/n
	-Mild sweating continues, still due to raised body temperature.
/n
	-Mental effects still strong, though they are beginning to taper off.
/n
/n
/n
3:19pm-  Increase in muscle tension.  (Shoulders, neck, back.)
/n
	-Mental effects tapering slightly more, though still noticeable.
/n
	-Significantly less tingling.
/n
/n
3:00pm-  Drastic drop in body temperature.
/n
/n
3:26pm-  100 beats/minute
/n
	-Significantly less drive.  (Only when compared with peak.)
/n
	-Significantly less ability to concentrate.
/n
/n
4:00pm-  Slight feeling of being hungry, but much less than would be expected.
/n
	-Feelings of being tired, strung-out, and shitty.
/n
	        (Come and go every ten or fifteen minutes.)
/n
	-Zero sex drive
/n
	-Easier to begin work due to momentum from the day, however 		    concentration and drive are no better than normal.
/n
	-Tingling almost completely gone.
/n
	-Neck muscles more tense than previously.
/n
/n
4:35pm-  72 beats/minute
/n
/n
5:19pm-  All mental effects have worn off.
/n
	-Very tense, and stressed.
/n
	-Standing up even slowly makes me very dizzy.
/n
	-My throat is slightly drier than previously.
/n
/n
6:27pm-  Took four Bayer to combat extreme muscle tension.
/n
	-Carla gave me a back massage which helped significantly.
/n
	-Drank glass of orange juice to boost blood sugar.  (Having not eaten.)
/n
	-Another back massage, and most negative effects have gone.
/n
	(Note: Had I not previously had problems with depression I would 	 have thought that I was feeling very depressed or shitty.  However, I was able to recognize it as mostly low blood sugar level, and stress.)
/n
/n
7:26pm-  Tension only in wrists and forearms.
/n
	-Still very small appetite.
/n
	-Taking nap.
/n
	-Took another two Bayer.
/n
/n
7:50pm-  Finished nap took a wonderful feeling hot shower.  (Very refreshing.)
/n
/n
8:10pm-  Hunger hits in full force.
/n
	-Still a little drained, but otherwise normal.
/n
/n
The one thing I learned from this experience, is less caffeine.  Also, I wouldn't want to use this drug/combination recreationally.  It could very well have its uses depending on the situation though.  Last minute studying, finals, or some other equally valuable use.  I would suggest for most people to use much less caffeine than I did.  The only reason I used so much is I am a heavy coffee drinker, and have a huge tolerance.</bodytext></report>