<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6638</idnum><title>More Research Needed on Research Chemical</title><author>Harold and Brandon</author><substance>2ct7</substance><bodytext>



I'm sitting in my room with my friend at T+6:30 on a 25mg oral dose of 2ct7.  I feel poisoned.  That's the only way I can describe my experience.  For the past 5 hours I've felt like this chemical is trying to eat my brain alive.  The constant headache is only a reinforcement that I'm still alive.  After sitting around and waiting for the drug to take affect for 2 hours, we walked around town for an hour or two, grabbing a bite to eat (which was a bit discomforting), and waiting to go to a reggae show.  After walking around for another 2 hours (T+4:00), we made our way to the club.  My headache was bearable, but the body load was still discomforting.  My friend stopped me as we went into the club because he thought he was having a heart-attack.  This set the mood for his 'trip' for the rest of the night.  For the next 4 hours his heart beat was hovering around 120 bpm and he kept having dizzy-spells.  We walked home from the show, which we never really got to see, at around T+5:00.  My friend's heart rate is back to normal now, but we both have bad head aches and body discomfort.  We both agree that we simply feel poisoned and have taken nothing positive from the drug.  Hallucinations were like acid hallucinations for a short peak, but were mostly like weak acid visuals.  Strangley, the change of state mentally was quite different from anything we've experienced.  It is best described as MDMA and LSD at the same time.  Not so much candy flipping though, more like the two chemical effects were combined at once as opposed to the layered feel we get when candy flipping.
/n
/n
Still mild visuals at T+7:00.  WE've both decided that if any further experimentation with this poisonous non-consumable is to take place, we will lower the dosage to ~15mg.
/n
/n
Overall, a negative experience.
/n
/n
~~Note:  Is this kind of 'trip' normal?  From the trip reports we had read here, we were under the impression that a good visual trip was fairly likely.  Then again, it is a research chemical and it does behave differently in people.  We would like to hear more no-trip and weak-trip reports to see if what we experiences is more common than the vaults of erowid led us to believe.</bodytext></report>