<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6758</idnum><title>No-One Dies</title><author>PsillyBoy</author><substance>hbw</substance><tag>Mystical Experiences</tag><bodytext>



There is no need for blind faith when you can experience that in which you believe.
/n
/n
We were to pay the Head a visit; before departing: two of us consumed a brew, carefully prepared a few days earlier:
/n
/n
I had taken 14 Hawaiian Baby Woodrose seeds and crushed them, leaving them to soak in boiled water before straining the liquid through an old t-shirt  Separating the none soluble, stomach-irritating fats, from the water-soluble psychoactive amide  being LSA, the naturally occurring precursor to LSD. Shared the tea with one other person.
/n
/n
I have some experience with the seeds and was expecting to peak in about three hours, to reach a mellow plateau from which I could soak in the surroundings.
/n
/n
An effigy of Buddha meditated on the brew as it brewed.
/n
/n
After a beautiful five mile cycle along the beach, we reach Hengistbury Head. We rise to the top as the sun sets deeper, casting fantastic reds &amp; oranges into our atmosphere. 
/n
/n
The third member of our group ingests roughly 80mg of MDMA.
/n
In a place like the Head you could experience euphoria without ever adding extra chemicals to the swirling pool already you. We decide not to without ever making the decision
/n
/n
One moment rolls on, before our eyes the intense beauty of day morphs to a beauty more subtle.
/n
/n
In the moment.
/n
/n
We lie a top the Head, a mellow plateau, sitting one hundred and eighteen feet above sea level
/n
Upside down, near the edge and all I can see is Sea,
/n
And Sky!
/n
And the curve of the Earth!!
/n
/n
In the moment.
/n
/n
The sky darkens, the wind chills
/n
We cover ourselves in a blanket plenty big enough for three.
/n
/n
In the moment.
/n
/n
The curtains are drawn back and we are allowed to gaze upon the greatest show on Earth,
/n
The Universe
/n
We look out from a point.
/n
We travel.
/n
/n
In the moment.
/n
/n
Three highs become one, then many.
/n
/n
I lose myself in the stars, the longer I gaze upon them  the more I see.
/n
The only times I slip back from ecstasy are the times I tell myself:
/n
/n
Its happening
/n
Response:
/n
I dont need to know thanks, Im already there.
/n
/n
Sitting here, writing this 
/n
I am confronted by a memory in a different category to those recalling everyday experience. A memory less focused on what happened, more on what I felt. A memory that is crystal clear but open to suggestion, a living memory that I know still has the power to teach me
/n
I felt what happened,
/n
It felt a bit like this
/n
/n
LOVE
/n
/n
Im unreasonably happy.
/n
Im filled with the most intense Love I have ever felt.
/n
Mad, directionless Love that flows out of me as it flows in:
/n
It blows through me as the wind blows over
/n
And I have a feeling that, like the wind, its movement is circular.
/n
/n
As I lose consciousness of my body, I too become Love
/n
And I move with it.
/n
/n
Having experienced such Love, and all it inspires. I cannot doubt that God exists,
/n
For I have known God in his purest manifestation, God as Love: 
/n
And so I realise that God is Love, the very same force 
/n
That which inspires creation.
/n
That which creates creation!
/n
/n
The Human experience of LoveGod, known to lie behind the words of the term Mystical experience, is both old &amp; new, eternal &amp; transient:
/n
It is a fountain that human beings have been swimming in and drinking of as long as we have been apart  And we have always been a part
/n
LoveGod:
/n
/n
The illicit truth of every Religion.
/n
A muse that inspires the whole Human race.
/n
The source of all existence  
/n
As simultaneously spiritual and material beings, not only is our Consciousness born from it, Our Body as well.
/n
/n
My hand is inexorably linked to thoughts of my hand. 
/n
He is an expression of my consciousness, of its will to reach out
/n
To Touch.
/n
/n
One cannot exist without the Other because: One and the Other are One and the same. 
/n
/n
LoveGod is a paradox, being every word we utter and the gaps in between  
/n
Explained equally inadequately by Good &amp; Evil, Negative &amp; Positive,
/n
Simultaneously both and neither 
/n
It is being in the same moment as becoming, it never began and it still hasnt ended
/n
/n
And so we find The Human Condition:
/n
/n
I grow within
/n
And on this strange world:
/n
An impossible tapestry,
/n
They try to unfurl.
/n
/n
Without knowing what to ask,
/n
They question each thread:
/n
Does it start when Im born?
/n
Does it end when Im dead?
/n
/n
I grow within
/n
And on this strange land:
/n
An impossible tapestry,
/n
Woven of its own hand.
/n
/n
Dont search for the answer,
/n
For the answer will come.
/n
Stand back far enough:
/n
Two merge into One.
/n
/n
And so we find the Human race:
/n
/n
In our relentless search for the answer (which is so ridiculously simple no-one stands a chance of comprehending it) we have neglected the beauty of all that provokes question.
/n
/n
And so we find ourselves
/n
/n
There is nothing as perfect for now as the ecstasy of the infinite question:
/n
The eternal involvement of self with other; finding out without asking a thing.
/n
A passive exchange of energies, of information 
/n
/n
If we concentrate on pursuing the answer, as opposed to cultivating a passive acceptance of the fact that the answer is immanent, we do ourselves no favours
/n
/n
First: We miss out on the ecstasy of the infinite question, in other words 
/n
We do not gain full enjoyment from our involvement with the outside and the inside worlds;
/n
This involvement is to be marvelled at, celebrated, cherished and explored
/n
/n
Second: As we dream of the most sacred thing, we neglect the fact that everything is sacred.
/n
This, combined with an unawareness of the inter-connectedness of all things, has contributed to the widespread destruction of our Mother Earth, Gaia:
/n
/n
She is our Garden yet we trample her plants and slaughter her animals, we suffocate her skin with a layer of concrete, pollute the air she breathes and the water she drinks with our foul concoctions
/n
/n
She is our Garden, the tree is our life  and we still forbid our children free run of her fruits
/n
/n
How I yearn for free run of her fruits
/n
/n
The Hawaiian Baby Woodrose seeds I consumed belong to a family of Gaias fruits termed Entheogen meaning God Within:
/n
/n
Many Entheogens having been helping Human beings find LoveGod since we first looked outside of meat for food. They are gifts 
/n
First from God,
/n
Then from Our Planet.
/n
/n
There is nothing less human about looking to nature for Mind food than there is about looking to nature for Body food 
/n
Yet the former lies well behind in the acceptance stakes  At least in so far as many Societies, with their Governments and Religions, are concerned.
/n
/n
*  *  *  *  *
/n
/n
The drugs had worn off.
/n
/n
We emerged from the woods, into which we had retreated after our Mystical experience a top the cliff, and lay once more under the blanket.
/n
The sound of the Sea, its partner the wind thankfully absent, soothed us to sleep.
/n
/n
I awoke cold &amp; damp but energised &amp; joyous.
/n
Climbing back up the Head in order to reach the warming rays of the morning Sun, I was sent two messages  arriving as thoughts
/n
/n
The first, from God, said:
/n
/n
No-one dies.
/n
/n
The second, from Our Planet, said:
/n
/n
Its not too late.
/n
/n
/n
copyright. Sam Ross. 2001.</bodytext></report>