<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>67892</idnum><title>Euphoria + Sensory Overload</title><author>Modells</author><substance>psilocybin</substance><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>4_fluoroamphetamine</substance><bodytext>


It was a Friday and Christmas Break had just started, and I was staying over at a friend's house, so I decided to celebrate in a rather unorthodox fashion. 
/n
/n
I had tripped about three times before, all on psilocybin, so I'm not unfamiliar with psilocybin, and I enjoyed myself thoroughly each of those times. Tonight, though, I wanted something different. 
/n
/n
I had originally planned to get some acid, which I had never tried, but was unable to do so, so I was offered an alternative by my friend (who I will refer to as Friend #1 from now on). What he offered was a considerably more expensive endeavor than acid, but it interested me greatly. 
/n
/n
I had never tried 4-fluoroamphetamine before, and the thought of doing those alongside psilocybin was intriguing. 
/n
/n
Several of my friends and some new acquaintances smoked a blunt and out of another friend (friend #2)'s vape. I was high by the time we went to go collect our contraband, Friend #2 was driving, and I popped the 4-fluoro more or less as soon as I got it in my hands. It was about 7:00, and my throat was rather dry, and we had no water, so it went down hard. We had not established where we would be staying that night, so I held off on the psilocybin for awhile. 
/n
/n
We went back to Friend #2's house, and it was decided that we would stay there, so at about 7:30, the psilocybin went into my mouth and down my throat. The 4-fluoro had begun affecting me, but it did not feel like a typical stimulant. I didn't really feel like moving, and I felt incredibly relaxed and content. I could feel euphoria approaching. 
/n
/n
About a half hour later, around 8:00, the psilocybin began taking effect. I was perfectly content to sit on the couch and do nothing while my friends did... well, I actually don't remember what they were doing at that point. After I peaked, at around 8:30, I showed my friends some things on youtube and proposed that we go outside and enjoy nature (I felt that they would enjoy that too, as they were all tripping as well). 
/n
/n
We went outside, and found that the snow had hardened into ice. I was feeling euphoric and slightly delirious, unable to contain myself vocally, I began just saying 'ahhhhhh....' while my friends looked at me strangely. 
/n
/n
It was dark, but not too dark to see. A very fun environment for a trip. My senses seemed amplified, so the euphoria, combined with the standard psilocybin-induced confusion, and the strange environment all added up to me being completely out of my mind. 
/n
/n
We (my friends and I) waded into the woods, and I began hugging trees. I had very poor motor skills, and appeared very intoxicated. We stayed out there for about an hour, went inside, and I was still tripping very hard, although the euphoric effects had dimmed. 
/n
/n
I had long since lost track of time, and the rest of the night proceeded like a very heavy psilocybin trip, with lots and lots of visuals and screwy emotions. 
/n
/n
Near the end of the night, at around 3:00 AM, we sat down to watch The Shining. The psilocybin had long since lost its effect, but the fluoro was still going. I found myself unable to watch some of the more disturbing scenes in the movie. around 5:00 AM, the fluoro ended, and my night ended with me passing out on the floor. A few hours later, I was woken up by my allergies at around 8:00 AM, but felt no real noticeable emotional or physical fatigue from the night.</bodytext></report>