<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>68569</idnum><title>A beautiful night! Raw material for you all,</title><author>dilated_pupils</author><substance>2ce</substance><bodytext>


Monday, January 21st, 2008
/n
/n
10:02 - insulfated 22mg~ of 2c-e
/n
10:40 - insulfated another 22mg~ of 2c-e, deciding this is what I want to do tonight, this is the journey I'm ready to take, I guess we'll see!
/n
/n
hands sweat a lot, from the beginning, til now 10:40, so I'm sure it will only grow, or it will go away I don't know yet, will report back hopefully.
/n
Like to add, everything in the corner of my eyes is someone, a person, somehow, but when I look with the front of my eyes they disappear, I really wish 
/n
/n
I could see this more, it's growing though, i'm seeing weird things on this white paper writing right now so, along listening to sound trip sector 9. 
/n
/n
but yeah going to join the others in my room which aren't there haha.
/n
/n
10:45 - take a hit of marijuana, hold it in and as long/deep as I want too, lovin' it! reminds me of mushrooms right there, but i still taste chemicals 
/n
/n
and wow as I'm typing this 3d patterns are coming off my screen at me literally this is awesome!!!
/n
/n
11:08 music don't matter no more i just realized, i like it all, but rather would had on random songs on my playlist right now then going to Sound tribe 
/n
/n
right now i dunno, talking to friend on AIM, intense open eye visuals crazy can't explain, 3d outta the comp def, my room is only alive outta the 
/n
/n
corners out of my eyes sometimes, it's hard to expalain, i can static it all, but allow it all to move when i don't center my focus on it, allow it all 
/n
/n
on the sides of me
/n
/n
before i light this cig i just got up to get, im sitting here realizing holy crap muscle stiffness big time, but its probably because i've been mainly 
/n
/n
stationary here on the comp but not really all true, i have no idea and really don't care to be honest lets just enjoy this thing!
/n
/n
- had to add, heard voices, not disterbing at all really, but i hear them outside in a happiness sort of way - male - it may have been from a song i 
/n
/n
don't know at this point, and what i mean is like it wasn't playing but from earlier, OR maybe it was playing i don't know honestly.
/n
/n
no convo on aim anymore at this point anyway, music is awesome i love it haha in the way i just enjoy it because its helping my trip and i like singing 
/n
/n
it - nas right now 
/n
/n
just had realization - girls - get to know the in depth example is janie right now she is so deep i know it because i know her and i can feel it, i 
/n
/n
don't know if i want to show her my deep side, mines good haha, but im saying i don't know how i feel about her righ now she is a complicated women to 
/n
/n
put it light, honestly. haha.
/n
/n
/n
/n
/n
ok going to go listen to music, i wish i had some more to snort but maybe thats my trip speaking ill enjoy this what i got ya know and its so strong 
/n
/n
haha i always wanna go more i wanna go somewhere uncontrollable i wanna find something that can knock me on my ass, we'll see someday..
/n
/n
/n
forgot what i was going to type hold on
/n
oh yeah at this point i can just push away all thoughts of negative, past about previous relationships, no problem, they are okay with me now, at this 
/n
/n
point, why not? i mean i'm not analyzing them right now so i can't tell you more then this, shit i don't know, hahahaha im laughing right now.
/n
/n
11:22 ok typo are easy right now, but i can type pretty much, anyway cig is all i meant to write haha funny i did that without even realizing it.
/n
11:25
/n
umm closed eye visuals are werid, girls yeah i anyway was being served some sort of 'dish' only way to say it right now. unknown but i wasn't taking it 
/n
/n
i don't think i don't even know really, it was just funny now looking back haha.
/n
very influenced by music right now very much so, everything is i love it
/n
LOVE IT hahahahaha
/n
oh here it comes sound tripe outta no where what to expect i dunno
/n
/n
wow haha you think you can see it all, but no remember your mind can always ALWAYS make something new, unexpected, awesome, amazing im lost for words 
/n
/n
right now, typing sucks right now anyway ok it doesn't but i so fucking wish i could type while i was listening to music closed eyes laying back, 
/n
/n
basically typing down my mind, i wish i could type FROM IT, so badly right now oh man ok back to it NOW! haha
/n
/n
11:35pm now this is awesome, great visuals closed eye, i love them however they drop when i wish to remember them, easily gone somehow i don't know but 
/n
/n
i wish i could hold onto them for future but it's ok i'm ok with it.
/n
anyway my mind JUST did me a favor by not bringing up girls in my past, right now, all of it just flew away in my mind its like it spoke to me i 
/n
/n
promised it weed ahaha so here he deserves it right now! but for real, i forgot changed a song and forgot now dammit i thought i wouldn't ok back to 
/n
/n
smoking and WOW how the fuck am i typing right now honestly i don't know and it's super speed!
/n
/n
--have to add in -- something i recently got over personally in my head, in my mind, it's ok now, and i can see it sitting there and let it pass by in 
/n
/n
my mind, and not care and its LOVELY because its GONE haha no more bad trips, MOTHERFUCKER. ok i need to smoke now i've promised my mind this LETS GO!
/n
/n
11:41 now out of weed and ok with it, wish i had more but its honestly ok, i wasn't planning this trip earlier or i'd have easily saved much more, i'm a 
/n
/n
pothead, and LOVE to smoke on pyschs they make it so much more in depth and emotion pures in music with each rip haha thats best way to explain it.11:42 
/n
/n
now.
/n
/n
11:44 im out of it typing this is so hard ok, only when i right slower, i get into grooves of perfectness, then i need to stop and i mess up, i don't 
/n
/n
know
/n
anyway, just made my playlist better for my suited needs on this trip so lets see where it takes me!
/n
/n
11:49
/n
wala mellting listening to sound tribe haha of course, and anyway of yeah mischief of a sleepwalker which in terms would make me think odd of the title 
/n
/n
but listening now i love it allowing it to take over fucking music i love it, it is the base to my trip and i love it, no doubt, i can't blieve on this 
/n
/n
dose i'm ok with all of this I DON'T KNOW how really, but let's enjoy it! and of course the music is going with what i'm typing it feels, wow this is 
/n
/n
awesome! i am loving this chemical now i'm over the personal problem i can trip now and i didn't even know if it was done with but obviously it is now!
/n
this is best thats all i have to say i'm happy as hell, would love to have someone else here right now, but at the same time ITS OK for real it is, i'm 
/n
/n
having a tempt to go drink some wine but that will kill this a bit duh only a little i guess.
/n
/n
must add 11:54 - real fast here, music and my mind easily melt together, and have weird coindiences, as such like song names and i quickly see something 
/n
/n
in my room, oh wow i meant music and my room i think? it must be, anyway, i looked at the fan and it had to do with the song name somehow don't ask but 
/n
/n
yeah that's what i'm trying to say i guess lol wow bad example sorry.
/n
/n
12:09 - ending some personal anxieties, let them go watch them go in my mind and was okay it because i know i need to do this i need to, i need to do 
/n
/n
this to help my self and right now in my life i need to mentally help myself, and i'm trying to hard in life right now you may not know but i am, very 
/n
/n
much so trying to make my life into something and i know i will succseed haha i can't even spell right now, but i know i will get there because my ego 
/n
/n
and ambition, hopefully my ego doesn't go ahead of me, let's keep that in tact with help from psychs i believe look at me now.
/n
ok back to music which by the way my whole thing of all this ended me with LIFE IS LOVE
/n
so i'm thinking that so purely right now let's enjoy it!
/n
/n
by the way occasional sips of wine here and there nothing much - one glass - still half full if i had to guess right now at 12:13am i can go get more 
/n
/n
but wanted to keep this trip in one room tonight that was my goal, with music and me and my problems lets do it i'm ready haha thats the attidude! oh 
/n
/n
and i'll add hands are extremely sweating, and i would use more slang but i'm forcing myself to type better because i am better then that. i really am 
/n
/n
haha. stil lovinnnnnnnnnnn this! 12:15 ending.
/n
/n
since i'm racing like a fucking racecar if i had to tell it that way, no music can be good right now unless its to my standards sometimes i like hearing 
/n
/n
others voices, sometimes i just want music without it and i get it because i'm controlling it haha, but honestly wow i say that a lot laughed at myself 
/n
/n
for that one, anyway i lost my train of thought peace. 12:17am now. oh yeah i just figured it out literally haha 2 seconds later, a quick glance at 
/n
/n
seeing my playlist made me realizing it, music can't be slow right now need something upbeat, entertaining, not slow AT ALL or it drives me insane 
/n
/n
making me feel like i have to come up from the bottom of the trip again and i am here now, so yeah.
/n
/n
/n
12:32leaving the room for the first time, my bedroom, to use the bathroom, urinate and i want some more wine so.
/n
/n
it's only 12:38 right now and i can tell you this trip has definitely hite a plataeu and i wish it was still growing, should have swolled the 2nd cap. 
/n
/n
my fault, but i still tactled some demons in my life, got rid of some anxieties and realized i have some new issues but i'm ok with them not actually 
/n
/n
'new' issues but moreso recently added issues so to say. close friends to be more specific, wait i'm remember and forgeting haha at the same time.
/n
/n
I'm remembering that i told myself i'd drop all of this anything that happens with ANYONE (was moreso towards friends) is their own path i cannot make 
/n
/n
them chose, only guide and if i can't guide any longer then fine, LET IT GO anxieties gone, let them be, why worry on things i cannot control at all i 
/n
/n
know this is awesome, i truely had a great trip already and i feel like it's over kind of, i know it will continue obviously, but it's definitely come 
/n
/n
to a plat that i've wished to just continue to grow dammit! haha.
/n
/n
ok i'm going to continue listening to music maybe i'll find something to stimulate my mind here, i mean i am STILL tripping, let's do this! 12:43 
/n
/n
closing now,
/n
/n
oh must add, walking is ok right now, allowing OCDS (checking doors etc) to just go, simply go because i know i'm ok. i love this drug. also open eye 
/n
/n
visuals have calmed down, but i don't really know i mean i can definitely find depth in them if i wish to. 'nough said, i'm out for now.
/n
/n
12:56 just talked too a good friend on AIM and had a quick convo, anyway, i'm still tripping hard no doubt but still platDOUGHED dammit. haha i'm ok 
/n
/n
with it i think this is a level i am only good with, extreme levels, bring it on, i always have been.
/n
/n
12:56 music dammit it like just went with the night so far so well, have to add, the music came at the PERFECT moments literally, it was magical to say 
/n
/n
the least.
/n
/n
1:40 updat here, loving everything music still is great, definitely more calm but still loving. im glad this trip went so well I really am. and could 
/n
/n
not be happier at this moment in my life.
/n
/n
I spent the rest of my last 40 minutes, enjoying some wine, cigarettes (yeah I want to quit so badly, I will though), and music and talking to someone. 
/n
/n
Music is still coming at odd coincidances funny that adds to previous trips of mine. coincidances.
/n
/n
1:57am okay i just realized, my past trips (if you've read them, you'll know) but anyway they were all talking about coincidances and paths, and they 
/n
/n
just collied, they are one I cannot explain yet. But I'll give you an example, Johnny wants mushrooms and Toria walks in I have mushrooms! okay now 
/n
/n
thats a coincidance, however EACH others person has brought themselves THERE by paths they have chosen. Oh man this is too much, I cannot wait to futhor 
/n
/n
my experiences with 2c-e and other drugs, I truely believe I'm onto something, LIFE.
/n
/n
2:33am still tripping hard, took some klonopin (4mgs, high tolerance prescribed for years), and finished off bit of wine I had left but am ultimately sitting here contimplating all that I've known.  I will progress, and with that will come great success. yeah quote me aha.
/n
/n
I'm done with this report, enjoy, the raw material in here, sorry for the typos but well that's life.  Maybe some of you will read all of this and get something from it, let me know, post a reply</bodytext></report>