<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6868</idnum><title>Bad Experience With Liquid G</title><author>CroverC</author><substance>mdma</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><substance>ghb</substance><bodytext>



Well about 2 weeks ago a new batch of beans had gotten into town.  Really smacked out X-Files from Panama City, FL.  Took 2 1/2 Friday night and rolled my balls off.  Really good loving experience.  Saturday could only get my hands on two pills.  Dropped one at around midnight.  Chased with one cap full of GHB.  Started feeling effects alot sooner and stronger than the night before.  Maybe had something to do with the lack of food consumed that day, or maybe had something to do with the G.  One of my best friends and closest friends decided to take a walk.  We walked for about 2 miles and then sat down and just talked for like an hour.  The effects were so strong at this point all we could do was just lay and hold each other for like 30 mins.  At that point we walked back to the house and me, her and another friend of ours decided to go get them some more beans.  We got to the dudes house were I dropped my other pill (roughly around 3 am ) and I also chased this one with another cap of GHB.  Within 30 min I was in Heaven.  Someone persuaded me to have a mixed drink.  Good Ole' Crown and Coke. Just what I needed.  Alcohol mixed with GHB. (Should have listened to EROWID's warning).  Now what happened next shows that I do possess a great level of stupidity.  I gave a hit of the GHB to a friend of mine who claimed she wasn't rolling hard off of 3 of the X-Files.  GHB has always made me roll super hard.  She didn't like the taste (go figure) and started complaining.  So being the smart ass that I am I turned up the remaining G in the bottle to show it wasn't that nasty.  I later found out there were 3-4 cap fulls left in the bottle when I perceived there only being at the most 1 1/2.  Now that is WAY too much G at once.  Well my close friend and I went riding around with this other girl.  At about 5:30 am it all hit me at fucking once.  I started crying insanely telling my friend how much I loved her.  She held me real close and told me that she loved me that much too.  At that moment I blew up like never before.  It felt like I blew up for days.  It was the single best feeling ever I have felt on drugs.  Well my friend had to leave at 6 am and I began to feel like I was going to hoop out.  I layed down on the couch and wanted to pass out.  Then the trouble started.  Some guys came over who were rolling and smoking lots of weed.  When they found out that I had been taking GHB they started nagging me, talking alot of shit.  All I remember is one dude hitting me while I was laying on the couch.  When I got up to defend myself I got a kick right to the ribs.  The next thing I remember was my roommate sitting next to me on the couch.  He and my friends had came to pick me up and take me home.  There was nothing that I could have done to protect myself.  I was told that I started the shit with the guys and I apologized to them and explained to them the situation I was in that night.  
/n
/n
The point of this long boring story is: Ecstasy mixed with GHB is INCREDIBLE, as long as you are careful about the amount you take and avoid alcohol.</bodytext></report>