<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6934</idnum><title>Euphoria and High Pulse</title><author>Phaedras</author><substance>caffeine</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>



(Note: I am a somewhat tall person, around 1.95 meters, therefore with me the effects of ANY drug should take slightly longer to manifest themselves than with a normal-sized person.)
/n
/n
Now, I had tried excessive doses of caffeine for the first time a day BEFORE this experience. I had swallowed a 200mg tablet around 10:00 AM and had a light euphoric, hyperactive feel for the rest of the day. Sleep was not a problem.
/n
/n
On the day after, at ca. 8:30 PM, I swallowed another 200mg tablet and 'washed it down' with a can of Mountain Dew, which contains another 50mg of caffeine. The effects started to kick in about an hour later, at 9:30, with my heart racing and me having the strong feeling of having to DO something. I met with a couple friends then, in a local bar.
/n
/n
After sitting down in the circle of people, with 1-2 people I didn't know (friends of friends), I immediately launched into a long conversation with the boyfriend of one of my friends. During that time, I talked fast and without thinking about what I was saying. My heart beated uncontrollably. This went on for a few hours. It also seemed my mind wasn't allowed even a single negative thought. If I even started to feel pessismistic about ANYTHING, my thoughts just raced passed the notion, bypassing it all together.
/n
/n
I drank and smoked very fast during those hours. It took me about 5 minutes for each beer (this is Germany, beer is more potent and heavier than American beer), though I did not feel any of the alcohol's effects until after the caffeine started to wear off, at around 12:30 AM.
/n
/n
The comedown was AWFUL.
/n
/n
After arriving home, finally getting hit by the first wave of alcohol-induced symptoms, I dropped into bed relatively fast. But sleep did not come easily. I tossed and turned for at least a half an hour, before finally falling asleep. The caffeine wasn't finished with me yet, though. I awoke several times during the night, feeling hot (though not feverish) and staying awake for several minutes before falling asleep again. The next morning all I felt was the residual effects of a hangover.
/n
/n
My suggestions:
/n
/n
PLAN. Realize you won't be able to get off the stuff until hours later, so plan when you're going to take the caffeine. Effects kick in after about 45-60 minutes, and stay for 4-5 hours AT LEAST. 200mg is fine for hyperactivity and light euphoria. 300mg is already going slightly extreme. And if you have heart problems, please, stay off it entirely.</bodytext></report>