<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>6997</idnum><title>Pure Euphoria</title><author>badboy</author><substance>alprazolam</substance><substance>codeine</substance><substance>acetaminophen</substance><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
By the way, this is my first time trying codeine. I stopped using illegal drugs and now use only pharmaceuticals when I can.
/n
/n
7:30
/n
I just swallowed four pills containing codeine. They each contain 30mg of codeine and 500mg of paracetamol. This makes a total of 120mg of codeine. Lets wait and see..
/n
/n
7:45
/n
I am taking 2mg of xanax for the combination. Just swallowed them...going to lie down and listen to gatecrasher...if the phone rings I will not answer...
/n
/n
8:00
/n
Lying down and feeling EXTREMELY euphoric...God Bless...going to smoke a cigarette too, to make sure I don't fall asleep...feeling really nice...I wonder how long this is going to last. I am going to take another two tablets. Just swallowed them...making a grand total of 180mg of codeine...I am LOVING IT...my back is feeling like I need to stretch it...when I smoke the cigarette, I felt SOOOOO dizzy and bouncy that I  put it off...
/n
/n
Ok...so I'm going to take another two pills, making a grand total of 240mg of codeine...it's just TOO good and its only 9 o'clock. I wonder how I'm going to feel tomorrow morning? I just took another three pills cause the half life is very short and I want the high... Strange...when I just got up to walk around, I felt some pain in my chest area (is that normal)...
/n
/n
WOWOWOWOWOWO!!!!!! I took 330mg of codeine on my first try... MY GOD!!! It was INCREDIBLE!! I just lay on the floor in pure euphoria for hour after hour after hour...listening to albums in the dark...every once in a while I would hear voices (hallucinate) and would be thinking of the ODDEST things on earth...then I would impulsively say out words that came to my mind. I HAD to say them...I felt like I was talking to someone who was listening to my every thought...tomorrow again!!! And again...and again...this was GREAT!!!! (except for the pain in my chest that subsided after a few minutes...I wonder what that was from). My mind set was strange. Sometimes I would find myself thinking of the weirdest things like I thought I was in a taxi one time and I started talking to the taxi driver to tell him where my house was...another time I remember imagining I was somewhere else and my mind REALLY thought I was there and so I would say things accordingly...I remember saying I love God very much for letting me feel this peace of mind.
/n
/n
I recommend doing codeine when the telephone is off, and you are NOT expecting anyone and have hours and hours and hours to kill...and of course REALLY good music... this was an INCREDIBLE experience for me...I'm off to bed now and the time in 2:00 AM...
/n
/n
Peace and Love to everyone in Erowids vault</bodytext></report>