<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>70092</idnum><title>Extreme Case Overdose</title><author>Rezidue</author><substance>bromo_dragonfly</substance><bodytext>


My story was featured on the BBC before I woke up!
/n
/n
On thursday 20th march 2008, I had the most intense experience of my life. I am an 18yo dnb DJ from Berkshire, and I a week ago, some friends and I went to purchase a dose of bromo dragonfly from a friend. The evening went well. We had 4 drops on the hand each, 300g per drop so a 1200g dose. One of my friends accidentally picked up a wrap off the side mistaking it for some k.
/n
/n
The night started well after we got home. Visuals came on nicely with a bit of weed and good music on nice speakers after about an hour. Was finding things quite confusing, faces morphed, nothing ever looked the same. Was a new experience, new feelings and senses.
/n
/n
To get to the good bit...
/n
/n
4 hours into the trip, I decided to snort what was in that wrap (thinking it was ketamine, and would just intensify this already great trip (a bit silly really as 1200g would last 36hours plus anyway).
/n
It burned my nostrils...
/n
It turns out the wrap contained around 60-70 undiluted doses of bromo dragonfly... And I inhaled it...
/n
/n
My memory starts to fall to pieces about 20mins after inhaling it. An hour in, I was uncontrallable and no one could get through to me or make me see them, I just went mad, tore my clothes off, went outside in the hail whilst I was sweating profusely, and proceeded to run into and through a large bramble bush. About 30% of my body has alot of deep scars now, including my face. My friends pinned me down, covered me in jackets and called an ambulance. It took 15mins for the ambulance to arrive, and as it arrived, I threw up blood, inhaled it, causing my lung to collapse, and my heart then stopped for the first time. When I got to the hospital, I was on life support. My heart stopped again, and then re started 5 mins later.
/n
/n
I was on life support for 36 hours... I was expected to be on for more than a week. I was told I made a 'miracle recovery', and the doctors had never seen anything like it. I was still very much intoxicated well into sunday and monday morning. I can tell you, I can think deeply back and remember the trips and the new sensations and emotions I felt, especially when my heart stopped.
/n
/n
And I can partly feel the feelings again. It is quite amazing, and I am glad to be able to feel like this now, but it definitely was not a good idea or a good risk. I am the only person to ever have survived a dose more than around 5000g... And I took more than 40times that amount... I have sworn off all drugs now, as I dont think I could ever have a more amazing experience. And as I can remember all of this one anyway, I dont need another one!
/n
/n
Bromo dragonfly is a powerful, amazing, and illegal (in norway and sweden) haha.
/n
/n
But seriously, treat it right... Or dont take it.
/n
/n
I found out the hard way. 
/n
/n
Here is the link to the news report again, I may be making a tv news appearance very soon! 
/n
/n
http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/england/surrey/7309732.stm
/n
/n
Cheers, happy reading :)
/n
/n
Rezidue</bodytext></report>