<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>701</idnum><title>Joy of Sadness #3</title><author>Zam</author><substance>unlinkable</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>
/n
September 1996
/n
Grams 1.5 : weird body feel, mild discomfort, strange headspace.  Crossed eyes produce mosaic /kaleidoscope images.  Lying in the forest looking up, crossed eyes make the trees and sky look like a stained glass cathedral image.
/n
/n
 Felt mild annoyance at bright incandescent lights  In the first 2 hours there are these waves of energy, sort of a feeling of being blasted through my body from legs to head with a shudder that moves my mind in some way.  Could be frightening or exciting, but I think its neutral by itself.
/n
/n
/n
A feeling of silliness for taking the mushrooms, of needing to go through this/these experiences to see.  What am I looking for?   Why do I expect to find it with mushrooms?  I laughed and smiled at myself and the world for producing such an odd circumstance, at me for going through gyrations to feel in touch, to find myself I realize how ridiculously impractical I am in the things I do.  The way I dress, the way I do things, the fact that I havent learned to keep track of the simplest things.  But overall, its a good feeling.
/n
/n
Learn to ritualize movements so that I can learn them well, move slowly, deliberately, become more aware of my movements.  Simplify.  Get to know the things Ive got so that each of the things I have and use I am familiar with.  Get small bags for each of the things I want to carry: a bag for a pipe, a pipe, a bag for each  different smoking mixture These things became obvious to me as necessities on the path that Ive chosen.
/n
/n
I tried to extend my range of perception and found no added abilities and became quickly distracted by other thoughts.  I started to pay attention to strange visual effects and chose not to do so.  I tried to focus on healing, by focusing on a friends dilemma and felt strongly the sadness of muddling through problems that have no clear resolution.  I feel sadness and joy for the difficulty of things in life.  I felt like I was able to connect more easily to feelings than I am normally.
/n
/n
I also felt and thought that what I am missing from my daily life is a quiet meditative space.  That when I use the mushrooms I act in the way I would choose to act more often.  Integrating the meditative, contemplative, quiet, connected feelings that I produce and act when seeking Spirit with mushrooms, may be more effective than doing the mushrooms themselves.
/n
/n
Overall effects: mild to medium, few visuals enhanced feeling, mildly insightful, confusing, mildly illuminating.  Another experience of the joy of sadness.  Positive experience.
/n
/n
-zam</bodytext></report>