<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7201</idnum><title>End of a Blue Stretch ;)</title><author>The Lyre Snake</author><substance>2ct7</substance><bodytext>



A day over two weeks ago I moved the first dose of 10 mg. 2C-T-7 powder with handheld razor blades from a foil packette to a five-inch glass one-hitter.  I sucked on the one-hitter while flicking flame over the crumbled paint-like off white powder, and found it melted before it would burn.  I eventually burned 10 mg., most of which reached my lungs, and stretched -
/n
/n
The rage I had struggled with all spring fell away, and when I closed my eyes I met (finally!) certain friends that had, I was to learn, watched over me my whole life. -
/n
/n
For the next nine days I continued my stretching, with approximately 10 mg. doses (always smoked) either divided throughout the day or taken all at once in the evening.  I am not sure as to why the drug affected me more strongly each time, although the 2 1/2 vials of fairly good acid I ingested between January and March, in particular, may have increased my sensitivity.
/n
/n
On the tenth day, by which I had learned more from my friends and their healing place than I could have imagined finding out in this lifetime, I had a severe allergy attack and promptly came down with ear and sinus infections.  
/n
/n
While in bed for the next two days, I continued healing psychically and emotionally.  I had been cut off from the experience of love ever since my energetically karmic childhood in this lifetime surrounded me and infused my memories.  On the thirteenth day I smoked approximately 15 mg. of the blue stretch and about thirty six hours later, while asleep, found myself free.  Then, this morning I awoke, immediately blew my lover and am (gods willing) still basking under a cosmic heat lamp as any of you are reading this.
/n
/n
I suggest that 2C-T-7 may well also be known to its friends as 'Blue Stretch' (hey, it gets you out of one) and the experience considered 'stretching' ;)  Stretching with the blue stretch filled me full of love emotionally, spiritually and psychically.
/n
/n
A Note On My Medications:
/n
/n
I use birth control pills (OrthoNovum 1/35), Solgar Earth-Source vitamins, and started taking Allegra-D, Doxycycl Hyc Caps and using a Flo-Nase inhaler as of three days ago due to those minor ear and sinus infections.</bodytext></report>