<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7212</idnum><title>Perfect</title><author>Adara</author><substance>mdma</substance><bodytext>



Four days ago I tried MDMA for the first time. I didn't plan on it at all. A friend of mine, who is much more experienced with drugs then I am, had four pills with her. I decided to try it, and bought two from her.
/n
/n
We sat outside in her front yard and took one pill each around 4 p.m. About a half an hour later I started feeling very hyper, joyful, and relaxed. Everything seemed brighter, more colorful. I felt warm all over, but at the same time I was getting sudden chills down my back. I tried explaining this, but it never came out making much sense. Actually, most of the things I felt made little sense. I was warm, but cold, I felt sick in my stomach for a little while, but yet, it was somehow a good feeling. Everything was a good feeling. I felt as if no matter what, everything was well. I felt as if I loved everyone and everyone would love me back. Everything was perfect. I was in my own little personal heaven. I had cravings for water, which tasted sweet, but otherwise I didn't want to eat. If I wasn't dancing in the driveway I was laying in the grass running my hands through it and staring at the sky. Everything felt good to the touch. The pavement or her rough tennis shoes felt even harder then normal, and slightly scared me if I felt them. Around 6 p.m. or so, she convinced me to eat some noodles because I hadn't eaten all day. They felt so wonderful in my mouth and instead of eating them, I played with them. We ran the noodles across our skin and they felt like cold rain. Water was amazing. She sprayed me with the hose at one point. I felt so alive. About 8 p.m. I took my second pill because I wanted the feeling to last longer. Soon after that I started feeling dizzy. I couldn't stand up too much because I wanted to make sure I would not fall over. I would move my upper body to the music and not realize it until she pointed it out. I just sat there moving like this for about two hours, in a daze. Soon after I fell asleep. I woke up the next day around 11 a.m. still feeling fine and somewhat giddy. I slept for hours that afternoon, still getting cold chills. I never felt a 'crash' or severe change of emotions afterwards. For the past 3 days I still had the 'perfect' feeling. Like everything was going to work out, everything would be perfect forever. Even now, four days later, I have the cold chills fairly often. I'm still getting a bit dizzy, much more then normal, and I still have slight 'perfect' feelings. Overall I enjoyed the experience. It was Perfect.</bodytext></report>