<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>73058</idnum><title>Not so Methy Lone</title><author>Tiger Faerie</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>lsd</substance><substance>methylone</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><bodytext>


It was a rainy day 
/n
I had a headache
/n
/n
This
/n
I have to say makes for an interesting tale of facets, of euphoria, of wellbeing and of love.
/n
/n
I had commitments last night, I had promised a friend that I would go to his gallery opening I had also however just received a curiousity, the methylone.
/n
I was never really one for social event such as gallery openings
/n
For those who dont know, it generally an ordeal for those who dont enjoy small talk, wine and large groups of insecure people gathered in one space.
/n
However this night I decided I would try the methylone
/n
I hadnt eaten anything for a number of hours so had pretty much an empty stomach.
/n
I dont have scales
/n
So I worked old school
/n
Dividing the yellowy powder with a card,
/n
Tipping it into a glass of water
/n
A little stir
/n
It tastes slightly bitter
/n
But not unpleasant
/n
The time now is about 7.10pm
/n
I am on the phone to my friend with whom I will join later
/n
I tell him that I am drinking this stuff
/n
I finish the phone call 
/n
I feel clearer
/n
Its now 7.20
/n
my headache has pretty much gone
/n
it normally take me a while to get out the house
/n
but I was on the bus by 7.30
/n
and the bus journey was nice
/n
I felt great
/n
And clear headed
/n
With no feelings of paranoia
/n
I didnt worry about the other people on the bus 
/n
I am listening to music, it sounds good, but it is good. A DJ set from Berlin. It just enhances my good mood.  Im tapping my feet a little but I dont feel like I want to burst into dance!
/n
I get there and there at about 8pm
/n
I felt as free as a bird
/n
I flitted around talking to many people, those I knew, those I didnt.
/n
I felt as though I was full of positive confidence, the kind which is not full of ego. 
/n
Everyone is drinking, I dont want to drink. I dont really like it anyway. 
/n
I have nice conversations, very caring. Conversations flow easily with everybody, even those that I dont like. Again there is no paranoia which I might feel on E or mdma. My mind is clear. I am able for the rest of the night to deal with all kinds of social situations which I may have otherwise found challenging.
/n
I clocked my friend 
/n
Lets call him MP
/n
Of course as many faceted as the world is I could not just go up and speak to him.
/n
Oh no for tonight, in this setting anyway, we were to play a little game.
/n
For no one was to know that we really knew eachother  yes, its true artists are a bunch of no good scoundrels!
/n
Exchanging glances every so often, I began to feel that enhanced sex drive similar to mdma but with out the confusion.
/n
I floated around looking at the artwork
/n
I didnt feel the forced need to mingle 
/n
It came very naturally 
/n
I was very comfortable in the space.
/n
Speaking is easy, with only one notable minor drug sounding,slur!
/n
An hour went by 
/n
9pm ish
/n
I felt the need to smoke more than usual, as I dont smoke cigarettes much anymore
/n
But, as with many drugs
/n
I enjoyed heart felt conversations with friends.
/n
Eventually after much circulating
/n
We decided it was time to leave MP and I
/n
We went out separate ways
/n
Meeting at the bus stop
/n
Yes!
/n
Now it was time to go to the circus!
/n
Yes, literally.
/n
We happen to live in a city which once a year, for one month only, experiences its population more than double, and this toy town comes to life with music, cabaret, theatre, dance etc.
/n
Approaching 10pm
/n
We kiss 
/n
It feels great
/n
Well it always feels great 
/n
But the methylone in my brain and the previous situation of sexual tension makes this kiss explosive.
/n
We go to a bar
/n
I am totally loved up 
/n
Again not like mdma really, you see I dont like mdma too much as it makes me feel a bit confused and paranoid, its like on mdma my feelings are not true. They are just chemical. 
/n
With Methylone I felt I could let my guard down completely, and let the drug take its course. I see now why its sometimes called Ease.
/n
I ask MP if he would like to join me down pleasant street
/n
We order juice and tonic water
/n
I dose his drink with about the same amount as me
/n
It is 10.20pm
/n
I am still flying
/n
I feel fantastic
/n
Again within 10 minutes MP has joined me
/n
And we cant keep our hands of one another
/n
Small rushes of euphoria come in waves, remaining just at the right level to remain tucked within the inner self.
/n
We talk about how we feel 
/n
Truly and honestly 
/n
And its beautiful
/n
There is no false e-talk here
/n
10.50 we head off to the circus
/n
it is still raining heavily
/n
and when we get there the que is long
/n
we continue kissing under our umbrella
/n
needless to say we are both very much hedonists!
/n
The que isnt too bad, I decide to drop a very small about of acid.
/n
Small as I dont want to override the methylone first time round, small also because we are going to the circus, and really there isnt need to enhance the experience too much!
/n
The acid came on quickly. Although at this small dose gave me that slight headache and feeling in the top of the mouth sensation. 
/n
The performance was great, twas Le Clique in fact
/n
I love that sort of thing anyway, I really enjoy this time of year here, as people like MP and I are always this way, and for this month many others come into town, other performers and new friends. I feel really happy in this new environment
/n
I am even starting to get a little full of myself
/n
I begin playing up to the circus/cabaret vibe, I am also wearing my soviet generals outfit one of them. This is normal for me though!
/n
We both enjoy the acts
/n
MP I can tell is feeling that increased sex drive I mentioned earlier
/n
We go out at half time 
/n
And enjoy cigarettes and dirty dancing in the rain.
/n
When we leave the circus it is about 2am
/n
The rain looked beautiful on the ground
/n
We wished we could go home
/n
But in our situation this was no possible 
/n
We had to eventually go our separate ways
/n
However horny we were!
/n
A taxi home
/n
A kiss goodnight
/n
/n
I am home
/n
It is nearly 3am
/n
I go into my room
/n
I think im tripping
/n
As to my surprise I see a shape in my bed
/n
There is someone asleep in there!
/n
I deal with the situation
/n
Its one of the lost boys of never EVER land
/n
I am surprised at my cool ability to deal with the situation
/n
He is promptly evicted 
/n
/n
I decide to have a joint
/n
Unexpected OEVs!
/n
Controlable though, nothing too heavy.
/n
I shut my eyes
/n
In a bid to hope that sleep will come
/n
I hear the sounds of rain outside becoming distorted 
/n
Intense CEVs!
/n
Woah
/n
I had no idea! 
/n
These CEVs were where I saw the really synergy between the acid and the methylone
/n
They had the slight dark side of acid, with similar colours. However the bliss was there which carried me through nicely into dreams of utopia with MP.
/n
/n
In all this was a very pleasant experience 
/n
Better than I had expected
/n
There is only one thing I worry about 
/n
And that is, I would be tempted to use this chemical more often for events such as openings and the like.
/n
/n
I awoke early
/n
Typically feeling as though I never slept
/n
I feel great though
/n
A little tierd
/n
But full of positive energy 
/n
/n
I hope MP feels this good</bodytext></report>