<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7336</idnum><title>Soma Overdose</title><author>The Shuffler</author><substance>carisoprodol</substance><bodytext>



The following is a description of possibly the stupidest most careless thing I've ever done.
/n
/n
8:30
/n
Ingest 2 Somas. I chewed them up, it's the worst tasting pill I've ever encountered.
/n
/n
9:30
/n
Not feeling anything from the first 2 pills so I eat one more.
/n
/n
9:40
/n
Getting frustrated so I eat 3 more. This was a mistake no doubt. 5 minutes later I was feeling a STRONG buzz and I knew it coudln't be the 3 pills I just took so I realize I'm fucked, but I don't worry about it.
/n
/n
9:45
/n
Spend the next 45 minutes sitting in a chair staring off into space and occsionally laughing. A real dead head feeling. A completely blank mind. Complete lack of thought.
/n
/n
10:30
/n
Get up and walk around a bit, sit down and an hour flies bye with me rockin around in a mostly circular motion in my chair. This is called the 'Soma Shuffle.'
/n
/n
11:30
/n
Get up and walk around a bit, walking is a lotta fun. It's about the only way to enjoy this sort of buzz. But I sit down and continue the Soma Shuffle. I pass out with 15 more minutes of this.
/n
/n
3:00
/n
Wake up in the ER. Feeling very confused. I can remember maybe 3 flashes of mental images from the time I passed out to now. I had to drink charcoal.
/n
/n
Some additional things that maybe should be noted is that I was COMPLETELY out of it. Two people took me by the arms and walked me a good 300 feet and I don't remember it and never woke up. I also went through some convulsions. This information came from people who saw me on it. Hopefully someone will learn from my mistakes. Some drugs can require patience. It's hard to be patient sometimes. This is understandable. If you're gonna take these or anything else I suggest starting with one pill and then two and so on but only after you're positive the last dose you took is completely out of your system, and stop increasing the dosage once you get a good effect. This is probaly obvious to most people though, but I'm sure there's someone else out there stupid enough that maybe they needed to be told this.</bodytext></report>