<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7337</idnum><title>Legal Speed &amp; Slight Hallucinogen</title><author>Dr. Dali</author><substance>yohimbe</substance><bodytext>



OK if you want to try this stuff be prepared because you may be awake all night.
/n
/n
I went down to my local witch shop where they have all sorts of interesting herbs and potions they sell (to use only for casting spells with ofcourse). They happen to have a ton of Yohimbe bark (ground to powder). I got 4 packs containing about a half an ounce each.
/n
/n
I went home and poured the 2 ounces of the brown Yohimbe powder into a large pot. I then added a quarter of a bottle of vodka (one pint) to it and stirred it all up. I boiled the concoction at low heat for about 10 minutes until most of the vodka evaporated. I then added a quart of water into the pot and boiled that on very low heat (covered) for 20 minutes. Finally, I used a mesh coffee strainer (you can poke small holes with a pin in a regular coffee filter) and strained all the liquid into a pitcher(discard the yohimbe bark).
/n
/n
The result was a brew that tasted like very strong Kava-Kava. I added alot of brown sugar. It wasn't too bad tasting. I procedded to drink a half a cup of this stuff and wait.
/n
/n
A half an hour later I knew this was going to be wierd - severe but manageable heat flashes and the feeling that I just had 25 cups of coffee. What was interesting although was the slight halucinogenic properties that it had. I definately felt like I ate a cap or two of Psilocybin mushrooms.. I got the perma-grin and a little spacial distortion.
/n
/n
We went out to the pub after that but alchohol couldn't tame this beast. I had some interesting babbling conversations with women I did not charm. My buddy drank the stuff as well (a whole glass) and proceded to puke about 3 times that night after drinking moderately. He was up for 2 days he told me.
/n
/n
I let the yohimbe sit in my fridge for a couple days every once in while just doing a small shot - it seemed to get more potent as the days went by. One small shot glass would speed me out for hours. I didn't notice any sexual effects, but it seems like sex would be alright. All I can say is the stuff is kind of wierd in way were you don't really know what to do with yourself, although you can handle it. But if you want a euphoric legal speed- this is definately it.</bodytext></report>