<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>73566</idnum><title>Not Worth the Time</title><author>E1983</author><substance>diphenhydramine</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


I came across a bottle from a friend, I didn't find too much info on experience so I started out small.  On 8/19/08 at 2pm I took 1/2 pill, I took the other half one hour later at 3pm.
/n
/n
3pm I felt slightly light headed and a little excited, mostly from the new experience. 
/n
/n
4 pm I took my second pill
/n
/n
5pm I felt just slightly disoriented, like I had to think about what I was doing, but it was easy to make myself concentrate. 
/n
/n
8:30pm I chewed up 3 pills, then ate a bowl of ramen noodles and took a shower to kill some time. 
/n
/n
10:00pm, slightly aggravated that I wasn't really feeling anything, I was more talkative though while watching TV with a friend. 
/n
/n
11:00pm- Still no changes, everything was the same when I walked. My nose itched and I was getting tired. 
/n
/n
12:00pm- It had been three hours and nothing worthwhile had happened, I figured that night was a bust and I went to bed. 
/n
/n
2:00am- I woke myself up scratching my shoulder. I had Never broken out in Hives before but I think that's what it was. They looked and felt like mosquito bites, on my arms, legs, shoulders, and stomach. My stomach was a little upset. I got up and chewed 2 Benadryl for the allergic reaction. Then made myself calm down
/n
/n
2:30am- Just when I was about to fall asleep I began to feel queasy. I fought it back for 15 minutes, then finally gave in a threw up only about 1/2 cup of fluid. I felt better a few minutes after. 
/n
/n
3:00am- I went to bed, with nothing worth writing home about. 
/n
/n
8/22/08- One last try
/n
I decided to start early. 
/n
/n
I started at 12:00pm and took one pill every two hours. 
/n
12:00pm, 2pm, 4pm, 6pm, 7pm, 8pm
/n
/n
I also took 1 Benadry just in case. But again no hallucinations. No weird feelings, I've had better stronger experiences taking OTC Sleeping pills.</bodytext></report>