<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7361</idnum><title>Yellow Jackets</title><author>krayzee</author><substance>ephedrine</substance><bodytext>


It all started a week before when I saw these really cool looking pills behind the counter at a gas station.
/n
/n
The pills were yellow and black, and actually looked like yellow jackets.  I got some before work where one of my co-workers and I sniffed one for kicks.  We couldn't handle the extreme burning sensation and it didn't really do anything for us, though we both seemed rather pissed off for no apparent reason.  My co-worker at one point went in the backroom and punched the wall.
/n
/n
A few days later I was really tired before work, so I popped two of them, even though the recommended dosage is one.  I ended up working my ass off all night.  I was rather happy and I had a good feeling going through my body, I didn't really like how my hair seemed to tingle, but I didn't really mind.  That night went ok, even though I felt a little sick later that night, nothing major though.
/n
/n
So, about three days later I'm in the same situation.  I wasn't really tired or anything, I got a good night's sleep.  On my way to work, I reached in my glove department, grabbed the bottle of Yellow Jackets and popped three of them.
/n
/n
I work at a restaurant, about a half an hour after I started, I was making the food faster than I've ever seen anyone make it.  It was made well too.  My boss told me I was doing the best she'd ever seen me do.  At about 2:00pm, the lunch rush was over.  It was my turn to go on break.  I made myself something to eat and the same co-worker that I tried snorting the shit with sat with me.  We had plans to go to the driving range later that night, I was looking forward to it.  I took a bite of my sandwich, that's the last bite I took.  There was no way I could eat.  I suddenly felt sick to my stomach, I've never felt that sick before.  I thougt I was gonna throw up, so I went to the bathroom, no luck.  
/n
/n
My boss let me go home early and that's when the shit really hit the fan.  I was trying to relax, lying on my couch, watching tv, when I started throwing up,  I ran to the bathroom and actually threw up blood.  I thought that would be the end of it.  I threw up again about a half an hour later, again blood.  I thought I should eat something, a bowl of cereal, since I lost so much shit throwing up.  The cereal came back up about ten minutes later.  I threw up once more about an hour later, but I still felt like shit. 
/n
/n
My heart was racing and I started to get really paranoid.  I went online and read all this shit about how it's possible to get a stroke or a heart attack on ephedrine.  I really thought I was gonna die.  At about 10:00pm, I felt fine.  I actually felt pretty good.  I still had energy to spare and had a little cool feeling in my body similar coming down on ecstacy, without the psychoactive effects.  I flushed those fucking pills down the toilet regardless.  I can't even look at those motherfuckers again!</bodytext></report>