<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7400</idnum><title>Confusion with Candyflipping+</title><author>Neely</author><substance>mdma</substance><substance>lsd</substance><substance>oxycodone</substance><bodytext>



Let me first say that unlike any of the other times I've candyflipped, this was very spur of the moment.  I still had some time to get some things together, and plan the majority of the night, though.  Also, because of the way I am on these two drugs combined, I usually feel safer doing it alone.  Rather, having somebody with me while I candy flip, but having them either sober or on one or the other, but never both.
/n
/n
The reason for this hesitation is because I was involved in a very serious car accident while on one dose of MDMA a little over a year ago.  Since then, taking ecstasy has never been the same.  My heart beats a little bit faster each time I take swallow that bitter taste.  This time, my best friend Sebastian, who has never candlyflipped, decided to do it with me.  Well, around 9:30 PM, we each consumed two hits of gel tab acid.  Within a half of an hour, the LSD had pretty much kicked in.
/n
/n
I had planned on listening to a certain set list of music that I had made earlier that evening.  So I gathered myself and let the music just play.  Around 10:30, my pill showed up.  I have been told to be skeptical about green pills.  I had never had one before, and I was faced with the situation of whether or not to take it, while my mind wasn't quite working properly.  The funny thing is, there were about ten other people at this place with us, and none of them found out that I was on anything for about another hour (around 11:30).
/n
/n
Well, I ended up getting the pill tested, and it tested to be MDMA, so I consumed the pill around midnight.  [erowid note: the Marquis test sold as /n in 2000 &amp; 2001 do not establish the presence of MDMA and can be used only as a negative test: if does NOT turn black/purple then it definitely doesnt contain MDMA, but turning black does not mean it contains MDMA.]
/n
/n
I had not yet peaked from the acid.  My mind was swirling in different directions.  I was at my house in Phoenix, with a pool in our backyard.  With your perception levels so high on acid, I instantly felt the pill start to work and I could feel what it was actually doing to my body.  Within five minutes, I was sweating.  At that point, I needed to smoke a bowl to calm me down.  I was losing it more by the minute.  After smoking a few bowls, I walked into the backyard with a sober friend, and we just talked.  She walked inside after about ten minutes, and left me outside for a brief period of time.
/n
/n
At that point, I laid on my back and stared up at the sky.  The sky immediately began to spin in a million different directions.  Usually, my visuals are not this intense on acid, and two hits is what I usually take.  At that point, I began to wonder why this time I felt so much more fucked up than usual.  I got scared, and I walked inside and instructed everyone not to leave me alone.  At this point, Sebastian, too was feeling very disoriented.
/n
/n
I have three animals in my house.  Two cats, and one puppy.  Sebastian and I decided to play with our animals to calm our nerves down, so we each brushed one of the cats for about thirty minutes.  I have never been closer to actually communicating with an animal than I was at that point.  I could feel their positive energy flowing through my hands as I brushed them.  Their eyes seemed to be looking directly into mine.  They seemed fascinated at the size of my and Sebastian's pupils.
/n
/n
After calming down with the animals, I walked outside to smoke a cigarette.  I put it into my mouth, and suddenly realized that I was about to vomit.  I ran inside the house and tried to make it to my bathroom, and barely made it.  There was vomit on my shirt, and a few spots on my floor.  I continued vomiting for what seemed to be about five minutes, although I'm sure it was actually shorter.  I was left to clean everything up by myself, because I didn't want anybody to know.
/n
/n
I was scared again, because I have never vomited off of either of those drugs before.  Either separately or combined, both of which I have done at least thirty times.  After vomiting, I realized I had felt better.  Even though I never realized that I was feeling bad, afterwards I just felt so much better.  So, I asked Sebastian to go into the pool with me, and we swam for awhile.  The feeling of the warm water against my body, the cooler breeze hitting my wet head, and the sound of the water as I swam was absolutely amazing.  It was a bit overwhelming.
/n
/n
Around 3:00 AM, everyone either left or went to bed, and that left Sebastian and I up for awhile.  We turned off all of the lights in the house, shut all of the blinds, and turned on the three lava lamps and Pink Floyd.  We sat there and listened to music, and thought about the things going on in our head for awhile.  Then, we conversed about acid, about the cycles that we had seen that night, and life.
/n
/n
Around 5:00 AM, we each took a muscle relaxer and a percocet.  We then smoked another few bowls.  This helped calm us down, and allowed us to sit and relax while we came down.  The sun came up shortly after that, so we retired to my bedroom, where we covered all of my windows with thick towels to keep all sunlight from coming in the room.  We continued laying in bed and talking until 8:00 AM, where we finally lost each other in the others golden slumbers.  I never found out why I vomitted, but it didn't matter after I felt better.  The green pill caused an intense roll, but I would have not taken it had I not tested it first.  For anybody who has never candyflipped, I would strongly recommend it.  But only if you enjoy both of the drugs enough to try to conquer them at one time first.  Sebastian enjoyed his first time and said he would definitely do it again, as will I.</bodytext></report>