<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>75201</idnum><title>The Beat of the Soul of Nature</title><author>Kapitan</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>2cb</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>General</tag><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


I had never had the pleasure of attending one before, but I never
/n
expected drugs to be sold so openly at music festivals. My journey to
/n
Spookstock 7 was long an uneventful, and mostly was spent mentally
/n
preparing for whatever psychedelic experiences I might have. I was
/n
actually doubtful that I would be able to find any doses at all, as
/n
it's fairly uncommon in my home state. I was not to be disappointed.
/n
/n
I awoke to the rising sun at about seven o'clock, on the second day of
/n
the festival. I had arrived at the campground at midnight the night
/n
before, to something like an all-night music and drug party, and
/n
hadn't slept much in the intervening time. I was feeling strangely
/n
refreshed anyway, for some reason. I think it was something about the
/n
atmosphere of this place; everyone I met seemed to non-verbally
/n
acknowledge the strange, subtle connectedness that the psychedelic
/n
state awakens me to. It was, perhaps, the change that was refreshing.
/n
Not many people I normally interact with have been awakened in this
/n
way.
/n
/n
As I climbed out of my friend R's car, stretched, and stumbled around,
/n
I encountered three new arrivals, camped out in the space next to
/n
us. were yelling at passerby, 'Molly!  Mescaline!'. (T-1:00)
/n
'Mescaline', I thought. That was definitely on my long, but
/n
shortening, list of 'Substances To Experience Before I Die'.
/n
/n
In addition to the connectedness, everyone here is just extremely
/n
friendly, too. Maybe it's all the good pot and beautiful scenery. I
/n
don't know. Anyway, I talked to this 'mescaline' guy for a while, and
/n
he invited me over to his campsite, and offered me some hot chocolate.
/n
He told me that what he actually had was MDMA, Peyote extract, and
/n
2C-B, which he explained was like synthetic mescaline.
/n
/n
However, I already knew 2C-B well from my research. I had never
/n
experienced it, though. It is indeed chemically similar to mescaline,
/n
but it has its own unique and interesting effects, also. I knew that
/n
it's effects are described as 'Somewhere between MDMA and LSD, but
/n
completely unlike a combination of the two.' He agreed to sell me one
/n
of his few doses. I took it on the spot, and proceeded up the hill to
/n
the site where people had been gathered around the bonfire the night
/n
before. I knew there would be a good aura up there. (T0:00)
/n
/n
As a bit of background information, I've been having a mild identity
/n
crisis over the past few months. A lot of my friendships had changed
/n
suddenly, and I found myself more alone than I'd ever been. I realized
/n
at this point that I had been defining myself too much by the people I
/n
was associating with, and, in the absence of them, I wasn't entirely
/n
sure who I was, where I was, or even why I was alive. It was very
/n
disconcerting, to say the least. 
/n
/n
The embers of the bonfire of the night before were still smoldering
/n
when I arrived, and about ten of my fellow early morning trippers had
/n
been drawn up here as well. They were all sitting around it, smiling,
/n
sometimes talking sporadically, but mostly just relaxing and being
/n
generally amicable towards the world. I'd never met any of these
/n
people before, but the seemed friendly enough.
/n
/n
A kid in glasses and an all-over print t-shirt welcomed me over. This
/n
was the first time I'd seen the camp in the daytime, and I must say,
/n
it is beautiful beyond description. It was a perfect day. Clear, blue
/n
sky with a warm sun beating down its pure energy onto us. The
/n
greenest, softest grass I'd ever seen encircled the fire like a
/n
carpet, stretching away into the woods at the bottom of the
/n
hill. Birds were flying in an unbelievable dance of life far above us,
/n
as the fire crackled in what I thought was a wise and especially
/n
soothing manner. I was definitely beginning to feel the effects of the
/n
drug now. (T+0:30-0:40)
/n
/n
All of my previous trips have been with tryptamine compounds, and what
/n
I found is that, if 2C-B is any indication, phenethylamines are much
/n
more pleasant. Much warmer, much friendlier, less 'glitchy', and with
/n
less distracting visual activity. That's not to say the visual
/n
activity is not there. If anything, it was much more intense than with
/n
other drugs I've tried. However, I was able to ignore it much more
/n
easily. It wasn't as mesmerizing as what I would see on, for
/n
example, LSD. This was a good thing, as it lets me focus more on my
/n
soul, which is what I came here to do.
/n
/n
When it finally arrived, after maybe 45 minutes, The come-up was fast
/n
and fairly intense; almost overwhelming. I felt the energy of it
/n
washing over me in waves, and it felt amazing. If I had been in a more
/n
neutral or hostile setting, things probably would have been
/n
frightening at this point, but I knew that everyone around me
/n
understood, and was supportive of my state of mind. This made it much
/n
easier to bare my soul, and slip into a pleasant state of openness and
/n
unity with my surroundings. (T+0:40-1:00)
/n
/n
Before I had been there thirty minutes, the kid in the glasses and an
/n
old hippie got together with a guitar and a drum, and started playing
/n
music. It started off rough, and before long the kid admitted that he
/n
was 'too fucked up on mushrooms' to be playing guitar well. Everyone
/n
laughed in that kind of spaced-out way, they switched instruments, and
/n
then proceeded to play the most beautiful music I've ever heard. The
/n
trees swayed, the wind blew, the birds swooped and dove in intricate
/n
patterns, and it seemed as though the whole valley was dancing to the
/n
beat of our collective soul.
/n
/n
Colors ... are amazing. Acid never did the colors thing for me, but on
/n
this ... the grass was the greenest green I have ever seen. I'll never
/n
forget it, as long as I'm alive. The world is a beautiful place, if
/n
only you can eliminate your bias and stop filtering the beauty through
/n
your worldview for a moment. I am in love with this place.
/n
/n
The birds ... its almost as if they act as a single organism, some
/n
kind of a pseudo-hive mind. Every one of them has a soul, but,
/n
together, they are something greater. Something ... beyond ... mere
/n
birds. They are a collective. WE are a collective. We are at peace.
/n
/n
It was quickly apparent that 2C-B is also much more of an intoxicant
/n
than LSD is, at least for me. My memory was dramatically affected, and
/n
somehow in-sync with the waves of energy crashing over my
/n
consciousness. The rest of the trip was superimposed upon sets of
/n
clearly-defined waves of beauty, awareness, and clarity. It was as if
/n
I was in a movie, and, at points, I would suddenly 'awaken' in a new
/n
place, as if a cutscene or transition had taken place. I was fully
/n
sane, conscious, and aware in the intervening time, and I remember it
/n
clearly, but it's not nearly as important as when I was on the crest
/n
of a wave of energy. Its as if I was coming to orgasmic revelations,
/n
every twenty minutes or so.
/n
/n
I remember clearly, at the peak of my come-up, two older clean-shaven
/n
men came over and sat down around the campfire with us. For some
/n
reason, it was obvious to me that they were undercover cops. Looking
/n
back, I'm not sure if they actually were. However, a man in camoflogue
/n
came over to the campfire, talking in a walkie-talkie, convincing me
/n
beyond a doubt that we were surrounded by some kind of undercover SWAT
/n
team. 
/n
/n
He reached down behind a log where a kid was sitting, and picked up a
/n
bag of weed. 'What's this?'  he said. 'Will you please stand up, sir?'
/n
I was sure that we were getting busted, and was really high at this
/n
point, so it was kind of starting to freak me out. But, it turns out,
/n
the guy was just selling weed. 'Crappy weed is what it is. Nugget
/n
delivery service!' he said. 'Somebody buy some nuggets!' I didn't see
/n
or hear about anyone get arrested during the entire festival. The guys
/n
that I suspected were cops even smoked some of the pot with us. (T+1:30)
/n
/n
As I started to come down from the crest of my first wave, I wandered
/n
away from the campfire, and walked down 'Shakedown Street', the place
/n
where all the vendors are set up. Everyone's face was severely
/n
distorted, but not in a menacing way. It was an obvious drug effect,
/n
so it didn't cause me much worry. The people didn't seem to notice
/n
that I was tripping, or just simply didn't care. I felt a strange
/n
benevolence towards everyone, tinged with a hint of suspisciousness,
/n
as I still suspected there were more undercover cops around here,
/n
somewhere. I didn't have anything on me, so it wasn't a fear, but
/n
rather an understandable delusion that I held for twenty minutes or
/n
so. There probably were cops around there, with all the drug
/n
trafficking going on. However, I recognized it as a drug-induced
/n
delusion, and brushed it off before I left Shakedown.
/n
/n
Eventually, I ended up by the creek that runs through the bottom of
/n
the valley. It's nothing like the creeks from my home state, all muddy
/n
and brown. No, this one was perfectly, unbelievably clear, like in a
/n
dream. Three more dudes were sitting by the creekside playing drums,
/n
and again, it seemed like they were playing to the beat of the
/n
river. Through the music, it seemed to me that they had uncovered the
/n
secret heartbeat of nature. Why hadn't I heard this before? (T+2:00)
/n
/n
I sat there for nearly two hours, in the sun, listening to the drums,
/n
the river, and watching the golden spiderwebs of the morning sky dance
/n
across the perfectly clear water. I bathed in the radiance of the
/n
heartbeat, its warm, pulsating waves. The energy of that time was
/n
absolutely amazing.
/n
/n
I find that, personally, with the exception of Ayahuasca, the 'comeup'
/n
of psychedelics in general is not nearly as useful, in terms of
/n
introspection, as the 'comedown'. That is, the comeup is more
/n
enjoyable, but, if I take anything away from the experience, I'm going
/n
to learn it while descending back to sobriety. That turned out to be
/n
especially true with this substance. During the last four hours or so,
/n
I spent a lot of time wandering around, both in the campground, and in
/n
my mind.
/n
/n
I realized that my identity crisis was more an issue of where I was
/n
derived from. That is, I need to be part of a collective, a culture,
/n
perhaps, or a group of friends, but I cannot be OF that culture. Much
/n
like the flock of birds on the hill, I need to enter into it,
/n
independently, as a developed person, and bring something new to
/n
it. Any other way, I would either be defined by cultural norms, or an
/n
outcast. I need to push out my identity to those around me, rather
/n
than pulling in theirs. This was my problem, and the realization of
/n
this greatly settled my soul, and still does, as I write this more
/n
than a month later.
/n
/n
After the sun had ascended so far into the sky that I could no longer
/n
justify calling this a 'perfect morning', I ended up back at the
/n
campsite of the people who had sold me the 2C-B. They were rolling up
/n
a blunt. Perfect. Everything had that shiny, plastic sheen of order,
/n
yet identity, about it. They invited me over to smoke. It was a
/n
wonderful, communal experience. I felt close with everything. I had a
/n
very intense feeling of having arrived home, at long last. (T+4:20)
/n
/n
There was what seemed to be an extremely long period of intoxication,
/n
after the main effects had ended. This may or may not have been a
/n
product of all the marijuana I had smoked over the course of the day,
/n
though I suspect it was not. I had the same 'waves of energy' feeling,
/n
but without any of the visual activity, or really anything other than
/n
a mild feeling of drunkenness. It was not unpleasant in the slightest,
/n
but it did seem to go on well past the peak of the experience. I was
/n
just confused as to how I could still feel like I was tripping hard,
/n
but without any kind of visuals at all.
/n
/n
I finally was completely sober around 3 or 4 PM. The world retained
/n
its beauty, however, and, strangely, the grass retained its surreal
/n
green color. Even today, I will occasionally come across a
/n
particularly green patch of grass in the morning or evening, with the
/n
sun falling across it just right, and I will again be overwhelmed with
/n
the beauty of the world.
/n
/n
All in all, I think this was hands-down the best trip of my life. I
/n
didn't learn as much from this substance as I did from Ayahuasca, and
/n
it wasn't nearly as intense as LSD or psilocybin mushrooms, but,
/n
rather, a soft, warm day spent in paradise. I'm glad I had the
/n
opportunity to experience this. Highly recommended.</bodytext></report>