<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7523</idnum><title>Guiding 101</title><author>EmmanuelGuide</author><substance>unlinkable</substance><bodytext>



A guide to me is someone who is called to open others to their spiritual nature.  A guide is sensitive enough to allow spirit guides to direct them to those who need help or are ready to become exposed to their spiritual nature.  A guide is different than a sitter who just watches over someone during a trip.  A sitter usually does not provide the material and/ or direct the individual in any way. As a guide, I usually am drawn to someone who has received the calling but doesn't know what it is or what to do about it. Often these people are in some form of trauma or emotional upset.  They usually have never had a psychoactive experience.  
/n
/n
When i establish contact with someone i feel is ready, i work on getting their trust and try to develop their understanding that they are ready to enter the realm of higher consciousness.  Then i provide the material and explain what it is, as i believe one should know what they are putting in their body and how much.  I then work with them to develop the mind set to be open to whatever comes up and to surrender to the experience.
/n
/n
The setting comes next, usually in their home or wherever they tell me they would be most comfortable, safe and undisturbed by outside distractions. I try to build a nest, usually on the floor in the living room with pads, blankets, pillows, water, music (new age, no voice), unplug phone etc. 
/n
/n
Having instructed them to not have eaten for at least 6 hours, i then go to the experience which starts with getting relaxed and discussing the material and answering questions that come up.  This time, just before and after ingesting is principally trying to minimize fear and get the person to open to the experience.  I usually try not to interfere with the persons journey unless they want to talk or are in difficulty.  with this type of preparation i seldom have a person get in trouble.  During the session i make sure they drink enough water and generally see to their needs.
/n
/n
Afterward, i give suggestions on integrating what came up and not to do it again for at least 30 days</bodytext></report>