<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7577</idnum><title>Four Years of DXM Psychosis</title><author>11enigma</author><substance>dxm</substance><bodytext>


I tried DXM for the first time in nov 1997.  Ever since that date my life has not been the same.
/n
/n
1st time: the first time i got high i drank about 6 oz of tussin and took 8 cold caps (i don't know the brand).  I was with 2 of my friends in a treehouse and I never thought anything would actually happen, but after about 30 min I started feeling pretty disoriented.  The distortion of time is very interesting.  What seemed like 20 min (3 hours). later we tried to climb out of the treehouse and could barely walk.  Later that night as i was falling asleep i would inhale and wouldn't exhale for about 15-20 seconds later.  The high lasted until the next morning and that whole week in school my visual perception was not the same. 
/n
/n
98-00 : After drinking robotussin max strength almost every weekend for a couple months, and getting sent to rehab for a school related incident I stopped doing drugs for a month or two.  Then on the 4th of July 1999 i learned that coricidin can give you the same type of high and since that day I've been eatting Coricidin like candy. The fireworks were cool, but after they would explode we could still see them in the air.  
/n
/n
present:  my point is that ever since that night in 97 my visual perception has never gone back to normal, or what i think normal should be.  When i am not high i get tracers on everything from glowsticks to my own hand... even not doing pills for 3 months in a row hand no effect correcting my perception.  I have gotten into a sick cycle: i believe that this perception of reality is not normal, so i do pills, coming down from them brings me back here, so it feels normal again, but after a month or so things are so unreal again that i have to take pills again to remind myself i'm not crazy.
/n
/n
mabye i'm just psycho or something, but the truth is that my perception is eternally fucked up, so be careful.
/n
/n
Also: ways to tell someone is on DXM:
/n
-eyes are wide open, pupils dilated
/n
-dry mouth
/n
-talk normal, but occassionally say something that is out of the norm
/n
-snap in front of their face and it will take them about 2 seconds and they'll react</bodytext></report>