<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>78045</idnum><title>Mushroom Ayahuasca</title><author>Orion, CO</author><substance>mushrooms</substance><substance>banisteriopsis</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


Citation: Orion, CO. 'Mushroom Ayahuasca'. /n. Vernal Equinox 1998;7(1):7-8.
/n
/n
Into one liter of pineapple juice (used to hasten the conversion of psilocybin to psilocin), I combined five grams (dried and powdered) /n and five grams (dried and powdered) /n leaves. (With all of the literature that I had encountered citing the stems as the primary component containing harmala alkaloids, I felt that using the leaves would offer a mild MAOI effect; assumptions can get you nowhere and everywhere). I refrigerated this overnight. Seven travelers gathered, divided the brew equally, and cruised. The effects were rapid, beginning in about fifteen minutes, rising to a dramatic height and gradually tapering after two hours. None of us were prepared for the intensity, and our focus was not maintained as we had planned. There was a greater internal visionary display than with mushrooms alone, which was more in the green and brown range (more organic) than the blues and red that I usually experience. I also encountered some plant communion with the /n growing in an adjacent room (vining, twining, searching, green), although this was an experience only felt by me and none of the other participants. There was some mild GI upset, and pronounced [sweating], but overall the experience was wonderful. -- Orion, CO.
/n
/n
/n B. caapi /n B. caapi /n
/n
/n
/n
/n
/n
Lordy, I have no idea. I kinda doubt it. Fresh pineapple (especially unripe pineapple) contains a rather potent protein hydrolysis enzyme called [bromelain] which is pretty effective at tenderizing raw meat (and is why there is no such thing as fresh pineapple Jell-O, since gelatin is also a protein). But there is no protein-like bond in psilocybin. And why would one want to do such a conversion anyway? Recent Swiss trials have demonstrated that psilocybin metabolizes to psilocin (and to 4-hydroxy-indoleacetic acid) in the human body. And for storage purposes psilocybin is the more stable compound.
/n
/n
</bodytext></report>