<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>78485</idnum><title>Cosmic Energy Cloud</title><author>Sam</author><substance>5meo_dmt</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Im struggling for words here. 5-Meo-DMT is without a doubt the most powerful substance I have ever experienced, and I am familiar with most things, psychedelics in particular.
/n
/n
I received a sample from an Australian friend, along with some changa. I had previously erred on the side of caution with 5-Meo, having read up on it and well aware of its reputation for potency. I had tried a tiny pinch, and got a pleasant, heavy intoxication, but that is it.
/n
/n
This experience took place at night, lying in bed, with candlelight and Shpongle playing. I decided to dump the rest of my sample into my glass pipe (impossible to know how much, approximately 15-20mg). I applied a flame to the pipe, vaporised, long and slow, and inhaled one, and then another vast lungful of 5-Meo (not that harsh).
/n
/n
Very rapidly, within a few seconds, my consciousness began to mutate in to something very different. I became aware that my mind was being flooded with light/energy. The feeling was very cosmic, of oneness with everything. There were some visual  patterning in this ocean of light, but this seemed a mere footnote compared to the energy I was experiencing. I felt massively intoxicated  very different to smoking DMT. When I smoke DMT, I encounter incredibly detailed and colourful visions, yet during the experience I feel incredibly clear headed. Not so with 5-MeO. The feeling was of pressure, yet incredibly pleasurable pressure, enveloping my being, and this feeling built up very rapidly after smoking. My pulse increased rapidly, my breathing became shallower, and I did feel nausea.
/n
/n
I didnt get the fear with 5-Meo, to be honest I actually find the trance state more inviting than on DMT, which can feel quite cold and alien on high doses. I find it very hard to describe the trance it put me in, particularly in comparison to other psychedelicswords are a poor medium for describing such a state. I was however, very impressed, and feel very lucky to have experienced it.</bodytext></report>