<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>78524</idnum><title>Falling Off a Chair and Hitting One's Head</title><author>tjshokk46</author><substance>dmt</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><bodytext>


My buddy had taken maybe 4 shots of whiskey and drank 3 beers. Nothing crazy but, he had a buzz going. When he got home, he was in a very very happy mood. Ya he was buzzed but he knew quite well what was going on. Him and his buddies had gone for a nature walk earlier and smoked some DMT. It was awesome he tells me. So, he decided to load his pipe the same way. He just used the pipe to scoop up a bunch of DMT and BLASTOFF. [He's pretty sure about 100mg got scooped up because of how much he had left before this incident and how much is left now.]
/n
/n
What happened next is so fuzzy... According to his father, he fell backwards off of his chair and cracked his head really hard. I guess it knocked him out. When he woke up, he was tripping fairly good. He felt so immobilized. He thought it was just the DMT because he was laying where he normally does while smoking. He thought he had a life/death trip where paramedics arrived and blah blah blah so, he woke up saying 'Dad I'm sorry' over and over again. He thought that was because in his trip, his dad saw him die.
/n
/n
When he woke up this morning he spoke to his dad, his dad told him 'you know, you said some really mean things on that shit.' I guess SWIM hit the DMT, fell and hit his head, then went on a rampage trying to fight his father for no reason whatsoever. I guess after that SWIM had gone and laid back down only to pass out and wake up at the point where he was saying 'I'm sorry.'
/n
/n
Now, SWIM knows the alcohol had a good bit to do with it coupled with past issues he's had with his father. I'm sure the hit on the noggin also threw SWIM off (his head still hurts.)
/n
/n
Point is, be very careful with when you choose to smoke DMT. SWIM'S dad almost called 911 yesterday... SWIM would have been in a world of shit. Also, don't be a dumbass like SWIM and smoke DMT while sitting on a tall chair.
/n
/n
I hope you guys take this warning seriously, mainly newcomers.</bodytext></report>