<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7868</idnum><title>Not Worth It - Horrible Vomiting</title><author>Jackal</author><substance>yohimbe</substance><bodytext>



So I saw the yohimbe preparations and decided to try it.  I bought 1/4 of a pound for $7.  I put 5 teaspoons into about 2 cups of water, and boiled it for about 7 minutes. I strained the bark out, and was left with a red mixture.  I added globs and globs of honey, and like this it wasn't at all difficult to drink.  It really wasn't bad tasting. 
/n
/n
I drank the mixture at 2:00 PM, and after about 20 minutes, I started having mild nausea.  I also started feeling something thatis difficult to describe.  Not very dopaminerginic like amphetamines or opiates (that warm feeling.)  It was very strange to walk, kind of like I was walking through water.  The effect was not really that pronouned.  There was no intellectual clouding; I was quite with it cognitively.  
/n
/n
Anyway, the nausea kept getting worse, and it eventually culminated in me vomiting very hard.  I vomitted so hard that I burst the blood vessels around my eyes, and had little red spots around there (I've heard that these go away within a couple weeks if not days.)  After that, I had mild nausea for the next 3 hours, especially whenever I drank or at anything.  I also had to burp every 5 minutes for the next 6 hours.  It did seem to elevate my mood for the rest of the day, as I was quite cheery and giggly.  I also had trouble falling asleep at 12:30 AM, 10.5 hours after I ingested the mixture, despite taking a benadryl.  
/n
/n
Overall, I would definitely not recommend this high a dosage to anyone.  The high wasn't even really a high.  If you want to try it, try one teaspoon, two at most.  In fact, I would just recommend you buy the tea bags of Yohimbe that they sell at the health food stores.  This could be an effective antidepressant in low dosages, I would think.  I will never again have this high a dosage, though I will probably try one or two teaspoons again.</bodytext></report>