<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>7963</idnum><title>Don't Get Silly</title><author>Dougal</author><substance>cocaine</substance><bodytext>


Reading many of the other submissions on this drug it seems that many people are severely addicted to coke. I've been taking coke on a party basis for about 5 years now, and I am definitely not addicted in the way described in many reports. Most of my friends do the same and none of them have any chronic addiction problems either.
/n
/n
How does it make me feel? I guess 'stimulated' is the answer. In a party situation when I'm drunk on alcohol it perks me up, helps me talk shit and keeps the party swinging. If I take it on my own I feel edgy, irritable and a bit sick. I do get some waves of pleasure but also very tense.
/n
/n
I guess I can see where the addiction might start. Once I've started on it, I can't stop until it is all gone, even if this involves lying to mates and keeping some back or secretly doing it when I get back from a club - pretending to do to the toilet to do it. However, the next day I feel like I never want to take it again. My head feels like my scalp has shrunk 2 sizes and my nose feels broken.
/n
/n
An for me, this is the problem. Because although I sincerely never want to do it again...as sure as night follows day....I do. This is not a rabid craving but a more subtle, social addiction. I've just go used to taking coke at a party and don't like the idea of drinking all night without it (or mayb an E or two). What pisses me off is that it's 50 - 100 for a night that isn't any better than when I don't drink. We (my friends and I) say we don't need it but if the dealer fails to turn up you should see the long faces - only for the sombre mood to turn to hilarity and joy when a mobile phone call signals a last minute reprieve. I think we are growing out of it now.
/n
/n
I have overdone it once - snorting most of a really strong gram. I passed out and had TREMENDOUS chest pains and crazy heartbeat. My vision went down to a tunnel and I started to pray. Used 'wisely' (hah!) I guess it can add to a night out but with all social drugs, you want to ask what your real motives are for doing it. I believe the answer is normally related to confidence.</bodytext></report>