<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>81800</idnum><title>Luminosity</title><author>Tia Serendipia</author><substance>iboga</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><bodytext>


One week and one day later, I can write about this.
/n
There is SO much to convey, to report, I won't be able to share it all.
/n
Layers upon layers upon layers of experiences, that continue to this moment
/n
in calm and profound ways. I did the right thing.
/n
/n
I began preparations a week before, cutting out meats, focusing on things
/n
I wanted to change in my life, intentionally introspective and self aware
/n
to the best of my ability. All this time, I had the feeling that Iboga was
/n
aware of me. I'll say this once, then just let it go: I'm reporting some
/n
things that won't jibe with consensus reality. Nevertheless, they are real.
/n
Think what you will.
/n
/n
The day before I was going to take the Ibogaine, I ate only vegetables, and had
/n
my last cigarette in the evening. I'd been sober off alcohol for about,
/n
well, 4 weeks? I spent time in the jacuzzi,
/n
relaxing and focusing, praying and meditating. I invited Iboga in
/n
intentionally during a meditation. Interestingly, I felt acceptance, and my
/n
visualization was intense. Felt like it wasn't self generated at all, and
/n
included splitting me open at the middle (solar plexus? xyphoid process to
/n
pubis?). I sealed and sent my intention with the energy generated by
/n
orgasm, then with some trepidation, went to bed.
/n
/n
The next morning at 9am, I took a test dose of TA extract. I tolerated
/n
this well and took a flood dose carefuly calculated for my height, weight,
/n
gender and length of sobriety. This did not take me where I needed to go,
/n
and so over time, in 300-400mg increments, I made it up to over 3 grams of
/n
extract. Apparently I was a hard nut to crack. Two other people I have
/n
spoken with used the same product and found it very potent, so that wasn't
/n
the issue. (Wish I had boosters, though!!! Damn!).
/n
/n
At around 3?4? in the afternoon, I looked in the mirror across from the
/n
bed and saw some people peeking around the corner of it-from the inside- to
/n
check if I was ready. I called for a giant mouthful of plain yogurt, I was
/n
craving it like mad, lay down, and went on a journey. :)
/n
/n
I threw up only twice, shortly after that, quickly and painlessly. I
/n
suffered no prolonged nausea and no dry heaves.
/n
/n
My BP was strong the entire time, not much fluctuation from my normal
/n
100/70. My pulse stayed at an average 56 beats. I was so incredibly
/n
relaxed. Of course there were visuals. So many visuals I could not possibly
/n
tell you all of them, as time was very different as well. I can tell you it
/n
began with an eye, that saw me. A sense of myself having waited, maybe as
/n
if in a queue, and I was finally seen, addressed. It was my turn.
/n
/n
I was matter of factly and sometimes with humor shown many, many things
/n
about Beverly, and about the world. Much of my thinking was realigned, and
/n
many old wounds were cleaned out. I also know very strongly that I will
/n
take this journey again, that Iboga has more for me, and I for Iboga,
/n
though I realize how presumptuous that sounds. I did indeed communicate
/n
with my dead elders, remember that was one of my early questions? I also
/n
think that my 20 some odd year history with meditation and visualization
/n
and traditional magics were a boon, as was having been fairly sober except
/n
for marijuana and a couple days of recreational darvocet for some weeks.
/n
I also did Not want to be disturbed during the experience, and maybe came
/n
across as bitchy in conveying that (sorry, dear husband!lol). I cried a few
/n
times during, but it seemed that as soon as the emotion made it to my
/n
mouth, I was onto healing the next thing.
/n
/n
I came around the next morning full of light. Or maybe just so clean
/n
inside that my light was visible. If I didn't have a witness, it would be
/n
almost hard to believe that my skin actually glowed. Light from within, I
/n
was luminous. I was enamored of my hands, so pretty and soft, though I
/n
didn't look in a mirror for three days. I didn't think of it.
/n
/n
I again went to the jacuzzi. I was able to sit lotus without a thought in
/n
my head, not a thought! for ten minutes. This is actually amazing, lol. I
/n
was and am so calm. I did not want a cigarette, a drink, nothing. I was
/n
free of all wants, really. A perfectly lovely place to be.
/n
/n
My ovarian cysts have shrunk to the point of being no longer palpable.
/n
This is down from 9cm and visible when I lay on my back. I no longer need
/n
surgery for the moment.  My surgery was scheduled for 9/14. :)
/n
/n
I then dined on a brilliant plate of fruits. In little teeny tiny bites,
/n
lol. Everything tasted divine. Interestingly, for most of my life I have
/n
disliked fruit. Now, I've been to three farmer's markets in one week
/n
because I can't get enough. I proceeded that same day to read 'The Easy Way
/n
to Quit Smoking' (thanks to the wonderful human here who brought that to my
/n
attention) and finished it. I've wanted a cigarette a couple times since,
/n
but mostly out of boredom and when it's a habit (afetr eating, etc) nothing
/n
I can't acknowledge away. :) I am not finding alcohol to be an issue any
/n
longer. I'm not even thinking about it.
/n
/n
I made roast chicken and braised squash on the next night, with a simple
/n
risotto. I needed a splash of wine for the risotto. The rest of the bottle
/n
is still sitting in my house. It is a non-issue.
/n
/n
I also must say that emotions bubbled up after, and still are, but not in
/n
the same way. For the first few days they came like puke or diarrhea. Not
/n
that it was gross, but definitely was a purge, and there was NO stopping
/n
it!!! Lol, walking down the street, getting sad about not seeing my beloved
/n
grandmother one last time before she passed. Looking desperately for an
/n
alley or hidey hole, because, man, I'm going to sob! After each cry,
/n
though, I just felt bigger inside. Wider, more expansive. I now fully
/n
inhabit my skin.
/n
/n
I can breathe into my feet, my breathe moves in me.
/n
/n
Also, in the past I have been buffeted by other people's emotions, I pick
/n
up on them like a sponge, often to my detriment and confusion. This is
/n
amazingly under control now. I am less porous, less...vulnerable? Yeah, but
/n
less porous seems more accurate. I have not lost the ability to connect,
/n
but it's a choice, and I can see whose emotions are whose. This is such an
/n
unexpected gift, but just one of many.
/n
/n
I also look much younger, according to husband and dear friends. My face
/n
feels so relaxed. There is less pain on it, to be sure.
/n
/n
I also am confirmed in needing to escape this darned day job! (In time, in
/n
time)
/n
/n
There is so much more, but this is a decent brief.
/n
/n
I see many things clearly now, and am confirmed in my thinking on many
/n
others.
/n
/n
I know I will be working with Iboga in some capacity, I have no idea how,
/n
but I am confident about it. I did the right thing.
/n
/n
My very heartfelt thanks to Iboga, the place it grew, the hands that
/n
harvested, the entities that got it from there to me, my husband for
/n
sitting with me and everyone who has contributed to the movement.
/n
/n
Particular thanks to the individuals who have taken the time to talk with
/n
me privately, and opened their hearts to me, giving me the gifts of their
/n
time and attention.
/n
/n
It is my hope to be able to give back at least as much as I have been
/n
given.
/n
/n
I am a different woman, or maybe just more profoundly and completely the
/n
woman I've always been. ;)
/n
/n
Love and rockets,
/n
Tia</bodytext></report>