<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>8267</idnum><title>Dark Perceptions Unfolding</title><author>Anonymous</author><substance>2ct7</substance><substance>oxycodone</substance><bodytext>


Dark Perceptions Unfolding 
/n
New Drugs For Population Reduction By Means Of Pleasure
/n
/n
Ok lets start off by saying that I at one time or another decided to obtain some 2c-t-7. The only way I ever came to hearing about it was on the web. So mulling over the effects I came to the idea that it was some what like a trippy physical sensation. The visuals profound and the body load a bit rough but that fact of it being new allured my attention. 'Well lets just get some', I thought to myself. Many days later my 250 mg package came Fed-X right to my door! When I opened the package I found it sealed in a foil and plastic lined corner of a bag closed shut by a heat seal.
/n
/n
Will it be amazing or will it be my demise? Taking the razor I sliced open the bag very, very carefully to discover a off white ivory colored sticky powder. That smelled foul in the chemical sort. I was abile to measure out 14 mg doses and put them in caps.
/n
/n
Having about 5 mg left over I pressed it on my finger and sniffed. Suddenly a burning heat over whelmed my face throbbing from my nose. My head begin to flush with a wave like drunkenness. My mind or my body started emulating thoughts of poisoning. Rushing to the bath room I trying to wash fresh water down my nose. The drip that followed down my throat made me puke in a colorful daze. Feeling hot and cold at the same time I got up and realized it was time to pick up my girlfriend. Scared is what came to mind because of the fact I had to drive. Ah but by the time I got to the car I was ok to drive.
/n
/n
Hours latter feeling bold I swallow 1 cap at about 20 mg. Body weighing in at around 125 lbs. I had not eaten dinner. I also ate a oxycodone tablet for fun. Is it hit me in a much slower time un-like sniffing 2ct7. The oxycodone calms me down as I wait with much anticipation. About 45 minutes latter a stiff strangeness cover comes my mind blurring soft pastels of transparent colors. A body buzz cranks on in a sweaty speediness very much like TMA-2. Yet not as meth like. Swirling in a sensation as though I was on a amusement park ride. I feel a vast space opening up inside the deeper realms of my mind. To another platue I ascend. Visual patterns of simple sci-fi channel nature materialize and fade into much more complex reflections like that of holographic chrome morphic qualities. Back and forth and multiplying layers of hallucinations over whelm me. But yet I feel empty, no warmth like that of MDMA. I found this 2c-t-7 a bit hard to control in the mind transcendental conception of human awareness. Bubbling away I ebb to the keen perception my brain is in a pleaureful state of death. Cells by the thousands exploding sending new switch connections for my thoughts to rely.
/n
/n
At some point later on I can tell a body load is present. A heavy toxic aspect lingering nastiness through out my soul. Hours latter I find it hard to sleep and can't until mid afternoon the next day! Upon waking up I find I can't talk straight. My words come out all jumbled. Oh no! Will I ever get back to normal?
/n
/n
Days latter the word jumbling goes away but a persisting head ache last for 7 days. The likes of a head ache I have never had before ever! My conclusion is that this like all the new ones out there are a evil sort in the production of genocide to who ever really want to experience a mind expanding journey. The only thing is that yeah you will get fuc*ed up. But the price is my brain! I don't think its worth it. Hell this 2ct7's body load seems bad enough to kill! THEY SHOULDN'T CALL THIS ONE MYSTIC THEY SHOULD CALL IT REDUCTION...</bodytext></report>