<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>8306</idnum><title>Raped by an Alien</title><author>Cale</author><substance>mushrooms</substance><bodytext>


My previous experiences with mushrooms had been interesting but mild.  I had eaten an eighth and gotten effects similar in intensity to that of half a hit of LSD.  Over-confidence was my first mistake.  I also was under the impression that I was bad trip immune, since i had taken rather large doses of LSD and never had a negative experience (although I had punched my friend in the face, mistaking him for my own multiple personality in elf-form, I was not in a negative state of mind at the time).
/n
/n
I was at my friend's house.  His father was sleeping upstairs.  We divided the 3 eighths between the two of us, giving us 6 fairly large caps each (it was all caps).  We started off eating 4 caps each.
/n
/n
I felt the trip start to come on within about 20 minutes.  Soon I was seeing incredible CEV's that surpass description.  My friend started saying something like, 'First, I ate the mushroom.  Now the mushroom's eating me!'.  I soon understood exactly what he meant.  I heard what sounded like a corny synthesizer tone, and as it got louder the 'alien' got closer to me.  It eventually attached itself to my head, and began devouring my soul.  Every now and then I would catch a glimpse of this creature in full light.  It was huge, with millions of legs and pinchers and slimy membranes etc.  Definitely an alien, it could have been straight out of some horror/sci-fi movie with incredible special effects.
/n
/n
Then I decided it would be cool to eat the rest of the caps.  My friend wasn't so sure that was a good idea, but I ate one.  He hesitated, then ate one as well.  There were two left, one large and one small.  The large was supposed to be his, but he refused, so I ate it.  I asked if he wanted the last one, or if I should eat it.  He finally gave in and ate it.  He said the effects of the latter two mushrooms were completely instantaneous.
/n
/n
Then things got really intense, quite a bit too intense actually.  The alien was raping me, and it was so loud, it was absolutely maddening.  My friend said something about how he had died and gone to hell.  Soon thereafter he decided it would be a good idea to get naked, which I didn't feel like doing myself but didn't particularly care if he took his clothes off.  I couldn't see my friend, but I could sense his presence.
/n
/n
We had been discussing the possibility of telepathy on high doses of mushrooms, and I'm pretty sure it worked.  As he moved closer to me all his thoughts entered my head, and I realized that he was planning on having sex with me!  This was a very difficult situation, dealing with my friend and the alien at the same time.  He mumbled something like, 'How... are we going to do this?  On the bed?' to which I replied, 'I don't know what you're talking about, but I'm just going to lay here and have my bad trip, alone.
/n
/n
After this he disappeared.  With my eyes closed I felt his presence, even with eyes open, but I could see that he was physically not there.  His clothes and mushroom necklace were all that remained, and I started to wonder if he was still alive, or if he had killed himself, or just disappeared into some hyperspatial dimension.
/n
/n
I tried to sleep, tried to escape the alien, but it was impossible.  I spent the majority of the night tossing and turning, crying and shaking with fear.  Eventually I entered a new phase of the trip, in which I became god, and completely knew everything.  All the knowledge of the universe was right infront of me, I was having a million thoughts a second.  I saw this earth revolving around the sun, and infinite other earths revolving around their suns.  I saw the creation of this earth, dinosaurs evolving into other creatures.  I saw our lives, how fractal and pre-destined they are. 
/n
/n
After awhile it was driving me insane, knowing all this, life seemed so pointless.  Existing was horrible, I didn't want to exist.  I didn't want to think about anything, I just wanted to have peace and be ignorant once again so I could possibly enjoy my worthless existence.
/n
/n
I found a lighter and lit my friends mattress cover on fire.  It was very interesting, watching the fire burn it seemed digital and in fast-forward.  I burned my arm and face in a couple places, the sensations were intense, but far from pain, and I could not feel the burns after the flame was not on them.  I held the lighter in the flames.  I didn't want to exist, I wondered if I would cease to exist if I burned myself to death in the fire.  The lighter exploded, sending a propelled stream of burning lighter fluid across the room.  I decided it was pointless, and put out the fire.
/n
/n
I wandered upstairs, my friend's parents were there.  They knew exactly what was going on.  They said, 'Are you alright?' to which I replied, 'Fine.' and proceeded to lay down on their couch and stare at one particular spot on the wall, thinking about everything and how horrible it is to be god.
/n
/n
My friend's dad said, 'Do I smell something burning?' and ran downstairs.  I guess the fire had started up again.  They're actions were like clockwork, just as they're meant to act, according to the fractal code.  His mom ran upstairs asking me if I was burnt, I showed her my arm.  She acted like it was a big deal, I told her it didn't even hurt.
/n
/n
They called my mother, who arrived shortly to pick me up.  She was crying.
/n
Later I found out what had happened to my friend.  He had ran outside completely naked, trying to kill himself with his own hands and tear his balls off, in order to escape hell.  His dad heard him and woke up.  He was troubling over how to go about asking his dad how to start a mushroom orgy with everyone in the house, including his dog.  He thought his dad was satan because every time he mentioned 'Jesus Christ' his dad would look away.
/n
/n
This was my first 'bad trip', and it was the most horrible and fucked up experience of my life.  In conclusion, ignorance is bliss, and being god is not as cool as you'd think.</bodytext></report>