<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>84250</idnum><title>Don't Take Too Much</title><author>DailyTripper</author><substance>cannabinoids</substance><substance>tobacco</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><tag>Difficult Experiences</tag><bodytext>


Here is some information on my psychoactive use, I am a regular user of Marijuana, Mushrooms, and Alcohol, I have done N,N,DMT, LSD, Ketamine, MDMA, Cocaine, Heroin, and many pharmaceuticals. I ordered a gram (1000+mg) ('99.5% pure') of JWH-018 from a trusted site. After nine hours of trial and error of finding a good dose (3-5mg) I was extremely 'high', I would say I did around seven 3-5mg hits (I didn't have a scale, so I divided my gram into around 400 tiny key bumps).
/n
/n
Next day I woke up at around 11:30 am, oddly I was feeling great very energized (not like I would after a day of smoking some really nice bud). So I was like what the hell I'll just wake and bake (bad mistake), as I had forgot I woke up early in the morning and did a hit to help me go back to sleep. So I loaded up a dose about that I would say was 7mg (it was a normal dose and a half) that was my second mistake.
/n
/n
 (T)11:45
/n
After I dosed I smoked a cigarette, then I noticed something odd, I was the highest I've ever been in my life, it wasn't bad at the time...
/n
/n
 (T)12:?
/n
Then things turned for the worst, I started noticing some intense visual like I would get from mushrooms (things growing, morphing etc) that's when I knew something was wrong, I started getting this ringing in my head... it got louder and louder and louder, until I felt like there was a heart inside my head that was beating like a drum...
/n
/n
 (T)12:45
/n
I started feeling some nausea, so I went to the bathroom... last thing I remember was the room was spinning and it was like a full on mushrooms peak (colors and geometric shapes where moving all along my morphing walls)
/n
/n
 (T)?
/n
I woke up on my bathroom floor, with the drum beating in my head again at the loudest its ever been (I thought I was about to die) then suddenly it stopped, I was completely fine, I was not high anymore at this point (so I thought...) I decided I would jump in the shower, (taking a shower always helps me relax or calm a bad trip)
/n
/n
 (T)1:30
/n
After getting out of the shower I smoked a cigarette and sat on my couch and watched some tv, but for the next hour, every like 5-10 minutes my head would start having the drum beat inside of it and I would be tripping my balls off, eventually it went away.
/n
/n
 (T)3:30
/n
I eventually became sober (feeling great, and energized)
/n
/n
My brother had some of the same effects when he did around a 7mg? hit, except he kept seeing his closest door open (when it was closed) and some monster thing in there..lol
/n
/n
SO some fair warning I would suggest NOT doing over 5mg of pure JWH-018.</bodytext></report>