<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>8428</idnum><title>It Was Entertaining</title><author>Thwar</author><substance>poppy</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><substance>tramadol</substance><substance>cannabis</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>



7/28/01
/n
/n
This report was started at T+50 minutes
/n
/n
First tried to make tea about 3 weeks ago. I replaced two tea bags with a total 10 grams of powdered poppy pods. Boiled for like 10-15 minutes pushing the bags around and such. Split the tea two ways. Me and my friend drank it and didn't feel much more than high from the herb consumed. Thought i might have felt it but only slightly.
/n
/n
Tonight i decided to make it more like how i had read. One person boiled 1 cup water in microwave, then dumped in 3 grams powdered poppy pods.
/n
let steep for 15 minutes, strained, and drank. He said it felt like a little more than a percocet. That sounded promising. I remember reading a while ago a lot of reports saying putting lemon juice in the water would extract everything out better.
/n
/n
I decided, based on previouse experience with hydrocodone and a few other opiates, that i would require a little extra. I decided to triple the dose of the one i had read. 
/n
/n
T-30min - boiled 1 + 1/2 cups water with ~1tbs lemon juice on stove
/n
/n
T-20min - dumped in 9-10grams powdered poppy pods and turned off stove let steep for about 15 minutes
/n
/n
T-5min  - strained with basic fine plastic mesh strainer, left some sediment, it went into solution if the glass was swirled, it was a yellow tan brown color, smelled bitter
/n
/n
T+0min  - drank vile yellow brown liquid, tasted bitter and slightly sour from the lemon, just enough nasty taste to be hard to swallow, chased it with apple juice and a peanut butter kudos bar, worked well
/n
/n
T+10min - stomach seams ok, smoked kind stomach medicine just in case
/n
/n
T+20min - took about a 25 minute shower, felt great, high, not sure if anything else
/n
/n
T+50min - started writing this report, everytime i look at my hand there apears to be a bar of light over my fingers, strange, goes away within a fraction of a second, guess that was good bud
/n
/n
T+1h	- feel good, kinda heavy, read about a feeling in back of neck, sorta feel that, though not sure if it is just me thinking about it, I keep mispelling stuff
/n
/n
T+1:15  - strong pain in lower stomach, tolerable, not like a vomiting feeling wich is good, still feel high maybe heavy too, pinch myself and feel little pain
/n
/n
T+1:35  - feel altered, it feels like it is fading then it comes back, it is an odd feeling, somewhat annoying almost
/n
/n
T+1:40  - open up a bud light long neck (born june 1, 2001), hopefully this will increase effects, though i read one report it made them through up within 5 minutes, we'll soon see, tastes alright
/n
/n
T+2h    - beer done, no extra nausea, except maybe from the nasty beer/poppy burps
/n
/n
T+2:30  - feel strange slightly off, kinda just a mild alcohol buzz, feels like the herb has worn off start ingesting beer number 2, bud light can (born same day!)
/n
/n
T+3:00  - beer 2 done, no real rise in effect, decide to ingest 225mg tramadol, has a nice general sedative feel to it after a couple hours, couldn't hurt
/n
/n
T+3:20  - smoke kind herb, started beer 3, feel high, not sure if i can even still feel the poppy tea no nausea for a while now, only one short bout of nausea at all 
/n
/n
T+3:45  - beer 3 done, feel alright, probably go to sleep here in a bit
/n
/n
T+4:10  - tired
/n
/n
T+4:30  - think I might try to sleep
/n
/n
T+5h	- instead of sleep decide to roll a cigarete, half kind half shwag
/n
/n
T+5:10  - noticing some itching lately within the last hour or so
/n
/n
T+6h	- smoked some kind herb, don't think i can feel anything from anything other than the herb. But I just pinched myself and I am very numb to pain
/n
/n
/n
Well it seemed to come on strong to begin with, though i was high too. It didn't last more than 3 hours. Perhaps the sludged strained off should be eaten to get everything out of it.
/n
I hope this wasn't a strong dose and morphine just doesn't do much for me. I remember reading about how a lot of people find heroin boring. Hydrocodone, even in large doses is pretty boring for me.
/n
/n
Over all it was entertaining. I think next time i will try to tuff out the nausea with no herb. So I can just feel what the tea is gonna do to me.</bodytext></report>