<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>86623</idnum><title>Decent.....</title><author>KD</author><substance>5meo_dalt</substance><substance>cannabinoids</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><bodytext>


To start things off I'm very experienced in many different drugs.  I've taken MDMA, (more times than I can count)  Mushrooms several times, LSD about 50 times, smoked chronic regularly, and have done a few random research chems that I'm not gunna list here.  
/n
/n
I ingested the chemical at 11:20 and although the taste is bearable it reminds me a lot of MDMA which I cant stand.  I have been drinking vodka and gatorade for about 2 hours now, so I've probably had a total of about 4 shots.  I'm not buzzed at all though, I have an extremely high tolerance to alcohol, and I'm not especially proud of it.
/n
/n
Its now 11:30 and I'm starting to come up slowly.  Its amazing how fast the body metabolizes this chemical.  Normally when I take tryps it takes almost an hour to feel anything.  I'm listening to Slightly Stoopid (great band btw) and its sounding better than it normally does.  I have a little bit more energy than I normally would.  The 5-meo-Dalt has almost sobered me up actually, I think I'm going to take a few more pulls off my nice drink :)
/n
/n
T + 1:00 - Those few pulls turned into a few more and I decided to smoke some jwh-018.  I'm flyin high now.  I think I over did it with the jwh-018.  I'm gettin a little paranoid but nothing I cant handle, I've been here before so many times.  I think I'm going to watch Dazed and Confused.  Yeah, that sounds like a good idea.  
/n
/n
T + 1:30 - Its just like Shulgin said in his book.  There are no oevs to speak of but when I close my eyes its like a whole different world.  Its nice but I really dont have a desire to close my eyes cause I'm so into this movie.  Maybe its best to do this in a dark room with some music and some good friends.  
/n
/n
T + 2:30 - I'm completely back down, I'm still drunk, however the 5meo-dalt seems to be gone.  Its nice to have a chem that doesnt last for 12+ hours.  I think ill try this a few more times but its not really what I was looking for.  If you like 
/n
/n
Sorry about all the spelling and grammatical errors.  Its hard to type when you're under the influence.</bodytext></report>