<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>87259</idnum><title>Has No Value</title><author>Bosley</author><substance>5meo_dalt</substance><bodytext>


I bought 5-meo-dalt about 6 months ago, When I received it, I noticed it was white, and I was kinda pissed, because all the pics I seen online showed a brown chemical that did not have any of the same properties. So for a few weeks I contemplated throwing it out, but after scouring the internet, I came upon some trip reports, were people said they took the white crystal 5-meo-dalt and tripped. Some other people said it was a freebase and needed to be smoked. I even read, someone received nrg-1 and 5-meo-dalt mixed together, from a rc supplier. So this makes me very skeptical of this chem. It feels like the chinese run the Research chem market and dont care for, its customers./n
/n
So the first time. Me and my girl friend smoke about 15 mgs each out of a bowl. I start immediately feeling uneasy, as if i smoked rubber. She said she immediately started experiencing tingling, but no euphoria or anything along those lines. I agree. 
/n
/n
2nd time I'm on tramadol, and smoking weed. I tried vaping 30 mgs out of a light bulb for the fuck of it. I immediately regretted this. This shit taste horrible. I've smoked crack, that I bought from a retarded hooker that taste better.  I snort some xanax, cause I just dont feel right. My g/f tries smoking 10 mgs out of the light bulb, and immediately swears she will never do that again. 
/n
/n
3rd time I tried 40 mgs... idk this drug sucks. I didn't feel anything. even after a nasty drip.
/n
/n
4th time Me and my girl friend are starting to come down from 7 grams of powdered mimosa hostilis grinded root bark and 2 grams of syrian rue seeds. We are about 3-4 hours into the trip but since none of us could bear to hold that sludge down in our guts, i think the trip was cut in half. I decide if the 5-meo-dalt is of any value, I should be able to tell now. I try smoking 10 mgs, on top of some mid grade weed, it actually felt like this shit. affected the way I felt. Made it worse. I decided to take 150 mgs of tramadol, smoke more weed, than fall asleep.
/n
/n
I'm  an ex heroin addict, I take anything under the sun these days but alcohol, heroin, and cocaine.  I consider my self a some what experienced drug addict. and in my opinion 5-meo-dalt has no value. whats so ever. I grew up in the DXM-era so I'm willing to feel shitty , or have deal with shitty effects to trip. 5-meo-dalt does not have anything. no visuals, no buzz no high. No value.</bodytext></report>