<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>8772</idnum><title>Exactly What I Was Looking For</title><author>Bomb</author><substance>cannabis</substance><substance>amt</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



OK in the interest of science I decided to share my first AMT experience.
/n
/n
I started with a brand new scale upon which I weighed out two piles of AMT a 25mg and a 20mg dose. (Im 205lbs)
/n
/n
I thought I would just start with 25mg to get the feel of it so to speak.  So at 7PM down the hatch it went.  
/n
/n
After about 30 minutes I felt a little speedy and until about +1:30 hours I kept feeling like I was going to roll, but then nothing happened.  Worth noting is that there was no nausea at all.
/n
/n
So after 2 hours, down the hatch with another 20mg.  It turned out to be the right decision.  It was about 9:45.
/n
/n
At 10:30 we all went to a huge music festival in Miami to see Oakenfold and a bunch of others at an indoor/outdoor party (formerly know as Mekka but now put on by Space)
/n
/n
Around 11 or 11:30 I started to feel very trippy and happy.  No real visuals, but just in a great frame of mind and feeling fantastic.  And still no nausea to speak of.
/n
/n
Around midnight I decided to smoke a blunt and see what would happen.  
/n
WHOAH!! Lift off.  The synergy between the pot and AMT was incredible, no visuals in the acid sense of moving stuff or swirling patterns, but things would kind of zoom in and out of my frame of reference and things seemed to move faster and then slower.  Very weird but good.  While dancing I would close my eyes and be in my own world until I would run into someone and be yanked back into reality with little idea of how long I was gone.  By far the best thing was simply the mindset that I was in.  Everything was perfect and I was just so happy with a nice body buzz to go along with it.  Things were pretty erotic too, but that could have been because of some of the women there were beyond hot.
/n
/n
A side note  One of the girls was this very hot chick with a skirt that was diagonally cut so it cut across her groin just below her sweet spot, she also had on this mesh bikini top that was see though.   She was just insane with her photon things that created all theses geometric patterns in different colors when they moved.  Well she would do her little dance thing to blow you up then kind of squat in front of you looking in your eyes.  When she did she would spread her legs and let one of the photons dangle between her legs so you could see she had no underwear and had a pierced clit!  Then she would just smile and get up and dance some more.
/n
/n
At points I wish I could come down just a little. There was no place to chill or get away from the overwhelming bass and lights.  I was almost overwhelmed at points but only to the point that I thought of leaving and loosing my $40 since there was no reentry.  At points I felt my heart really racing and with the music roaring it was hard to relax and calm it down, and Im sure the dancing didnt help.
/n
/n
I stayed at the peak until around 5:00 or so, when I started to come down it was a huge relief,  I needed to get home and was a little afraid that I might be very late and have my woman worried about me.
/n
/n
By 6:00 I felt almost sober but if I paid close attention I knew I wasnt but just didnt know how I knew. No visuals or anything just a slight high feeling.
/n
/n
I was able to get to sleep around 7am with my last 1mg of xanax and slept fitfully until 2:30 the next day.  I felt pretty slow but not as bad as the next day with E.
/n
/n
I was out of it for the whole day, but the next day (today) I am fine and well rested.
/n
/n
All in all it was a great experience. It was exactly what I was looking for, a substance for those times I want to go out but dont want to roll since I rolled recently.
/n
/n
For me it was a much better experience than acid, but I missed the cool acid visuals.
/n
/n
At some point I would like to try it at a higher dose in a non social situation to get a better feel for the true power of the drug, maybe (80mg or so) but 45mg was plenty (maybe a little too much) for a social situation in a trip friendly environment.
/n
/n
BTW I am usually a hardhead with acid, 2-ct-7, 5-meo-dipt etc, but not with AMT.
/n
/n
I also wonder if I didnt feel nauseous because of the split dose or simply because AMT doesnt make me nauseous.  BTW I have felt nauseous before on other things but never to the point of puking, but I have never done mescaline or any of the others that you are almost guaranteed to puke on. So YMMV.</bodytext></report>