<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>88011</idnum><title>Great but Dangerous</title><author>Dretch</author><substance>carisoprodol</substance><bodytext>


First the bad, I had my first soma overdose after 8 months of heavy heavy use. It was not uncommon on a fun day to take 10 300mg somas, (not EVER at once). I take 600mg for a warm euphoric melty high. Usually just relax and listen to some music. When I would go out I'd take 4 to get a stagger warm and melty high. Almost like XTC in a way. Then I accidently took too many I took at least 10 within an hour and a half. Its kinda like alcahol I just got on a roll kept on going with no one home and ended up on life support in a coma. Even veterans will get shot down, always get high with friends and be social, it will save your life. IMO its the best drug in the world, I'd choose it over any other pharm for sure and I'd be high all day everyday for the rest of my life.
/n
/n
I havent stopped using though, I just got more responsible with I do. Bottom line is if I'm gong to be dumb I do it smart, or die. This was the most painful overdose I ever have had and I have crossed that line a lot. It was like being stuck in a painful flex, I couldn't really talk, deffinatly not walking. Luckily I was with friends and the seizures hit first so they called the ambulence and saved my life. I quit breathing shortly after the ambulance got me to the hospital.
/n
/n
Over all though if it was up to me I would outlaw booze and legalize soma. Than no one would care about pot becase its both a head change and body high. Although withdrawl is horrible. The bad side affect for me was not erectile... well broke dick, if anything I can have sex longer because of the lack of feeling there and hightened sense everywhere else. Its really hard to deal with the shaky hands especially when just doing everyday things like going to the store, smoking a cigg, well anything in public because I drop stuff sometime and people stare.</bodytext></report>