<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>8814</idnum><title>It Felt Like My Brain Was Beaten With A Brick</title><author>Oscar</author><substance>clonazepam</substance><substance>dxm</substance><substance>amphetamines</substance><substance>cathinone</substance><substance>bupropion</substance><bodytext>



Last night I decided to try dxm again.  I drank 500mg of dextromethorphan in the form of cough syrup.  After getting the vial taste out of my mouth I decided to check up on a small batch of methcathinone simmering on my stove.  The batch was almost dry, so I scraped it up and later took around 100mg of m-cat (a little too high of a dose).  I cooked the m-cat out of curiosity, and had no intention of selling or even giving it to anyone else.  I don't believe in drug dealing.  Anyway, I then browsed the internet for a while before the effects came on.
/n
/n
Now, before I go on telling you the rest of this completely fictional story, I must tell you what else I had in my system - my regular dose of wellbutrin 400mg-sr, 40mg of Adderall (a mix of dextroamphetamine and amphetamine), and 2mg klonopin.  All of these were legal prescriptions, it just happened that I took the Adderall and the klonopin all at once with the dxm.  The wellbutrin was taken earlier.
/n
/n
Back to the story.  After taking adderal/DXM/klonopin combo, I felt the effect of the speed within 10min.  At 20min I felt the rush of the speed combined with the calming effects of the klonopin.  My eyes started to feel like they were going to pop out of my head, my heart started beating faster, I felt a nice warm goosebumpy feeling flow over my skin in waves.  I must note that I had just been prescribed the Adderall for ADHD, so my tolerance was very low. Around the 30 minute mark I took the methcathinone, a substance that is similar in chemical structure to methamphetamine but has very different effects.
/n
/n
The m-cat came on within ten minutes (this stuff is is very fast orally).  The m-cat gave me tremors and I started to feel a little paranoid.  M-cat just seems to jack your mind up.  Its a stimulant, and feels like a strong dose of caffeine without the sickening caffeine side effects.  It causes much more paranoia than any other stimulant I have taken and also doesn't do shit for concentration.  Anyway, at the 50min mark I start to feel a little woozy and slightly nauseous.  The dxm was starting to come on.  For the next hour I was heavily speeded up and paranoid.  Come to think of it, that's not a good state of mind for a DXM trip or any hallucinagen for that case. 
/n
/n
Fast forward to the two hour mark.  I start feeling the full effects of the DXM.  Floaty, a spinning feeling, mind starts wandering off, etc.  The problem here was that DXM makes me paranoid as hell, and I was already paranoid.  I had hoped the klonopin would help to keep me calm but it was overpowered by everything else I had taken.  At the 3hr mark, I peaked on the DXM and couldn't bare to look at the coputer screen any longer, the letters were starting to become 3D.  My eyes couldn't focus on anything.  I tried listening to the radio and couldn't stand it.  I tried putting in a favorite CD but it just irritated me so I tried a more relaxing CD, ah yes Jimmy Buffet, that oughta do it!  Nope.  I started to think that the DEA could come a knocking.  I wasn't enjoying the trip, or shall I say mind-f*ck.
/n
/n
Finally, around the six hour mark I started to come down.  I for some stupid reason ingested another big dose of methcathinone!  Aghhhhhh.  For the next two hours I felt like total hell.  I felt psychotic, with horrible thoughts of death, getting the door kicked in, etc.  Any little sound made me jump.  It horrible.  I decided to try and end the paranoid feeling and took 3mg of klonopin.  I paced around the apartment, bored as hell with this horrible DXM hangover.  My eyes still couldn't focus, my mind was numb and my head felt just plain f*cked.   
/n
/n
Finally, within an hour I felt the relaxing effects of the klonopin bringing me back down.  Ahhhh, much better.  The annoying paranoia, shakes, and the feeling of my brain just being beaten by a brick remained throughout the day, but thanks to my lovely little klonopin friends I got through it.  Bad combo, bad setting, crappy drugs with the exception of the Adderall and klonopin.  Never again...  The end, dasher.</bodytext></report>