<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>8824</idnum><title>Two Faces Of Oxycodone</title><author>Squanch</author><substance>oxycodone</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>



This was my first experience with oxycodone, I wasn't quite sure what to expect. I took two Roxicets (same thing as Percocet), 5mg oxycodone/325mg acetaminophen and waited for the magic to happen.  After about 20 minutes, I felt my heart flutter a bit, but I've felt much worse fluttering from E and such, so I wasn't worried.  A few minutes later, my entire body itched - it wasn't so bad that I couldn't do anything else, but I found it slightly annoying.
/n
/n
I had been told by a friend that wrapping yourself in a blanket and watching cartoons was some kind of heaven, so I did the same.  I found that as long as whatever I was watching was either relaxing or funny, I was having quite a good time, but if something offensive came on the screen, I was quick to start screaming at the TV in protest (Jerry Falwell usually has that effect on me anyway whenever I channel surf). I was curious so see exactly what other effects the drug had on me, so after about an hour of just chilling on the couch, I took a hot shower in complete darkness (something I LOVE to do while baked).  The hot water was fairly relaxing, but the best part of the whole shower experience for me was drying myself off - I mentioned earlier that I itched all over, so rubbing a rough towel all over felt really damn good.
/n
Then, I retired to my room for a while, turned on some tunes and some porn. The porn held my interest for about two seconds, and the music wasn't all that interesting either, although I did notice some strange audio things going on, like sound coming from the walls and different areas in my apartment, rather than my two crappy speakers. I can imagine that a very paranoid person might freak out if the same thing happened to them.
/n
/n
I wandered around my apartment for a little while longer and I decided to take another pill. I wasn't really tired at all, so I decided to go for a bike ride.  A voice in the back of my head kept telling me that this was the worst idea in the world, I had no idea if I would be able to even ride the damn thing in the condition I was in, but the rest of me was determined to find out.  As it turns out, there was no problem whatsoever riding the bike.  I did find myself seriously contemplating doing some other very bad things, such as random acts of violence and vandalism--things that usually get me nervous enough just thinking about them so as I won't do them, but this time, I wasn't nervous at all.  But, I'm generally a nice guy, so I didn't do anything else that I shouldn't have.
/n
Eventually, I got back to my apartment and started making preparations for some of the random acts of violence I mentioned earlier, just in case I really did want to do them, but I ended up watching TV for the rest of the night, wrapped up in a blanket.
/n
/n
Here's the moral of the story for those of you who skipped ahead, or maybe those who just like things summarized, or maybe both:
/n
I can definately see how oxycodone can be extremely dangerous.  I've read that oxycodone is habit forming from a physiological standpoint, which is one HUGE reason why you need to be very careful when using this drug.  But, more importantly, at least in my limited experience, the drug made me much more agressive and also suppressed the little voice that says, 'Don't DO that!'  What a wonderful world would it be if the streets were littered with hyperagressive oxy junkies with no conscience looking for their next fix!
/n
/n
There are two circumstances that I can see for this drug to be very beneficial, and I use that word very LOOSELY.---
/n
1.  Chilling out watching cartoons, wrapped in a blanket.
/n
2.  If you find yourself in a position where you NEED to do something illegal and your conscience keeps holding you back.
/n
/n
Do yourself and everyone else a favor, if you decide to take this drug, be VERY careful!</bodytext></report>