<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>89004</idnum><title>A New Year</title><author>Whiterussian</author><substance>unlinkable</substance><bodytext>


So this is my first report but not my first use so i think this chem needs a lil recognition. 
/n
/n
so after drinking hard and doing adderal for the three days i went home and recovered from New Years. After sleeping almost 20hrs i woke up around 2 in the morning. With nothing to watch on tv and noone to txt, i go jonesing and i srcape an empty syringe and a bowl. i mix the crystals with some rez and put it in my bong. this chem isnt water soluble so smoking through a bong doesnt affect anything.
/n
/n
So i take the first hit nice and slow and only clear half and cover the top immediately feel it one hit is comparaple to a bowl or two of k2 so i clear it and do the same for the second hit. I can definitely feel it now pretty high and as far a i could tell it just intensified my high just as much as the first hit. And not even a few minutes later something says fuck it lets get high (a real high) so i have about half the rez gone and dont see any crystals on the rez. I rip all thats left in one hit and exhale my neck jerks and my sight changes quickly the the verticals of my sight squeeze together and the horizons stretch. This was a high. tv is instantly interesting i remeber and laugh about old lost friends weird moments and just happy thoughts. (: 
/n
/n
Well after about twenty or thirty minutes of hystericals laughing in a NOT SCARY CRAZY WAY i took notice of the hallucinations both open and closed eyed, tracers, and intense lights the hallucinations werent like trippin on shrooms more like the front seat of a roller coaster like its projecting towards you but not to intense and the closed eyed visuals were pretty much paisley objects moving in space melting me into a relaxing nap for a few hours. 
/n
/n
--smpke this shit dont eat it or snort it or stick it up your arse hole your wasting the drug it takes much higher doses (120mg) for for those routes and none of those doses ever got me even close to this trip. also it burns like hell so shootin up is at your risk and like i said not water soluble so it dont cook well.
/n
/n
[Reported Dose: '5 - 15 mg smoked']</bodytext></report>