<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>89229</idnum><title>Skeptical to Believer</title><author>oneman</author><substance>cannabinoids</substance><substance>syrian_rue</substance><bodytext>


Intentions: to see the result of syrian rue and indian warrior together and to see if my last attempt at using these items was just bad preparation or if they dont actually work. I will end up suprising myself this time.
/n
/n
Preparations: did not eat for 6 hours prior to ingestion.
/n
/n
Last entoxicated day: 2 days before experiment
/n
/n
Mindset: skeptical
/n
/n
12:00am I drink a concentrated concoction of syrian rue and indian warrior together. I walk to meet up with friend who says he wants too kick it because he just moved yesterday and is staying at his grandparents house.  I call him and he says he will be a while so I sit down at a bench on the trail near my house and smoke a cig.
/n
/n
12:30am I am just about to dose out the jwh-018 when I remember that I had taken the naturals earlier so I wait and as I do I meditate.
/n
/n
1:00am I do not feel anything but a slight headbuzz and this is very faint. I decide I am going to dose out some jwh-018 and let it sit in the home made vaporization pipe I have on me until I feel more from the drink I had earlier.
/n
/n
1:30am I realize that I am starting to see lines and tracers with faint silver outlines on everything I look at. Yet again this is faint but still abnormal. I know I am feeling it at this point because I think these things are normal until I remember what I drank earlier.  You should know I usually forget what I did earlier because I am listening to music or talking to friends usually. I got the call from my friend saying he can kik it now so I smoke the 15 mg's jwh-018 and get on my way.
/n
/n
1:45am I am fucked up at this point. I am seeing mearcury collored visual lines everywhere and there are geometric patterns when I close my eyes. I am forgetting where I am walking but I keep on walking anyways. Luckyly I recive a phone call from my friend telling me he sees me and tells me where to go. I explain whats going on.
/n
2:15am  I am sitting on my couch now. I dont remember how I got home. I am seeing tons of lines everywhere and floating through the air. My friend is way fucked up. He is crossfaded and I am laughing. I only realised I was laughing at this point because I realized I was out of breath and thought I couldnt breath. I calmed myself and redosed at 15 mg's again.
/n
2:20am (black out)
/n
/n
11:30am I feel extreamly hungover and feel like shit. Mom is bitching about a mess me and my friends made the day before working on our airsoft guns. I still feel very.. Euphoric but like shit.. At the same time.  Dont know how to explain. Kind of like if you were to get hit in the head by a baseball bat but at the same time be getting head???
/n
/n
5:30pm I realize that I blacked out yet again and fell asleep in my chair. I will not be messing with that high of a concentrated dose of syrian rue. I have proved to myself that my last attempt before this one was just a bad preparation of the syrian rue and this really works. I am not one of those guys that just says that it works because I want u too feel like a dumbass and waste your money. I am a skeptic and this worked for me.</bodytext></report>