<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>8957</idnum><title>Crazy Trip and Always in Control</title><author>Mesc</author><substance>cacti</substance><bodytext>



I have tried San Pedro 2 times prior to the trip I had yesterday and I would like to tell you about it in a brief summary of what happened.  
/n
/n
Preparation
/n
First I cut the cactus into small slices and removed the core. Then I placed the pieces in a pressure cooker for 3 hours adding water as necessary.  I was left with about half a liter of dark green liquid.  I then took out the remaining cactus and put it in a blender and strained the remaining liquids out of it and combined all the liquid and put it in the fridge.
/n
/n
The Experience
/n
The next day I drank it around 2:30 and spread out the drinking over a 45-60 minute time period (it tasted really bad). I then took a bus to a park in LA and went exploring in the desert with 2 quarts of water and all the bud and snacks I could bring with a backpack.  When I arrived about 3 hours after ingesting I felt a little different but not much and no real visuals or anything.  I then hiked to a very beautiful spot and smoked three bowls of kind bud. After the third bowl I was gone, I looked at the mountains and stared at them while colors became brighter and textures were better defined.  All of a sudden the entire mountain was flowing like water in wierd patterns and shapes all around me, I saw frames of people walking and everthing looked like I was looking through a kaliedescope.  The really great part was that if the visuals became to intense for me I could turn it off and calm down.  I have tried acid and shrooms several times before and somtimes I can't control it but with this cactus I was in total control. I could also think very clearly.  I would just sit and contemplate things while I would stare at the trippy scenery.  I suggest for all people who try this to go to a park or a very beautiful natural area and bring along some bud and just relax and let the mescaline take you away. Try not to eat too much before or while you are on the drug, to prevent vomiting.  I also use grapefruit juice as a chaser and gargle it in my mouth for about 10 sec. after consuming the cactus and I cannot taste it at all.  Use this drug wisely and not as a recreational drug (I would suggest never doing this more than 3 times in a week, although I felt no come down or after effects of the drug)  This is an amazing substance that you must try. The effect last until I go to sleep but visuals slow down after about 6 or 7 hours on it.</bodytext></report>