<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>89583</idnum><title>Fun Night With Friends</title><author>Gagak</author><substance>mdai</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><tag>Glowing Experiences</tag><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


Some friends and I ordered a few grams of MDAI on an internet website that we'd ordered other chemicals off before. I researched MDAI and honestly, had low expectations. My preferential chemicals are Methylone and MDMA. I had taken a couple months off doing anything other than alcohol so, I was excited to try something, but had read many descriptions of others taking this chemical with little or no effects.  
/n
/n
We took 100mg dose mixed with liquid and had a couple of drinks (2 or three strong drinks). Not alcoholics anything, but we drink quite a bit, so when we started to feel it, we questioned ourselves and thought it could be the alcohol.  About 25 minutes after initial dose we knew it was more than the alcohol.  I had an inexplicable happy feeling and felt as if I could talk forever.  People I had been pissed at just an hour previous suddenly became my best friend.  The feeling was a lot stronger than I had expected it to be and I really loved it.  Everyone in our group had the same reaction to the initial dose and we all decided to up it about 50mg a little over an hour after initial dose.  I'm not sure how much this did, but my high lasted a very long time. I peaked at about 1 hour and stayed at peak for about an hour. After that, I stayed pretty high for 2-3 hours.  
/n
/n
I slept easily through the night (usually does not happen with me and methylone or MDMA).
/n
/n
The following day I was drowsy, but felt great.
/n
/n
I don't know why my experience differs so greatly with others.  I was thinking at first that maybe the website had sent us a different chemical, but if so, which one?  I have tried the others that would be similar and it didn't feel exactly like any of them.  Also, the alcohol??  Perhaps a few drinks really boosts it a lot, I'm not sure.  Either way, my experience was phenomenal and look forward to trying it again.</bodytext></report>