<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>909</idnum><title>Vivarin - Intense</title><author>Madness</author><substance>caffeine</substance><bodytext>



I have been taking vivarin regularly, just for something to do, be hyper and to have a little fun.  One friday, me, a couple friends and my brother went out.  As usual, we had nothing to do, so i took about 2 vivarin, and drank 2 cans of mountain dew.  Effects of mild body warmth and relaxation, not wanting to move. We went to a place we like to eat, and i ordered the fish plate.  I was not sure if i had acted normal there.  I was not hungry, but for some reason i ordered fish (don't ask why), and for a drink I ordered a mountain dew, unfortunately not refillable.  Right before we left i took 2 additional vivarin with my mountain dew.
/n
/n
On our way around, about 2 miles from the restaurant, i felt different than i have ever felt.  My body felt intensely warm, good feelings.  I took my off my hat, because if i did nothing, i felt sick.  Korn was playing on the cd player rather loudly.  I continued to hit my shoulders with my hat, trying to look like i was doing something (i dont know why).  I could not stop singing the music because it was so loud.  I felt very sociable, stiff.  We went to my grandmother's neighborhood.  I had no idea we were seeing if they were home. I felt awful, thinking i would be like this in front of my grandma and grandpa.  Luckily, they weren't there.  This was a relief.
/n
/n
Leaving her neighborhood, i felt as good as i'd felt since i had tripped last.  Everything flowed together.  My perception of depth was as if things were really close to me. This was my peak.  This lasted for about 1 hour. As we reached a local Eckerd [drug store], i just sat in the car.  I thought to myself, i wish i felt as i did an hour ago. But when i went home there was a mild hangover, just stomach pains.  I would recommend doing as i did.  Just keep checking your pulse to see if it's too fast.</bodytext></report>