<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>91102</idnum><title>Break-Up on The Akashic Plane</title><author>Lytesbre</author><substance>4_acetoxy_dmt</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>


Dose - 15 mg ACO-DMT  ('K')
/n
       20 mg ACO-DMT  ('V')
/n
/n
850 pm - drank powder dissolved in water
/n
910 pm - felt a heavy vibration, palms sweating
/n
/n
We sat on a couch , holding hands, that's when we noticed our palms were 
/n
sweating. Indian raga music playing on stereo.DMT like visions with 
/n
closed and open eyes.
/n
/n
K--I entered into a golden realm with a bright deity present, who said 
/n
very clearly 'Not with him' which snapped me back to the awareness of 
/n
sitting on the couch. I asked V 'What does that mean?' And V, 
/n
flabbergasted, twisting and turning,said 'What do YOU think it means?'  
/n
My response was indignant and I wanted to go after the entity that had 
/n
said this to me!
/n
/n
V-I was deep into the music and felt like I was entering a sacred realm. 
/n
Suddenly I got to a point where I was being told where this realm and 
/n
music is only for those entering with a single heart and pure love. I  
/n
could go no further till I had expressed my pure heart. I took K by the 
/n
hand and said let's go lie down on the bed. We cuddled and preceded with 
/n
our trip.
/n
/n
K-Upon cuddling, I entered into a beautiful moving colorful oneness with 
/n
V. I sensed V taking my hand, approaching a golden being, where he had a 
/n
conversation with it, requesting us to enter together into the entryway 
/n
beyond the being.V pulled me into the entryway, where we became as one 
/n
and back into the beauty of the oneness with V again. I was loving this 
/n
so much and I said to V, this is so beautiful, where are you taking me? 
/n
and V responded , 'That's what we're going to talk about..'
/n
/n
V-I confessed/explained that my heart was not int the same place as K's 
/n
and that I had to be 110 % honest before we continued this journey 
/n
together. K told me to chill out and relax and we continued to embrace.
/n
/n
K- I went back into a huge golden space that the entity had permitted us 
/n
to enter, it was beautiful but I as I went further into the entryway,  I 
/n
came upon the essence of some kind of accident/ train wreck/distortion, 
/n
preventing me from going any further. Very clearly, I was now told to 
/n
listen and be quiet. I was not permitted to speak..However, I was 
/n
blurting out things I was not suppose to say, and constantly reminded to 
/n
be quiet at least four times.I.I perceived V to my left as a golden 
/n
being on a throne,and to my right was the entryway with the being 
/n
inside, I was dressed all in blue, veiled, with bangles all over my 
/n
dress. I was in a realm of intense blues and golds.I laughed at V, and 
/n
said 'You will not be my God!' V, angered said 'You will laugh when I 
/n
tell you to laugh' I responded with silence.
/n
/n
V- I remembered saying to K, I like to hear her laugh, it is interesting 
/n
that she heard it a completely different way.
/n
/n
K- in my anger, I now possessed a staff in my right hand and I went into 
/n
the chamber where the entity was and proceeded to tell it that it was a 
/n
false god and that Jesus  was the real God and that he had created 
/n
everything, including them. I raised my staff and struck the being and 
/n
it vaporized. I did this repeatedly with many entities, I was angry and 
/n
like a warrior princess archetype. I was now thrown back on the bed, 
/n
noticing how I would go in and out in waves. V and I were astonished at 
/n
how beautiful we both looked to each other and commented on it. and we 
/n
cuddled and kissed...even with all the ongoing craziness of it we still 
/n
had a love for each other.
/n
/n
V-We had some intense conversations on our relationship and due to my 
/n
personality and her religious beliefs that there were some 
/n
irreconcilable differences. K pointed out some very astute observations 
/n
on what my problems dealing with woman were. Boy, did she nail me! These 
/n
were some valuable insights. I realized and said that I was like a wolf 
/n
stalking his own heart .We also discussed our very different spiritual 
/n
beliefs. This took place over a span of  several hours as we would 
/n
alternate intense conversations as the effects of the drug ebbed and 
/n
flowed in waves.
/n
/n
K- I would drift back to the beauty constantly, but I could only go so 
/n
far until I encountered the vision of a trainwreck. This happened four 
/n
times, I didn't want to face it and on the fourth time I realized that 
/n
the trainwreck was V's relationship with me..and I was now trying to fix 
/n
it.
/n
/n
At 5:30 am the most intense parts had passed, sleep was difficult,so we 
/n
both took Xanax.We were both shocked at waking up at 5:30 pm on the 
/n
next day !
/n
/n
V- Basically this was an incredibly potent substance, but like MDMA I 
/n
believe that this has strong empathogenic and therapeutic properties. We 
/n
both joked that we had saved thousands of dollars in therapy bills!
/n
/n
K- With the right person, the person you love, this could be the best 
/n
experience of oneness one could ever have in this lifetime.</bodytext></report>