<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>92434</idnum><title>Qualitative Description</title><author>Alexander Shulgin</author><substance>tma2</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
/n   end image-surround   /n
/n
/n
Qualitative Description: TMA-2
/n
/n
Dose: 12mg + 1mg = 13mg
/n
/n
Date: Sunday May 30, 1976: 11:40 = 0.00 - no EtOH for 5 months
/n
/n
1:10 Onset of first threshold effects - slight nausea - probably coincidence - but numbing of 4-5th fingers of the left hand. But these fingers have been troublesome (Right hand too) and are often asleep on awaking in mornings.
/n
/n
3:00 Really pleasant, with-nature euphoria. Sat behind lab on steps in the sun how often I have been apprehensive in a drug using that some emergency or other crisis might occur requiring sane logical action, and would I be able to respond adequately - but I here realize that if a fire, strange person, insect- were to threaten - then, and only then, do I need to consider the situation -so- until then enjoy - I did.
/n
/n
This was in especial contrast to yesterday's study on DMT - perhaps I was so attentive to the possibility of some falling-down-stoned response, that I neglected to be receptive to a true altered state of consciousness - without perceptual change, without pretentious impact, without the LSD impact or the DMT physical aspects.
/n
/n
I am completely convinced I would be able to handle 16 mg by myself and this as a full dose would quite accurately be 20 M.U. (with mescaline at 300 mg base - say 320 mg = exactly 20 M.U.). However, I would not care to pretend to be responding normally to a demanding world.
/n
/n
5:20 still with it. Tried to elicit visual distortion by going (1st time) into Cost Plus Imports in W. Creek. No such induction. Did a rather bad job of driving however. Had to pretend distractions. /n To 'All the Presidents Men' - with no clear visual distortion. I MUST REMEMBER - an ASC need not have visual disruption as a symptom!.
/n
/n
8:00 Drove to Berkely Farms for dinner with N &amp; her mother. Still odd driving which N. commented on (What is the matter with you?). I had forgotten where the place was! Clearly emerging. On into evening without further events except a light sweatyness 10:00-12:00. Difficult (mental disturbance) in going to sleep
/n
/n
This is a clear ASC process - perhaps valuable to describe (display) to a subject what this all is - without some annoying sensory modality demanding attention by misbehaving. Interesting day!!</bodytext></report>