<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>92432</idnum><title>Threshold Effects</title><author>Alexander Shulgin</author><substance>dom</substance><tag>General</tag><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
/n   end image-surround   /n
/n
/n
Threshold effects of DOM
/n
/n
Jan 9 1964
/n
/n
Dosage: Dissolved 1.6 mg as HCl in H20 - pipetted out 1/8 -&gt; 1.4 mg computed down to free base 1.19 call 1.2. at currently 180 lbs -&gt; 81 Kg = .0147 mg - 14.7 g/Kg thus - assume initial at 11 g/Kg - max differentiate at 20 /Kg - and effective (useful) at 17 g/Kg = 220 M.U. ! This is too optimistic probably ~ 120 better value
/n
/n
Times corrected to 0 hrs at 7:05 - moment of ingestion.
/n
/n
1:15 - am talking to AM in his office - am suddenly aware of warm flushing and tingling in genitalia - the usual hint that I am going to be sick. My mouth is very dry. I want to leave and tell AO but I cannot for several minutes.
/n
/n
2:05 - teeth are quite rubby - there is the feeling of heavy pressure on the ears - as if some one were squeezing my head - mouth has the taste of having smoked far too much the night before (haven't smoked since 1962 - no EtOH for 9 days). I would like to go outside and run away but I am afraid my heart wouldn't take it.
/n
/n
3:15 Morning is creeping along - I feel I am paying a physical price without any mentally distorted reward - I feel at this point - at a somewhat higher dose - this will be a psychotomimetic.
/n
/n
3:35 To greenhouse - distinct pleasure in looking at the lush salvia divinorum - the smell fits the appearance - signs of visual distortion - at a somewhat higher dose things would creep and crawl.
/n
/n
4:00 Still at it - considerable hyperventilation - eyes dilated 10-15% over normal
/n
/n
4:25 I think I start out here - do not have any desire to eat but I do eat - and complete my lunch (chicken, banana, apple.)
/n
/n
7:10 eyes ~20% dilated - I am still shaky as if my body had had a vigorous drug blow - but mentally I am O.K.
/n
/n
one or two more awareness in afternoon ( at ~8, ~9 hrs) P.M. fine. next A.M. fine.</bodytext></report>