<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>92698</idnum><title>Should've Called Poison Control Bro</title><author>ilovethagreenery</author><substance>spice_product</substance><substance>alcohol</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><bodytext>


I was at a party with my girlfriend and I did not have any bud, so I bought some synthetics called 'Diamond Dove'. I arrived at the party and I started to drink some vodka. I was drunk and had ran out of alcohol. I wasnt satisfied of how fucked up I was so I took out my Diamond Dove and packed a bowl. I had only taken 2 hits and about 10 seconds later I had felt the following: 
/n
/n
-my heart beat was 3 beats per second, at 180bpm, 2nd degree hypertension. 
/n
/n
-I was leaning sideways when walking and all sounds echoed strongly
/n
/n
-my vision would pulse everytime my heart beated
/n
/n
-my vision was extremely swirly like a horizontal S and moved not stop like a wave.
/n
/n
-my reaction time a about 5 seconds 
/n
/n
-I collapsed on the balcony against the railing and was in aw when looking at        everyone staring at me 
/n
/n
-many people tried to help me but I kicked them away because I thought they were going to kill me
/n
/n
-I was screaming at the top of my lungs 'go away!' 
/n
/n
-my speech was slurred to where it would only be mumbles and grunts (I was actually trying to say a full sentence)
/n
/n
-I had sat on the railing for about 15 to 30 mins
/n
/n
-when my girlfriend tried for 15 mins to get me up and to the car so she could help
/n
/n
-when I had gotten up I fell again
/n
/n
-eventually she got me up and literally was holding my whole body up
/n
/n
-I punched her in the face leaving her with a black eye (she told me that the next morning because I did not remember)
/n
/n
-I passed out in the car
/n
/n
-woke up in the car near my house with my best friend in the drivers seat
/n
/n
-I tried with all I had to just move my arm and when I did I threw up from the movement 
/n
/n
-I got the bed spins in the car and passed out again. 
/n
/n
- 2hrs had passed and my heart rate had not decreased
/n
/n
- I had a seizure (yes a real seizure) and my friend had to help me 
/n
/n
-they had spent 30 mins to get me out of the car but I would refuse.
/n
/n
-stumbled inside and luckily no one was home
/n
/n
- passed out on my bed 
/n
/n
-woke up and I did not remember a single thing (not exaggerating, and my memory had come to me weeks later)
/n
/n
The day after that night I had gone out with my friends and smoked more, geeking about what had happened. You can never stop a true stoner from smoking.</bodytext></report>