<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>93364</idnum><title>Vaporised</title><author>Dioptre</author><substance>2ce</substance><bodytext>


I won't go into a full diary style report, I just want this to give a rough summary of my experience vaping 2C-E.
/n
/n
I use a lightbulb vape which I am pretty good at using. I load whatever in there and then hold a flame about 1-2cm away from the glass to prevent sooting. When I see the first hint of vapour I will usually begin inhaling, keeping it on the heat if I want a strong hit. I typically hold in hits for a good minute.
/n
/n
2C-E develops a thick white vapour when heated. A rolling hit (breathing while heating) gives an easy-breathing smoke which is barely noticeable. A regular hit (heat then hit) is the same, unless a thick vapour is allowed to build in which case the smoke is quite harsh and leaves a burning sensation, much like DMT.
/n
/n
The first time I did this was with 9mg. I would equate it to about 15mg but I do not think I vaped all the material. 
/n
/n
I tried to smoke all the material at once. I felt my alert within 5 minutes and peaked within 15 minutes. I would say the experience last about 2 hours after which I was left with a very mild psychedelic mentality for an hour. I used 2mls GBL to sleep after this.
/n
/n
The second session was 10mg loaded up. I took a medium hit and peaked to about 4/10 within 10 minutes. I continued to hit the vape whenever I wanted to up a notch for the next two hours. After the first one hits seemed to come almost instantly, peaking within 5 minutes. 
/n
/n
I think this has awesome potential for managing your dose to find a level you like.
/n
/n
At one point I was lying in bed with the subwoofer set to max, enjoying waves of euphoria with each vibration from Amon Tobin's ISAM.
/n
/n
After my last hit it took about 2-3 hours and a good cycle to stop tripping, but I still had a strong psychedelic mindset until I went to sleep.
/n
/n
I did not finish all the material so I cannot give an absolute dose comparison to oral, but my experience was more intense than 15mg oral. I would estimate that vaping is around twice as potent as oral consumption
/n
/n
Hope this helps clear some of the fog which surrounds vaping 2C's.</bodytext></report>