<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>9348</idnum><title>Simply Amazing</title><author>Krazy_Calvin</author><substance>salvia</substance><bodytext>



It was about 10 at night the first time I decided to try the salvia I had bought.  I bought 1 gram of the 10x salvia from a website I got linked to.  All I had lying around at the time was a pipe, but FAQs I have read about it said to use a water bong.
/n
/n
As i packed the bowl and got ready to smoke it, prepared for the experience by doing a couple things.  First, I shut all the lights in my room off except for one small lamp.  Second, I turned on Pink Floyd's CD, Dark side of the moon.  Last, I set up my camcorder to record the expierence.  Everything was set, and I started the camcorder.  I took out the pipe and lit it up.  The first hit was very harsh, but i held it in.
/n
/n
The FAQ i read said to take a deep hit and hold it for 30 seconds.  I held it as long as i could, almost thirty, and blew it out.   I coughed for about thirty seconds after that.  As soon as i got my breath back, i took a second hit.  This one was easier to hold down, but i still wasnt feeling anything.  I held it in for 30 seconds.  I blew that out and took the last hit.  This one was very difficult.  I had a hard time lighting the lighter and my head was feeling heavy.  I took the hit and tried to hold it in, but even that was hard.  The salvia was starting to take effect.
/n
/n
Over the course of the thirty minutes that it lasted, quite a few weird things happned.  for the first couple of minutes, I just felt like i was melting. I couldnt keep any of my bodyparts up in the air, and it even seemed like liquid was hard to keep in my mouth. for the next five minutes or so I just climbed onto my bed (which was a HARD task) and layed down there under my blanket.  The blanket felt really strange.  It felt like it weighed 500 pounds but it was still confortable.
/n
/n
After I finally got out from under the covers, I felt strangely compelled to dance to the music.  I still couldn't stand up, but as the notes of the music got higher, it seemed that I had to move my body higher away from the bed, and as the notes got lower, i had to get closer to the bed.  I danced to the music for a few minutes intil I got tired.
/n
/n
I cant quite remember what all happened after this, so i will stop here.  All in all, I liked that first experience.  I did it a couple times after that and it was pretty interesting both times.  If you have the time and the money, Buy the 10X salvia.  My whole expierence lasted about 60 minutes (thats the time it took til my thoughts were clear.)</bodytext></report>