<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>94526</idnum><title>Combined with an SSRI</title><author>iofthehurricane</author><substance>sertraline</substance><substance>4_fluoroamphetamine</substance><tag>Combinations</tag><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


This chemical has great potential, and is a new favorite of mine. Very experienced with psychedelics/ empathogens/ stimulants, and decided I would give this a try.
/n
/n
50mg Zoloft is taken daily, but I will touch more on this because I feel the SSRI may have negated some of the euphoric effects. It was still a very beneficial experience.
/n
/n
Total time (come up to comedown): roughly 5-6 hours, simply body/ slight mind stimulation for the last couple of hours.
/n
/n
0:00 - Stuck my finger into the bag of the 4FA and took about 3 licks (roughly 80mg), first reaction. WOW, what an awful taste! Reminds me of eating an acidic/ sour powder of some sorts, I recommend NOT insufflating this substance.
/n
/n
0:25 - Stimulation and slight euphoria start to kick in, wow this is shaping up to be a great evening!
/n
/n
0:45 - Full effects have set in, very euphoric (lasting about 2-4 hours). Body feels weightless, endless energy, lights/ colors and music are GREATLY enhanced. Mind is flying with  various thoughts, ended up sitting down and simply writing in a journal for a couple of hours. My ideas seemed to piece themselves together, and create conclusions to different issues I have been encountering.
/n
/n
1:30 - Still feeling great, very sociable and talkative. ALOT of energy.
/n
3:00 - Euphoria seems to be weening off a little bit, but definitely still apparent. 
/n
4:00 - Very little euphoria if any at all at this point, but still just loving life. 
/n
5:00 - Pure body stimulation at this point, the energy that I had hours prior are starting to come to a close.
/n
6:00 - Very tired at this point, still feeling body stimulation. But was able to fall asleep shortly after this point.
/n
/n
Overall reaction to this chemical: 
/n
Really can't beat it.
/n
It's fairly easy to obtain from various online vendors, and has great effects [for an empathogen lover].</bodytext></report>