<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>94779</idnum><title>Fear and Loathing in New Hampshire</title><author>Cullen</author><substance>nbome</substance><substance>mdma</substance><substance>lsd</substance><bodytext>
/n
/n
/n
I started off the night in the car waiting to go into the club. I was a bit nervous to try pure MDMA for the first time, only having done E that was most likely cut quite a bit. I dissolved 150mg in a bottle and drank it along with two of my friends. After that we each blew about 50mg each. 
/n
/n
We walked into the club and paid to get in, and made sure to get bottles of water for each of us. After about 10 minutes i started feeling euphoria. I felt bliss in its purest form. After dancing and hanging out for about an hour one of my friends and i walked out to his car and we each put a blotter of acid on our tongue which was the equivalent of 2 hits. I danced and held the blotter on my tongue without swallowing until it was completely dissolved. 
/n
/n
We had an hour long ride back and i was still rolling because the music in the car still sounded better than any i have ever heard. We stopped at a gas station and my other buddy put a blotter of acid on his tongue. There were 4 of us in total and we made sure that we all did the same dosage of lsd and 25i. I put two blotters of the 25i under my upper lip and waited for the best. 
/n
/n
We drove about 2 minutes when i started feeling the acid kick in. Things started looking odd and it was hard to keep my eyes focused on one single thing for a period of time. We got back to his house and the trifecta had started. All three of them were working their magic individually, yet combined at the same time. 
/n
/n
I had the up feeling of molly, the colors of 25i and the mind altering of LSD. The combination was such a feeling that i have a hard time describing it. I saw a film of colors on anything and everything that i looked at. especially my phone and the TV. 
/n
/n
This feeling lasted me until about 10:30 the next morning. I had initially taken the molly at about 12 midnight. the acid an hour later and the 25i an hour after that. The feeling was incredible and i would suggest it to anyone that doesn't get enough of a kick out of the three individually.</bodytext></report>