<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>9496</idnum><title>Living Light in New Orleans</title><author>Fionuir</author><substance>absinthe</substance><tag>First Times</tag><bodytext>


A friend of mine got her hands on some Absinthe in England and successfully brought it back with her.
/n
/n
Since it was made in the Czech Republic, we decided that it was authentic and not just absenta.
/n
/n
Nothing could prepare me for the taste of that stuff.
/n
/n
At first it wasn't so bad, but after our first glass my taste buds hated me. We found out subsequently that we weren't adding nearly enough water, and our sugar cubes weren't melting becuase we weren't lighting them on fire. We live in New Orleans so it wasn't too hard to ask around and find out what we were doing wrong. But despite our amateur approach, the effects were actually the same as when we drank it the proper way. Like others have said, absinthe does not get you high. It wasn't even really a noticeable phenomenon for us.
/n
/n
We were sitting in our darkened kitchened drinking and playing Scopa, and there wasn't much around for visual stimulation. Everyone was ready to turn in for the night when I went out onto our balcony.
/n
/n
There's a huge moss-infested oak tree right outside our apartment and I realized suddenly that it was very, extremely, oddly green. My friends joined me on the balcony and without my prompting they voiced my exact thought about the color of the tree. From there we decided a walk might be nice.
/n
/n
The light from the street lamps was thick and very orange, and the contrast between where the light fell and the darkness laid was very stark. It occurred to me in a way that the light might be alive. We passed a building where one of my friends decided he needed to go inside and urinate. The rest of us hid from him behind these tiny skinny tree-lings. We stood there with our arms and legs bent like a bunch of kids, trying not to laugh. The funny thing is he actually didn't see us for a few minutes. Then he shook the tree branches so that the evening's rain fell on our cheeks and hair. From there we came to a fountain that just begged for us to play in it. We walked back to the apartment soaking wet and laughing and went to bed.
/n
/n
The coolest thing about our experience isn't that we were fucked up, or that the absinthe was making us do all these silly things. They were things we always want to do but don't always feel it's okay to act in such a way. For an evening she told us it was okay. Since then we've had many quiet evenings and giddy evenings and many laughter-filled walks through the mindight streets of New Orleans, hand in hand with the Fey.</bodytext></report>