<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>95579</idnum><title>Overdose (High Stress, Anxiety for Weeks)</title><author>movetheshadow</author><substance>methoxetamine</substance><tag>General</tag><tag>Post Trip Problems</tag><bodytext>


A brief report due to having to write on my phone.
/n
/n
Having tested the substance with a friend at low doses 50mg and then 100 approx and experiencing only threshold effects, mild stimulation and very slight ketamine style cev's.
/n
Decided the following night after a few beers to take 2 150mg doses a couple of hours apart.
/n
The result was a journey that literally blew my mind.
/n
Ketamine-like in nature, but very different all the same.
/n
I lost all sense of self, stretched and pulled across time and space, experiencing ever more absurd things, becoming everything and nothing. Alot of amnesia follows the experience.
/n
One situation that stood out was a period of extreme vibration, I was a highly electrified being, dragged up into a place that was inhabited by 2 being, it was a large and open space, they were smooth faceless and this was the only part of the trip in which I felt I had a form, I communicated with them through a form of energy conversion language, pushing and pulling.
/n
/n
The majority of the trip was k-hole style travel. Seemed darker and more absurd, worm holes, becoming the suggestion of things that could happen. 
/n
/n
The entire journey was 5 hours in the 'm hole' the ever effects were pleasant closed eye visuals.
/n
/n
On a serious note, the dose was too high, the substance is very hard on the central nervous system and left me with a permanent high stress and anxiety feeling which persisted relentlessly for weeks.
/n
/n
Use with caution, the dose I took caused extreme pressure on mind and body. I won't be researching this chemical again.
/n
Much better alternatives are available.
/n
Methoxetamine took me deeper and darker than ketamine, felt like a 20 journey and I suggest extreme caution. 
/n
/n
Stay safe
/n
Peace frogs</bodytext></report>