<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>9611</idnum><title>AMT Combination Reports</title><author>FlowGnome</author><substance>mdma</substance><substance>meth</substance><substance>amt</substance><bodytext>



** WARNING ** Neither of these experiences involved stacking the peaks, nor did they involve high doses of anything.  Even trying either was probably silly, but I thought I'd report one test and no bad reactions.
/n
/n
These are two quick reports of combinations with these substances that I just wanted to add because most information on the internet indicates that AMT is an MAOI, and could cause dangerous reactions with either of these combinations, but did not in the case of a few friends.  All of the people involved are healthy people in their 20s, who have plenty of experience with all of the substances involved.  My personal experience with AMT involves amounts from 17mg-150mg, so I have a good idea of how my mind/body normally deal with it.
/n
/n
1) The AMT + MDMA combination came about during the comedown of the MDMA.  Me and a group of 3 other friends finally decided that we wanted to stay up and chill all night, but that none of us wanted to blow another 25.00$ on another roll.  Thankfully I had a 66mg capsule of AMT with me (don't leave home without it), and we broke it into 4 lines and each snorted one.  The AMT hit fully in about an hour or so, with no nausea.  I noticed no increase in blood pressure or heart rate over the roll alone, and no negative physical effects of any kind.  The AMT synergized with the MDMA, producing more 'realistic' visuals than would be had from that amount of AMT, and generally stronger effects than should be had from that amount, although in general it was mild.  I was able to sleep fine about 10 hours after doing the AMT.  And woke up well-rested in another 7 hours or so.
/n
/n
2) This combination came about somewhere around 8 hours after a group of 3 of us had taken 25mg of AMT.  The friends I was with had found some meth at the rave we were at, and wanted to do some to wake themselves from the beginning of the 'dream phase' of them AMT.  I recommended against it, but they ran off and tried it anyway.  Finally, I gave in, and noted a great synergy.  The ecstasy-like effects of the AMT were back in full force, and I was wide awake again without starting to drift off.  We continued to do small bumps for the rest of the day, mainly to keep awake, and walked around 10 miles during this time.  No abnormal increase in pulse or blood pressure was noticed, again, and no other side effects.</bodytext></report>