<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>9754</idnum><title>Boy next door goes bad</title><author>Birdie</author><substance>meth</substance><tag>Addiction & Habituation</tag><bodytext>



I'm a 29 year old gay male living in San Francisco.  It wasn't until 8 months ago that I discovered the drug/party scene, and I was easily sucked into it.  I started out just doing E, then quickly graduated to K and G.  
/n
/n
I had done my research beforehand about all the party drugs and vowed never to try crystal - all the reports sounded so scary.  Well, when out clubbing one night with my now ex-boyfriend a few months back, he asked if I wanted a bump.  I was starting to come down from my E, so I figured what the hell - life is all about new experiences.  I snorted a bump off a car key and in a minute I felt more awake than I ever had before.  I had this extreme sense of clarity and was so energized.  Now, I already talk incessantly when on E, and the crystal only made it worse.  I could not shut up (much to my boyfriend's dismay).  Never did sleep that night, but paid the price the following day.  I had never felt so strung out and depressed in my life.  I'm normally a very happy, funloving person, but I seriously felt suicidal.  I swore to never do crystal again, and made my boyfriend promise he would never offer it to me again.
/n
/n
Guess what...I did it again, and again, and again.  I've probably done it 10-12 times total, even as of this past weekend.  I find myself craving it and dreaming about it at night.  I'll buy a bag on the weekend, and flush down the toilet what is left so I don't have it around.  Then the weekend comes around again and there I am buying more.
/n
/n
I hope there are people out there like I was a few months ago who are doing their research before they try anything.  I want to tell those people to stay the hell away from this evil drug.  Sure you get a good long high, but the come down is an absolute bitch.  Plus, there are many long term health effects.  I pray I have the resolve to quit this nasty little habit before I get in to deep.  So far the worse thing that has happened to me is that I've lost some weight (7 lbs?)  I was skinny to begin with, so I didn't really need to and people have commented on it.
/n
/n
Moral of the story - don't touch this shit.</bodytext></report>