<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>977</idnum><title>Call 911</title><author>Andrea</author><substance>unlinkable</substance><bodytext>



The other evening I went over to a friend's house (a friend that I have known for nine years) who lives with her boyfriend, to have dinner, a few drinks and a movie.  The pasta and meatballs were delicious complimented by a very small dirty martini over ice.  
/n
/n
After dinner they mixed me another cocktail and I was feeling a little buzzed.  NOT DRUNK!!!!
/n
/n
Her boyfriend brought over three shots of what he called his funky beer shot.  I really didn't feel like doing a shot, but if it was only beer, I thought, what the hell.  So I did the shot.  It tasted like a shot of lime juice.  
/n
/n
They asked me to take a dip in the hot tub with them at the community pool.  I didn't really feeling like going, but they finally talked me into it.  
/n
/n
There were a bunch of people already at the pool, but no one that I knew.  I sat for a while just chatting with people.  I was now on my third drink (this was in a span of about 4 hours).  I began to feel really funny.  
/n
/n
The entire place was spinning and I felt extremely sick.  I tried to hang in there and pretend that this was nothing, but it just got more intense.  I was going to puke for sure.  I staggered to the pool bathroom, and with no hesitation began projectile vomiting all over.  Well, the bathroom was spinning and I felt like I had absolutely no control.  I was really dizzy, but I thought I would try to go back to where everyone was.  I staggered a few feet and went right back in the bathroom and puked like I never puked in my entire life.
/n
/n
The pasta and meatballs were everywhere.  
/n
/n
I stumbled back to their apartment and scrambled looking for a phone to get some help.  I knew that this feeling was not normal....
/n
/n
I finally was able to reach some help.  The happy drunk couple made it back to the apartment and kept walking to the bathroom where my head was over the toilet and my friend(?) would come back in the bathroom and steal the phone away from me so I couldn't make any phone calls. (Very Strange!!!)
/n
/n
I was sad to find out that there is no way to prove that they put this awful drug in my drink.  They will probably deny it forever, but I know the truth.
/n
/n
I am 30 years old and I know what three drinks feel like and what happens to me when I drink too much.  This was not even close to that feeling.
/n
/n
I don't know how anyone can take this as a recreational drug.  It was one of the most horrible experiences of my life.  
/n
/n
Final thought... You don't really know what people are capable of and you just better watch your back in any partying, drinking situation.  When your best friend screws you over, who the heck knows what a stranger could do?!</bodytext></report>