<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><report><idnum>9777</idnum><title>Floored</title><author>kypay</author><substance>mda</substance><bodytext>



Saturday night the 30th of September, I experienced MDA for the first time.  Unknowingly a friend sold my boyfriend and I three blue D&amp;G (XTC, he thought) pills, which later we found out were pure MDA. 
/n
/n
   Aprox. one hour after taking one pill each, we both thought we were sold bunk pills.  Feeling nothing but a little tired we decided to dance a little and try to enjoy the party.
/n
/n
  Twenty min. later, we felt extremly nausiated which we were used to from taking extacy or MDMA.  This time something was different...very different, we didn't know what to do??  I felt weird, confused, oh my gosh, we were FLOORED!  For those of you who don't know what that means, we were pretty messed up, we couldn't even move. I can honestly say I was scared! Before you make any judgements I should tell you my boyfriend and I are frequent extasy users and we both have NEVER, EVER, BEEN THIS MESSED UP! I felt like I couldn't move but yet I wanted to jump out of my skin! I wanted to run circles around the party.  My mind was racing faster than I could keep up with it.  I just wanted to SCREAM , my heart felt like it was going to explode out of my chest.  My eyelids both top and bottom were spazzing out wiggling all over the place, not to mention I couldn't see very well because my eyes wouldn't sit still, my vision was blury, my pupils were all you could see, the irises of my eyes (the colored part) were almost non exisistint. My jaw felt like a vibrator that had a never dying battery, making my teeth chatter so loud people kept looking at me. It was impossible to stop shaking my hands and feet. People kept asking us if we were ok!!!! Now every party kid knows that you have to look pretty messed up for someone to ask you that! The extreme feeling of anxiousness was almost TOO MUCH to handle. Thank God my boyfriend was experiencing the same effects so I had someone to make it through my 3 HOUR PEAK with!!!! Since we couldn't dance I couldn't handle sitting in the smelly bowling ally venue any longer so we decided to leave.  
/n
/n
 We tried to go to sleep around 7:30 that morning after taking our 1st and only pill at 10:30pm the previous night.  RIGHT!  Sleep was impossible!!! We had the side effects all through the next day till aprox. 9:00pm after finally being able to eat. The next day I felt surprizingly normal not all cracked out like I was expecting.   WOW, that was definitely an experience!  If I was ever to take MDA again I think my boyfriend and I will SPLIT a pill! Good luck to all and be safe!!!! San Diego</bodytext></report>